-DOCSTART-	0	O

Event	0	O
and	0	O
narrative	0	O
or	0	O
:	0	O

Difficulties	0	O
in	0	O
comprehensively	0	O
understanding	0	O
Albrecht	1	B-PER
Lehmann	1	E-PER
allows	0	O
refugees	0	O
and	0	O
displaced	0	O
persons	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
their	0	O
say	0	O
in	0	O
West	2	B-LOC
Germany	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
1945	0	O
1990	0	O

Discussions	0	O
about	0	O
asylum	0	O
seekers	0	O
,	0	O
resettlers	0	O
and	0	O
immigration	0	O
issues	0	O
have	0	O
dominated	0	O
politics	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
media	0	O
in	0	O
Germany	1	S-LOC
in	0	O
recent	0	O
months	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
therefore	0	O
not	0	O
difficult	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
moment	0	O
to	0	O
attract	0	O
attention	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
publication	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
book	0	O
on	0	O
refugees	0	O
and	0	O
displaced	0	O
persons	0	O
in	0	O
West	1	B-LOC
Germany	1	E-LOC
from	0	O
1945	0	O
to	0	O
1990	0	O
.	0	O

Indeed	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
hardly	0	O
any	0	O
serious	0	O
scientific	0	O
discussions	0	O
that	0	O
have	0	O
taken	0	O
up	0	O
this	0	O
subject	0	O
so	0	O
far	0	O
.	0	O

Nonetheless	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
questionable	0	O
whether	0	O
such	0	O
topicality	0	O
must	0	O
necessarily	0	O
lead	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
undoubtedly	0	O
pending	0	O
debate	0	O
being	0	O
deprived	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
real	0	O
core	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
blurring	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
difference	0	O
between	0	O
past	0	O
and	0	O
present	0	O
problem	0	O
constellations	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
his	0	O
book	0	O
In	0	O
the	0	O
foreign	0	O
unintentionally	0	O
at	0	O
home	0	O
,	0	O
Albrecht	1	B-PER
Lehmann	1	E-PER
tries	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
a	0	O
neutral	0	O
perspective	0	O
,	0	O
free	0	O
of	0	O
accusations	0	O
and	0	O
protests	0	O
of	0	O
innocence	0	O
,	0	O
towards	0	O
a	0	O
policy	0	O
and	0	O
its	0	O
consequences	0	O
that	0	O
led	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Second	2	B-MISC
World	2	I-MISC
War	2	E-MISC
twelve	0	O
million	0	O
people	0	O
fled	0	O
or	0	O
expelled	0	O
from	0	O
East	3	B-LOC
Germany	3	E-LOC
and	0	O
the	0	O
German	0	O
settlement	0	O
areas	0	O
in	0	O
Eastern	4	B-LOC
Europe	4	E-LOC
have	0	O
been	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
what	0	O
way	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
refugees	0	O
''	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
called	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
pejorative	0	O
connotation	0	O
immediately	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
war	0	O
or	0	O
''	0	O
displaced	0	O
persons	0	O
''	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
the	0	O
common	0	O
name	0	O
since	0	O
approx	0	O
.	0	O

1948	0	O
found	0	O
their	0	O
way	0	O
into	0	O
their	0	O
new	0	O
circumstances	0	O
and	0	O
how	0	O
these	0	O
experiences	0	O
have	0	O
passed	0	O
down	0	O
over	0	O
the	0	O
next	0	O
few	0	O
decades	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
different	0	O
generations	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
day	0	O
,	0	O
Lehmann	1	S-PER
demonstrates	0	O
using	0	O
a	0	O
series	0	O
of	0	O
stories	0	O
,	0	O
personal	0	O
notes	0	O
,	0	O
diaries	0	O
and	0	O
documents	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
expellees	0	O
'	0	O
press	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
picture	0	O
is	0	O
brought	0	O
up	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
although	0	O
not	0	O
surprisingly	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
convincing	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
composition	0	O
,	0	O
allowing	0	O
readers	0	O
to	0	O
comprehend	0	O
a	0	O
specific	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
foreign	0	O
experience	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
respective	0	O
experiences	0	O
and	0	O
their	0	O
coping	0	O
are	0	O
presented	0	O
very	0	O
differently	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
certain	0	O
topics	0	O
keep	0	O
coming	0	O
up	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
rape	0	O
of	0	O
German	0	O
women	0	O
by	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Red	1	B-ORG
Army	1	E-ORG
not	0	O
only	0	O
led	0	O
to	0	O
irreparable	0	O
mental	0	O
disorders	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
women	0	O
themselves	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
to	0	O
complicated	0	O
marital	0	O
relationships	0	O
that	0	O
often	0	O
dominated	0	O
the	0	O
lives	0	O
of	0	O
entire	0	O
families	0	O
for	0	O
years	0	O
after	0	O
these	0	O
events	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
uprooting	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
homeland	0	O
produced	0	O
in	0	O
not	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
cases	0	O
forms	0	O
of	0	O
social	0	O
overadaptation	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
caused	0	O
difficulties	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
long	0	O
established	0	O
population	0	O
,	0	O
especially	0	O
in	0	O
narrow	0	O
village	0	O
communities	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
''	0	O
sentimental	0	O
insistence	0	O
''	0	O
on	0	O
old	0	O
traditions	0	O
and	0	O
customs	0	O
expressed	0	O
how	0	O
incapable	0	O
the	0	O
displaced	0	O
were	0	O
to	0	O
forget	0	O
their	0	O
old	0	O
homeland	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
stories	0	O
it	0	O
becomes	0	O
evident	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
striving	0	O
for	0	O
social	0	O
harmony	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
the	0	O
guiding	0	O
principle	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
long	0	O
time	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
creation	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
sense	0	O
of	0	O
community	0	O
should	0	O
compensate	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
was	0	O
mostly	0	O
experienced	0	O
as	0	O
cruel	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
exhibiting	0	O
such	0	O
typical	0	O
difficulties	0	O
,	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
book	0	O
's	0	O
strengths	0	O
is	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
emphasizes	0	O
the	0	O
differences	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
experiences	0	O
of	0	O
different	0	O
generations	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
thus	0	O
becomes	0	O
plausible	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
generation	0	O
that	0	O
grew	0	O
up	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
1960s	0	O
and	0	O
1970s	0	O
wanted	0	O
little	0	O
to	0	O
do	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
parents	0	O
who	0	O
had	0	O
been	0	O
expelled	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
consciousness	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
lost	0	O
home	0	O
''	0	O
existed	0	O
;	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
sentimental	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
only	0	O
changed	0	O
again	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
eighties	0	O
,	0	O
when	0	O
a	0	O
renaissance	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
concept	0	O
of	0	O
home	0	O
in	0	O
Germany	1	S-LOC
allowed	0	O
a	0	O
stronger	0	O
reference	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
former	0	O
German	2	S-MISC
settlement	0	O
areas	0	O
again	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
describing	0	O
and	0	O
reproducing	0	O
the	0	O
stories	0	O
of	0	O
expellees	0	O
,	0	O
Lehmann	1	S-PER
never	0	O
tires	0	O
of	0	O
pointing	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
,	0	O
despite	0	O
long	0	O
held	0	O
prejudices	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
adhere	0	O
to	0	O
revanchism	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
can	0	O
believe	0	O
the	0	O
author	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
sees	0	O
his	0	O
book	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
contribution	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
understanding	0	O
of	0	O
different	0	O
nations	0	O
,	0	O
if	0	O
he	0	O
calls	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
sense	0	O
to	0	O
understand	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
homeland	0	O
only	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
home	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
in	0	O
spite	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
certainly	0	O
laudable	0	O
attitude	0	O
and	0	O
program	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
many	0	O
reports	0	O
and	0	O
narratives	0	O
leave	0	O
a	0	O
pale	0	O
aftertaste	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
is	0	O
primarily	0	O
attributable	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
methodology	0	O
of	0	O
German	0	O
folklore	0	O
.	0	O

History	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
written	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
book	0	O
is	0	O
presented	0	O
primarily	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
perspective	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
involved	0	O
in	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
story	0	O
is	0	O
broken	0	O
down	0	O
into	0	O
many	0	O
narratives	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
in	0	O
turn	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
scientifically	0	O
classified	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
different	0	O
genres	0	O
.	0	O

Success	0	O
stories	0	O
,	0	O
rascals	0	O
and	0	O
stories	0	O
of	0	O
trump	0	O
cards	0	O
are	0	O
typical	0	O
forms	0	O
of	0	O
telling	0	O
a	0	O
certain	0	O
group	0	O
who	0	O
still	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
people	0	O
forget	0	O
their	0	O
initial	0	O
difficulties	0	O
in	0	O
their	0	O
new	0	O
home	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
repressive	0	O
form	0	O
of	0	O
storytelling	0	O
,	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
found	0	O
among	0	O
women	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
victims	0	O
of	0	O
rape	0	O
.	0	O

Nevertheless	0	O
,	0	O
this	0	O
scientifically	0	O
derived	0	O
classification	0	O
of	0	O
narrative	0	O
types	0	O
remains	0	O
only	0	O
superficial	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
narratives	0	O
themselves	0	O
are	0	O
central	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
present	0	O
form	0	O
of	0	O
presentation	0	O
;	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
reflection	0	O
on	0	O
them	0	O
and	0	O
thus	0	O
no	0	O
opportunity	0	O
for	0	O
evaluation	0	O
and	0	O
classification	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
this	0	O
circumstance	0	O
leads	0	O
all	0	O
too	0	O
easily	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
sympathetic	0	O
comprehension	0	O
or	0	O
sympathetic	0	O
identification	0	O
with	0	O
those	0	O
affected	0	O
make	0	O
those	0	O
constellations	0	O
of	0	O
history	0	O
forgotten	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
context	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
unquestionably	0	O
cruel	0	O
individual	0	O
events	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
should	0	O
definitely	0	O
be	0	O
presented	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
example	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
seems	0	O
quite	0	O
irritating	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
double	0	O
luck	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Anton	1	B-PER
K.	1	E-PER
from	0	O
Transylvania	2	S-LOC
is	0	O
reported	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
as	0	O
ethnic	3	B-MISC
German	3	E-MISC
was	0	O
not	0	O
allowed	0	O
to	0	O
go	0	O
to	0	O
Wehrmacht	4	S-ORG
,	0	O
but	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
go	0	O
to	0	O
Waffen	5	B-ORG
SS	5	E-ORG
;	0	O
who	0	O
was	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
save	0	O
himself	0	O
over	0	O
the	0	O
war	0	O
years	0	O
and	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
time	0	O
was	0	O
spared	0	O
from	0	O
captivity	0	O
.	0	O

To	0	O
visualize	0	O
the	0	O
happiness	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
Anton	1	B-PER
K.	1	E-PER
is	0	O
one	0	O
side	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
other	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
to	0	O
classify	0	O
the	0	O
respective	0	O
individual	0	O
fates	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
history	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Second	1	B-MISC
World	1	I-MISC
War	1	E-MISC
and	0	O
the	0	O
years	0	O
thereafter	0	O
in	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
way	0	O
that	0	O
an	0	O
objectifying	0	O
perspective	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
adopted	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
mistake	0	O
to	0	O
assume	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
mere	0	O
reproduction	0	O
of	0	O
authentic	0	O
accounts	0	O
must	0	O
inevitably	0	O
lead	0	O
to	0	O
an	0	O
adequate	0	O
view	0	O
of	0	O
history	0	O
.	0	O

Rather	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
harbors	0	O
the	0	O
risk	0	O
of	0	O
looking	0	O
at	0	O
history	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
all	0	O
those	0	O
involved	0	O
stylize	0	O
as	0	O
their	0	O
victims	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
undoubtedly	0	O
necessary	0	O
to	0	O
also	0	O
deal	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
victims	0	O
of	0	O
history	0	O
who	0	O
were	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
perpetrator	0	O
's	0	O
side	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
should	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
be	0	O
avoided	0	O
as	0	O
much	0	O
as	0	O
possible	0	O
to	0	O
encourage	0	O
a	0	O
relativization	0	O
of	0	O
history	0	O
that	0	O
seeks	0	O
to	0	O
blur	0	O
all	0	O
differences	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
comprehensible	0	O
understanding	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
context	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
enough	0	O
to	0	O
issue	0	O
programmatic	0	O
slogans	0	O
for	0	O
''	0	O
Reconciliation	0	O
of	1	B-MISC
all	1	I-MISC
cultures	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
.	0	O

Rather	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
leads	0	O
to	0	O
other	0	O
fundamental	0	O
misunderstandings	0	O
which	0	O
help	0	O
to	0	O
blur	0	O
crucial	0	O
differences	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
blurring	0	O
is	0	O
most	0	O
evident	0	O
with	0	O
Lehmann	1	S-PER
at	0	O
the	0	O
point	0	O
where	0	O
he	0	O
advocates	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
post	0	O
national	0	O
Europe	2	S-LOC
''	0	O
and	0	O
declares	0	O
this	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
perspective	0	O
that	0	O
should	0	O
result	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
non	0	O
Protestant	0	O
emigrant	0	O
perspective	0	O
,	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
German	0	O
solution	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
emigrant	0	O
problem	0	O
becomes	0	O
a	0	O
model	0	O
for	0	O
those	0	O
questions	0	O
and	0	O
Problems	0	O
arising	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
wake	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
immigration	0	O
movements	0	O
will	0	O
:	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
subject	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
book	0	O
remains	0	O
topical	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
question	0	O
of	0	O
how	0	O
individuals	0	O
and	0	O
families	0	O
with	0	O
their	0	O
children	0	O
and	0	O
grandchildren	0	O
find	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
home	0	O
in	0	O
our	0	O
country	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
memories	0	O
they	0	O
carry	0	O
and	0	O
pass	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
homeland	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
culture	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
region	0	O
of	0	O
origin	0	O
,	0	O
how	0	O
they	0	O
maintain	0	O
contact	0	O
with	0	O
their	0	O
first	0	O
homeland.	0	O
''	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
equation	0	O
made	0	O
here	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
problems	0	O
of	0	O
resettlers	0	O
and	0	O
asylum	0	O
seekers	0	O
as	0	O
well	0	O
as	0	O
their	0	O
respective	0	O
experiences	0	O
of	0	O
foreignness	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
fundamental	0	O
difference	0	O
between	0	O
these	0	O
groups	0	O
is	0	O
swept	0	O
under	0	O
the	0	O
table	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
post	0	O
national	0	O
Europe	1	S-LOC
consists	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
coexistence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
varied	0	O
of	0	O
ethnic	0	O
groups	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
forcibly	0	O
or	0	O
willingly	0	O
ended	0	O
up	0	O
in	0	O
Germany	2	S-LOC
or	0	O
other	0	O
countries	0	O
Europe	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
experiences	0	O
of	0	O
strangeness	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
groups	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
are	0	O
likely	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
fundamentally	0	O
different	0	O
from	0	O
those	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
resettlers	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
1940s	0	O
or	0	O
those	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
children	0	O
decades	0	O
later	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
latter	0	O
have	0	O
proven	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
identified	0	O
with	0	O
Germany	1	S-LOC
despite	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
''	0	O
old	0	O
homeland	0	O
in	0	O
East	2	S-LOC
''	0	O
and	0	O
have	0	O
built	0	O
up	0	O
a	0	O
national	0	O
awareness	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
ethnicity	0	O
.	0	O

Such	0	O
an	0	O
identification	0	O
is	0	O
neither	0	O
possible	0	O
nor	0	O
desirable	0	O
for	0	O
immigrants	0	O
.	0	O

While	0	O
the	0	O
idea	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
homogeneous	0	O
nation	0	O
state	0	O
was	0	O
decisive	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
resettlers	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
idea	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
heterogeneous	0	O
nation	0	O
state	0	O
for	0	O
asylum	0	O
seekers	0	O
and	0	O
immigrants	0	O
today	0	O
.	0	O

Concentrating	0	O
on	0	O
subjective	0	O
sensitivities	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
undertaken	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
volume	0	O
,	0	O
should	0	O
not	0	O
lead	0	O
to	0	O
fundamental	0	O
,	0	O
objective	0	O
differences	0	O
being	0	O
neglected	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
conducive	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
scientific	0	O
context	0	O
,	0	O
nor	0	O
does	0	O
it	0	O
help	0	O
the	0	O
author	0	O
's	0	O
wish	0	O
to	0	O
''	0	O
build	0	O
''	0	O
a	0	O
Europe	1	S-LOC
in	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
differences	0	O
are	0	O
overcome	0	O
without	0	O
denying	0	O
them	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

OFTEN	0	O
IT	0	O
IS	0	O
the	0	O
little	0	O
problems	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
doorstep	0	O
that	0	O
cause	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
of	0	O
trouble	0	O
for	0	O
Frankfurt	1	S-MISC
citizens	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
DistrictRundschau	1	S-ORG
reader	0	O
's	0	O
hotline	0	O
has	0	O
always	0	O
been	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
help	0	O
find	0	O
ways	0	O
out	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
thicket	0	O
of	0	O
government	0	O
errors	0	O
and	0	O
to	0	O
find	0	O
solutions	0	O
to	0	O
some	0	O
problems	0	O
.	0	O

Even	0	O
if	0	O
rapid	0	O
success	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
always	0	O
achieved	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
face	0	O
of	0	O
typical	0	O
everyday	0	O
adversities	0	O
(	0	O
stubborn	0	O
long	0	O
term	0	O
parking	0	O
offenders	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
impressed	0	O
by	0	O
parking	0	O
tickets	0	O
or	0	O
newspaper	0	O
articles	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
direct	0	O
line	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
editorial	0	O
team	0	O
always	0	O
contributes	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
some	0	O
seemingly	0	O
insurmountable	0	O
rifts	0	O
are	0	O
found	0	O
Donkey	1	B-LOC
bridge	1	E-LOC
can	0	O
be	0	O
tensioned	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
District	1	B-ORG
Rundschau	1	E-ORG
reader	0	O
telephone	0	O
(	0	O
number	0	O
21	0	O
99	0	O
3	0	O
60	0	O
)	0	O
is	0	O
busy	0	O
:	0	O

every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
from	0	O
2	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
5	0	O
p.m.	0	O
,	0	O
Friday	0	O
from	0	O
10	0	O
a.m.	0	O
to	0	O
1	0	O
p.m	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

When	0	O
the	0	O
scales	1	S-ORG
indicated	0	O
112	0	O
kilos	0	O
Andrea	2	S-PER
,	0	O
27	0	O
years	0	O
old	0	O
:	0	O

Addicted	0	O
to	0	O
food	0	O
after	0	O
pregnancy	0	O

She	0	O
has	0	O
always	0	O
been	0	O
overweight	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
never	0	O
minded	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
she	0	O
's	0	O
been	0	O
married	0	O
to	0	O
for	0	O
ten	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
marriage	0	O
seemed	0	O
happy	0	O
,	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
was	0	O
happy	0	O
.	0	O

When	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
pregnant	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
second	0	O
time	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
age	0	O
of	0	O
24	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
delighted	0	O
.	0	O

She	0	O
always	0	O
wanted	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
of	0	O
children	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
birth	0	O
of	0	O
Mirjam	1	S-PER
,	0	O
she	0	O
felt	0	O
overwhelmed	0	O
.	0	O

Andrea	1	S-PER
started	0	O
to	0	O
eat	0	O
more	0	O
and	0	O
more	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
was	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
the	0	O
healthy	0	O
appetite	0	O
that	0	O
drew	0	O
her	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
refrigerator	0	O
:	0	O

Suddenly	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
stuffing	0	O
tons	0	O
of	0	O
food	0	O
into	0	O
herself	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
at	0	O
some	0	O
point	0	O
the	0	O
scales	0	O
show	0	O
112	0	O
kilos	0	O
.	0	O

Andrea	1	S-PER
had	0	O
become	0	O
addicted	0	O
,	0	O
addicted	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
feeling	0	O
of	0	O
fullness	0	O
.	0	O

Hunger	0	O
was	0	O
alien	0	O
to	0	O
her	0	O
,	0	O
her	0	O
whole	0	O
body	0	O
was	0	O
suddenly	0	O
alien	0	O
to	0	O
her	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
that	0	O
time	0	O
she	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
know	0	O
that	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
sick	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
was	0	O
n't	0	O
until	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
reading	0	O
a	0	O
diet	0	O
book	0	O
one	0	O
day	0	O
that	0	O
she	0	O
realized	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
woman	0	O
addicted	0	O
to	0	O
food	0	O
was	0	O
described	0	O
and	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
recognized	0	O
himself	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
story	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
that	0	O
moment	0	O
she	0	O
knew	0	O
that	0	O
she	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
do	0	O
something	0	O
about	0	O
her	0	O
suffering	0	O
.	0	O

So	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
took	0	O
the	0	O
initiative	0	O
and	0	O
registered	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
clinic	0	O
for	0	O
addicts	0	O
in	0	O
Allgäu	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

A	0	O
few	0	O
weeks	0	O
later	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
left	0	O
her	0	O
husband	0	O
and	0	O
children	0	O
for	0	O
three	0	O
months	0	O
of	0	O
therapy	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
relatives	0	O
accused	0	O
her	0	O
of	0	O
being	0	O
a	0	O
bad	0	O
mother	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
clear	0	O
:	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
good	0	O
mother	0	O
when	0	O
I	0	O
am	0	O
fine	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

When	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
introduced	0	O
herself	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
group	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
day	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
said	0	O
:	0	O

''	0	O
My	0	O
name	0	O
is	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
,	0	O
I	0	O
eat	0	O
too	0	O
much	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
I	0	O
have	0	O
no	0	O
other	0	O
problems	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

Everyone	0	O
laughed	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
soon	0	O
she	0	O
knew	0	O
why.	0	O
''	0	O

I	0	O
had	0	O
pushed	0	O
my	0	O
problems	0	O
aside	0	O
until	0	O
I	0	O
went	0	O
to	0	O
therapy.	0	O
''	0	O

It	0	O
turned	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
Andrea	1	S-PER
was	0	O
not	0	O
so	0	O
satisfied	0	O
with	0	O
her	0	O
existence	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
young	0	O
mother	0	O
and	0	O
wife	0	O
after	0	O
all	0	O
.	0	O

Today	0	O
she	0	O
admits	0	O
:	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
still	0	O
feel	0	O
like	0	O
I	0	O
missed	0	O
something	0	O
when	0	O
I	0	O
was	0	O
young	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
therapy	0	O
she	0	O
has	0	O
learned	0	O
to	0	O
deal	0	O
with	0	O
her	0	O
dissatisfaction	0	O
,	0	O
her	0	O
fears	0	O
and	0	O
worries	0	O
.	0	O

If	0	O
the	0	O
now	0	O
27	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
conflict	0	O
with	0	O
her	0	O
husband	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
of	0	O
them	0	O
talk	0	O
about	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
example	0	O
in	0	O
marriage	0	O
counseling	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
they	0	O
go	0	O
to	0	O
regularly	0	O
.	0	O

Andrea	2	S-PER
is	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
cured	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
disease	0	O
''	0	O
food	1	B-MISC
addiction	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

Once	0	O
you	0	O
're	0	O
addicted	0	O
,	0	O
somehow	0	O
you	0	O
'll	0	O
always	0	O
be	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
she	0	O
says	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
so	0	O
she	0	O
plans	0	O
exactly	0	O
what	0	O
she	0	O
will	0	O
eat	0	O
every	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

If	0	O
she	0	O
does	0	O
n't	0	O
do	0	O
it	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
gets	0	O
angry	0	O
.	0	O

Dealing	0	O
normally	0	O
with	0	O
food	0	O
will	0	O
remain	0	O
a	0	O
dream	0	O
for	0	O
her	0	O
too	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Stefan	1	B-PER
Müller	1	I-PER
Doohm	1	E-PER
Interdisciplinarity	0	O
from	0	O
below	0	O
Against	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
utopia	0	O
in	0	O
sociology	0	O
:	0	O

Incitement	0	O
to	0	O
strife	0	O
in	0	O
ivory	1	B-LOC
tower	1	E-LOC

It	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
without	0	O
reason	0	O
that	0	O
sociology	0	O
has	0	O
suspected	0	O
impostor	1	S-PER
.	0	O

Because	0	O
it	0	O
claims	0	O
nothing	0	O
less	0	O
than	0	O
the	0	O
whole	0	O
of	0	O
society	0	O
as	0	O
its	0	O
specific	0	O
subject	0	O
area	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
surprising	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
society	0	O
so	0	O
targeted	0	O
reacted	0	O
suspiciously	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
takeover	0	O
by	0	O
sociology	0	O
.	0	O

Until	0	O
the	0	O
Adenauerzeit	1	S-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
Lady	2	B-ORG
Society	2	E-ORG
,	0	O
eager	0	O
for	0	O
public	0	O
recognition	0	O
,	0	O
felt	0	O
extremely	0	O
embarrassed	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
rapprochement	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
increasingly	0	O
brazen	0	O
sociology	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
was	0	O
only	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
turbulent	0	O
political	0	O
times	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
late	0	O
1960s	0	O
that	0	O
she	0	O
gave	0	O
in	0	O
to	0	O
her	0	O
stormy	0	O
urges	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Society	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Sociology	1	E-ORG
blushed	0	O
and	0	O
fell	0	O
into	0	O
her	0	O
arms	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
yes	0	O
word	0	O
did	0	O
lead	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
bond	0	O
for	0	O
life	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
it	0	O
has	0	O
turned	0	O
out	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
anything	0	O
but	0	O
a	0	O
fervent	0	O
love	0	O
affair	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
meantime	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
enthusiasm	0	O
that	0	O
carried	0	O
the	0	O
expectations	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
young	0	O
social	0	O
science	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
height	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
academic	0	O
expansion	0	O
has	0	O
gone	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
conviction	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
associated	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
ambitious	0	O
goal	0	O
of	0	O
knowledge	0	O
of	0	O
formulating	0	O
a	0	O
theory	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
society	1	I-MISC
as	1	I-MISC
a	1	I-MISC
whole	1	E-MISC
that	0	O
was	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
both	0	O
critical	0	O
and	0	O
practical	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
time	0	O
disappeared	0	O
.	0	O

Are	0	O
we	0	O
therefore	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
process	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
course	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
utopian	0	O
energies	0	O
that	0	O
were	0	O
invested	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
mighty	0	O
undertaking	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
revolution	0	O
in	0	O
all	0	O
outdated	0	O
working	0	O
and	0	O
living	0	O
conditions	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
brought	0	O
about	0	O
through	0	O
enlightenment	0	O
and	0	O
criticism	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
completely	0	O
consumed	0	O
?	0	O

In	0	O
other	0	O
words	0	O
:	0	O

How	0	O
can	0	O
the	0	O
attractiveness	0	O
of	0	O
sociology	0	O
be	0	O
regained	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
reality	0	O
changing	0	O
force	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
lost	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
course	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
''	0	O
maturation	0	O
process	0	O
''	0	O
to	0	O
become	0	O
normal	0	O
science	0	O
?	0	O

There	0	O
are	0	O
three	0	O
main	0	O
reasons	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
utopia	0	O
in	0	O
sociology	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
utopia	0	O
itself	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
become	0	O
modest	0	O
out	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
historically	0	O
imposing	0	O
experience	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
failure	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
great	0	O
visionary	0	O
promises	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
evident	0	O
until	0	O
recently	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
reality	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
utopian	0	O
challenge	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
become	0	O
more	0	O
and	0	O
more	0	O
concrete	0	O
,	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
faced	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
simple	0	O
ruse	0	O
of	0	O
realizing	0	O
the	0	O
utopian	0	O
ideals	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
time	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
historical	0	O
situation	0	O
has	0	O
assumed	0	O
a	0	O
force	0	O
of	0	O
gravity	0	O
that	0	O
allows	0	O
any	0	O
projection	0	O
of	0	O
longing	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
completely	0	O
different	0	O
person	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
coming	0	O
morning	0	O
only	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
apocalypse	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
ideal	0	O
images	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
origin	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
modernity	1	S-MISC
were	0	O
transformed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
critical	0	O
tradition	0	O
of	0	O
social	0	O
theory	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
concrete	0	O
utopia	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
real	0	O
history	0	O
of	0	O
advancing	0	O
bourgeois	0	O
emancipation	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
ladder	0	O
goes	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
fictional	0	O
future	0	O
paintings	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
More	1	S-PER
,	0	O
Campanella	2	S-PER
and	0	O
Bacon	3	S-PER
to	0	O
the	0	O
technical	0	O
and	0	O
early	0	O
socialist	0	O
utopianism	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
Owen	4	S-PER
,	0	O
Saint	5	B-PER
Simon	5	E-PER
,	0	O
Fourier	6	S-PER
and	0	O
Proudhon	7	S-PER
.	0	O

Marx	1	S-PER
polemicized	0	O
against	0	O
these	0	O
utopian	0	O
socialists	0	O
with	0	O
all	0	O
sharpness	0	O
,	0	O
accusing	0	O
them	0	O
of	0	O
being	0	O
mere	0	O
dreamers	0	O
.	0	O

Like	0	O
so	0	O
many	0	O
other	0	O
things	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
himself	0	O
turns	0	O
utopia	0	O
upside	0	O
down	0	O
and	0	O
comes	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
point	0	O
materialistically	0	O
:	0	O

In	0	O
communism	0	O
,	0	O
utopia	0	O
and	0	O
reality	0	O
merge	0	O
,	0	O
namely	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
society	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
free	1	I-ORG
producers	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
as	0	O
material	0	O
abundance	0	O
and	0	O
as	0	O
social	0	O
relations	0	O
that	0	O
are	0	O
transparent	0	O
for	0	O
all	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
society	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
this	0	O
concretization	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
utopia	0	O
has	0	O
in	0	O
no	0	O
way	0	O
led	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
paradise	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
promised	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
we	0	O
read	0	O
in	0	O
Horkheimer	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
diary	0	O
note	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
fifties	0	O
,	0	O
heaven	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
to	0	O
which	0	O
one	0	O
can	0	O
point	0	O
the	0	O
way	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
one	0	O
.	0	O

Even	0	O
more	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
productive	0	O
forces	0	O
turned	0	O
out	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
destructive	0	O
forces	0	O
,	0	O
class	0	O
consciousness	0	O
became	0	O
a	0	O
fossil	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
individualization	0	O
of	0	O
life	0	O
situations	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
revolutions	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
prove	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
locomotive	0	O
of	0	O
world	0	O
history	0	O
.	0	O

Rather	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
words	0	O
of	0	O
Walter	1	B-PER
Benjamin	1	E-PER
,	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
the	0	O
reach	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
human	0	O
race	0	O
traveling	0	O
on	0	O
this	0	O
train	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
emergency	0	O
brake	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
shock	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
''	0	O
normal	0	O
catastrophes	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
reactor	0	O
accidents	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
endanger	0	O
the	0	O
survival	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
species	0	O
,	0	O
has	0	O
torn	0	O
social	0	O
science	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
twilight	0	O
sleep	0	O
of	0	O
belief	0	O
in	0	O
progress	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
awakening	0	O
finds	0	O
its	0	O
current	0	O
expression	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
circulating	0	O
term	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
risk	0	O
society	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
whose	0	O
secret	0	O
message	0	O
of	0	O
salvation	0	O
is	0	O
to	0	O
still	0	O
make	0	O
the	0	O
course	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
controllable	0	O
in	0	O
accordance	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
self	0	O
enlightened	0	O
explanation	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
hope	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
reflexive	0	O
modernization	0	O
''	0	O
cherished	0	O
by	0	O
Ulrich	1	B-PER
Beck	1	E-PER
is	0	O
by	0	O
no	0	O
means	0	O
new	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
order	0	O
to	0	O
avoid	0	O
the	0	O
foreseeable	0	O
catastrophe	0	O
,	0	O
so	0	O
have	0	O
already	0	O
argued	0	O
leading	0	O
sociologists	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Weimar	1	B-MISC
epoch	1	E-MISC
like	0	O
Max	2	B-PER
Weber	2	E-PER
and	0	O
Karl	3	B-PER
Mannheim	3	E-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
real	4	S-MISC
should	0	O
be	0	O
approximated	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
concretized	0	O
utopian	5	S-MISC
.	0	O

And	0	O
in	0	O
fact	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
rule	0	O
of	0	O
law	0	O
,	0	O
democratic	0	O
self	0	O
determination	0	O
and	0	O
material	0	O
welfare	0	O
security	0	O
are	0	O
nothing	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
a	0	O
disenchanted	0	O
form	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
realization	0	O
of	0	O
that	0	O
utopia	0	O
that	0	O
has	0	O
long	0	O
since	0	O
been	0	O
brought	0	O
from	0	O
heaven	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
earth	1	S-LOC
:	0	O

Everyone	0	O
produces	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
abilities	0	O
,	0	O
everyone	0	O
consumes	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
needs	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
secularized	0	O
ideal	0	O
of	0	O
everyone	0	O
's	0	O
right	0	O
to	0	O
everything	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
currently	0	O
sees	0	O
itself	0	O
as	0	O
utopian	0	O
overtaken	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
ecologically	0	O
inspired	0	O
''	0	O
utopia	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
the	1	I-MISC
zero	1	I-MISC
option	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
more	0	O
precisely	0	O
:	0	O

put	0	O
in	0	O
place	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
kind	0	O
of	0	O
general	0	O
no	0	O
overtaking	0	O
rule	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
formula	0	O
,	0	O
with	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
scientist	0	O
Claus	1	B-PER
Offe	1	E-PER
started	0	O
to	0	O
step	0	O
out	0	O
of	0	O
such	0	O
almost	0	O
objective	0	O
processes	0	O
as	0	O
automobilization	0	O
,	0	O
agricultural	0	O
chemistry	0	O
,	0	O
cabling	0	O
,	0	O
etc	0	O
.	0	O

wants	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
palatable	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
little	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
a	0	O
residual	0	O
hope	0	O
of	0	O
avoiding	0	O
the	0	O
inexorable	0	O
disaster	0	O
resulting	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
generalization	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
principle	0	O
''	0	O
free	0	O
travel	0	O
for	0	O
free	0	O
citizens	0	O
''	0	O
by	0	O
pausing	0	O
and	0	O
standing	0	O
still	0	O
.	0	O

Does	0	O
n't	0	O
this	0	O
utopia	0	O
of	0	O
voluntary	0	O
standing	0	O
in	0	O
line	0	O
run	0	O
the	0	O
risk	0	O
of	0	O
succumbing	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
spell	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
omnipotence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
present	0	O
?	0	O

Because	0	O
the	0	O
critical	0	O
power	0	O
of	0	O
utopian	0	O
thought	0	O
in	0	O
Enlightenment	0	O
science	0	O
slackens	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
dimension	0	O
of	0	O
historical	0	O
meaning	0	O
formation	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
horizon	0	O
of	0	O
historical	0	O
target	0	O
perspectives	0	O
disappears	0	O
in	0	O
social	0	O
self	0	O
thematization	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
vacuum	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
a	0	O
breeding	0	O
ground	0	O
for	0	O
ideologies	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
posthistoire	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
this	0	O
lack	0	O
of	0	O
utopia	0	O
also	0	O
promotes	0	O
the	0	O
fixation	0	O
on	0	O
substitute	0	O
programs	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
fundamentalism	0	O
,	0	O
regionalism	0	O
and	0	O
feminism	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
memory	0	O
of	0	O
what	0	O
is	0	O
uncompleted	0	O
in	0	O
utopian	0	O
thinking	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
utopian	0	O
forward	0	O
thinking	0	O
that	0	O
strikes	0	O
the	0	O
spark	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
ignite	0	O
the	0	O
light	0	O
that	0	O
accompanies	0	O
the	0	O
idea	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
better	0	O
society	0	O
is	0	O
dispensed	0	O
with	0	O
.	0	O

When	0	O
it	0	O
comes	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
risks	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
risk	0	O
society	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
disciplinary	0	O
organized	0	O
scientific	0	O
enterprise	0	O
is	0	O
objectively	0	O
overwhelmed	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
the	0	O
growing	0	O
destructive	0	O
potentials	0	O
in	0	O
nature	0	O
and	0	O
society	0	O
generated	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
individual	0	O
sciences	0	O
themselves	0	O
are	0	O
due	0	O
not	0	O
least	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
subjects	0	O
only	0	O
look	0	O
at	0	O
their	0	O
navel	0	O
and	0	O
remain	0	O
in	0	O
their	0	O
ivory	0	O
towers	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
mandatory	0	O
multidisciplinary	0	O
cooperation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
natural	0	O
,	0	O
spiritual	0	O
and	0	O
social	0	O
sciences	0	O
,	0	O
science	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
special	0	O
responsibility	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
object	0	O
related	0	O
relationship	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
totality	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
.	0	O

First	0	O
of	0	O
all	0	O
,	0	O
sociology	0	O
has	0	O
the	0	O
self	0	O
critical	0	O
task	0	O
of	0	O
sweeping	0	O
in	0	O
front	0	O
of	0	O
one	0	O
's	0	O
own	0	O
house	0	O
and	0	O
through	0	O
this	0	O
exemplary	0	O
nature	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
contagious	0	O
.	0	O

Only	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
house	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
open	0	O
door	0	O
''	0	O
with	0	O
internal	0	O
plurality	0	O
does	0	O
it	0	O
enable	0	O
a	0	O
process	0	O
of	0	O
combining	0	O
diverse	0	O
methods	0	O
and	0	O
theories	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
cognitive	0	O
identity	0	O
of	0	O
sociology	0	O
is	0	O
in	0	O
no	0	O
way	0	O
endangered	0	O
by	0	O
this	0	O
openness	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
the	0	O
subject	0	O
has	0	O
organizationally	0	O
stabilized	0	O
and	0	O
its	0	O
academic	0	O
reputation	0	O
seems	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
secured	0	O
.	0	O

Its	0	O
status	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
science	0	O
of	0	O
interpretation	0	O
necessitates	0	O
extreme	0	O
tolerance	0	O
towards	0	O
the	0	O
competing	0	O
paradigms	0	O
,	0	O
various	0	O
methodological	0	O
approaches	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
divergent	0	O
interpretation	0	O
of	0	O
social	0	O
issues	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
social	0	O
analyzes	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
operate	0	O
with	0	O
an	0	O
objective	0	O
claim	0	O
to	0	O
knowledge	0	O
.	0	O

Rather	0	O
,	0	O
social	0	O
theory	0	O
convinces	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
formation	0	O
of	0	O
arguments	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
,	0	O
through	0	O
empirical	0	O
validity	0	O
and	0	O
interpretative	0	O
plausibility	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
this	0	O
reason	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
of	0	O
sociology	0	O
lies	0	O
in	0	O
creating	0	O
a	0	O
unity	0	O
of	0	O
originally	0	O
diverging	0	O
traditions	0	O
:	0	O

the	0	O
empirical	0	O
method	0	O
of	0	O
knowledge	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
hand	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
hermeneutics	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
humanities	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
principle	0	O
of	0	O
tolerance	0	O
in	0	O
one	0	O
's	0	O
own	0	O
house	0	O
also	0	O
implies	0	O
a	0	O
direct	0	O
connection	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
houses	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
street	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
strict	0	O
cooperation	0	O
of	0	O
sociology	0	O
with	0	O
other	0	O
social	0	O
sciences	0	O
if	0	O
it	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
divulge	0	O
its	0	O
great	0	O
goal	0	O
of	0	O
knowledge	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
Horkheimer	1	S-PER
,	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
theory	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
historical	0	O
To	0	O
formulate	0	O
the	0	O
course	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
epoch	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
gigantic	0	O
research	0	O
program	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
be	0	O
realized	0	O
if	0	O
sociology	0	O
advances	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
medium	0	O
of	0	O
communication	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
subjects	0	O
of	0	O
history	0	O
,	0	O
economics	0	O
,	0	O
anthropology	0	O
,	0	O
ethnology	0	O
and	0	O
psychology	0	O
,	0	O
among	0	O
others	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
engage	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
philosophical	0	O
fundamental	0	O
reflection	0	O
,	0	O
are	0	O
ready	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
continuous	0	O
exchange	0	O
of	0	O
individual	0	O
scientific	0	O
advances	0	O
in	0	O
knowledge	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
empirical	0	O
Systematically	0	O
link	0	O
research	0	O
efforts	0	O
with	0	O
theory	0	O
building	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
orientation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
sciences	0	O
towards	0	O
a	0	O
historically	0	O
and	0	O
empirically	0	O
substantial	0	O
theory	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
the	1	I-MISC
social	1	E-MISC
to	0	O
be	0	O
developed	0	O
through	0	O
research	0	O
cooperation	0	O
is	0	O
only	0	O
a	0	O
first	0	O
step	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
second	0	O
must	0	O
follow	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
the	0	O
subject	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
research	0	O
efforts	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
slips	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
fingers	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
ever	0	O
more	0	O
specialized	0	O
social	0	O
sciences	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
meaning	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
teaching	0	O
and	0	O
research	0	O
is	0	O
limited	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
tinkering	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
shoemaker	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
stays	0	O
with	0	O
his	0	O
last	0	O
,	0	O
no	0	O
matter	0	O
how	0	O
his	0	O
neck	0	O
is	0	O
up	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
contrast	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
perspective	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
humanities	0	O
and	0	O
social	0	O
sciences	0	O
lies	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
emerging	0	O
coalition	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
human	1	I-MISC
sciences	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
American	0	O
historian	0	O
Robert	1	B-PER
Darnton	1	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
subject	0	O
configuration	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
consequently	0	O
includes	0	O
the	0	O
dissolution	0	O
of	0	O
traditional	0	O
faculties	0	O
and	0	O
departments	0	O
,	0	O
leads	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
surge	0	O
in	0	O
innovation	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
one	0	O
dimensionality	0	O
of	0	O
cause	0	O
and	0	O
event	0	O
research	0	O
is	0	O
overcome	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
realistic	0	O
scientific	0	O
understanding	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
symbolic	0	O
cultural	0	O
system	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
common	0	O
reference	0	O
point	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
human	0	O
sciences	0	O
.	0	O

Let	0	O
's	0	O
summarize	0	O
:	0	O

First	0	O
,	0	O
sociology	0	O
must	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
recognize	0	O
the	0	O
status	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
empirical	0	O
,	0	O
understanding	0	O
and	0	O
critical	0	O
social	0	O
science	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
use	0	O
its	0	O
character	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
multi	0	O
paradigm	0	O
science	0	O
productively	0	O
for	0	O
itself	0	O
.	0	O

Second	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
project	0	O
requires	0	O
a	0	O
restructured	0	O
social	0	O
theory	0	O
of	0	O
interdisciplinary	0	O
collaboration	0	O
among	0	O
the	0	O
various	0	O
social	0	O
science	0	O
subjects	0	O
.	0	O

Thirdly	0	O
,	0	O
thirdly	0	O
,	0	O
because	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
perspective	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
whole	0	O
of	0	O
human	0	O
life	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
science	0	O
of	0	O
society	0	O
is	0	O
best	0	O
suited	0	O
to	0	O
asserting	0	O
an	0	O
overall	0	O
interest	0	O
of	0	O
mankind	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
dangerous	0	O
goings	0	O
on	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
magical	0	O
apprentices	0	O
of	0	O
technical	0	O
scientific	0	O
civilization	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
independent	0	O
individual	0	O
sciences	0	O
with	0	O
their	0	O
particularistic	0	O
rationalities	0	O
bring	0	O
to	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
present	0	O
task	0	O
of	0	O
sociology	0	O
is	0	O
to	0	O
bring	0	O
the	0	O
sciences	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
differentiation	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
is	0	O
irreversible	0	O
,	0	O
down	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
common	0	O
denominator	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
multidisciplinary	0	O
discourse	0	O
that	0	O
endeavors	0	O
to	0	O
solve	0	O
a	0	O
question	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
binding	0	O
for	0	O
everyone	0	O
through	0	O
its	0	O
interpretative	0	O
translation	0	O
and	0	O
mediation	0	O
services	0	O
:	0	O

how	0	O
to	0	O
prevent	0	O
the	0	O
disaster	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
processing	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
existential	0	O
question	0	O
will	0	O
certainly	0	O
not	0	O
succeed	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
stroke	0	O
of	0	O
genius	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
researcher	0	O
or	0	O
a	0	O
subject	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
is	0	O
only	0	O
conceivable	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
joint	0	O
effort	0	O
of	0	O
all	0	O
sciences	0	O
.	0	O

Seen	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
way	0	O
,	0	O
enlightenment	0	O
science	0	O
is	0	O
definitely	0	O
the	0	O
protagonist	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
utopian	0	O
program	0	O
:	0	O

that	0	O
of	0	O
overcoming	0	O
disciplinary	0	O
boundaries	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
indifferent	0	O
coexistence	0	O
of	0	O
university	0	O
sciences	0	O
is	0	O
scientifically	0	O
irresponsible	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
face	0	O
of	0	O
world	0	O
dangers	0	O
and	0	O
their	0	O
complex	0	O
interdependencies	0	O
and	0	O
just	0	O
as	0	O
out	0	O
of	0	O
date	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
idea	0	O
of	0	O
standardized	0	O
science	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
melody	0	O
''	0	O
If	0	O
everyone	0	O
does	0	O
their	0	O
own	0	O
thing	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
will	0	O
all	0	O
work	0	O
out	0	O
''	0	O
is	0	O
an	0	O
extremely	0	O
dangerous	0	O
slumber	0	O
song	0	O
.	0	O

An	0	O
''	0	O
interdisciplinarity	0	O
from	0	O
below	0	O
''	0	O
awakens	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
sleep	0	O
of	0	O
reason	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
Jürgen	1	B-PER
Mittelstraß	1	E-PER
describes	0	O
as	0	O
lateral	0	O
thinking	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
questions	0	O
where	0	O
no	0	O
one	0	O
has	0	O
asked	0	O
yet	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
learning	0	O
what	0	O
one	0	O
's	0	O
own	0	O
discipline	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
know	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

''	0	O
Often	0	O
a	0	O
dominant	0	O
mother	0	O
''	0	O
FR	0	O
conversation	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
psychotherapist	0	O
Arthur	1	B-PER
Cooper	1	E-PER

WETTERAUKREIS	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

Eating	0	O
disorders	0	O
are	0	O
often	0	O
still	0	O
a	0	O
mystery	0	O
to	0	O
therapists	0	O
.	0	O

Your	0	O
patients	0	O
have	0	O
an	0	O
addiction	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
solely	0	O
psychological	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
healing	0	O
method	0	O
that	0	O
would	0	O
rule	0	O
out	0	O
a	0	O
relapse	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
more	0	O
frightening	0	O
that	0	O
more	0	O
and	0	O
more	0	O
people	0	O
,	0	O
especially	0	O
women	0	O
,	0	O
are	0	O
suffering	0	O
from	0	O
bulimia	0	O
,	0	O
anorexia	0	O
or	0	O
overeating	0	O
.	0	O

FR	1	B-ORG
employee	1	E-ORG
Daniela	2	B-PER
Saur	2	E-PER
spoke	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
psychotherapist	0	O
Arthur	3	B-PER
Cooper	3	E-PER
about	0	O
the	0	O
diseases	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
considers	0	O
eating	0	O
disorders	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
most	0	O
exciting	0	O
''	0	O
topics	0	O
in	0	O
psychotherapy	0	O
.	0	O

FR	1	S-LOC
:	0	O

Mr	0	O
Cooper	1	S-PER
,	0	O
you	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
you	0	O
particularly	0	O
enjoy	0	O
working	0	O
with	0	O
people	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
abnormal	0	O
eating	0	O
habits	0	O
.	0	O

Why	0	O
?	0	O

Cooper	1	S-PER
:	0	O

The	0	O
increase	0	O
in	0	O
addictions	0	O
,	0	O
especially	0	O
bulimia	0	O
,	0	O
anorexia	0	O
and	0	O
food	0	O
addiction	0	O
,	0	O
reflect	0	O
our	0	O
broken	0	O
society	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
shows	0	O
that	0	O
we	0	O
are	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
healthily	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Where	0	O
helpless	0	O
people	0	O
can	0	O
find	0	O
help	0	O

Many	0	O
people	0	O
with	0	O
eating	0	O
disorders	0	O
feel	0	O
alone	0	O
with	0	O
their	0	O
suffering	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
that	0	O
way	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
are	0	O
also	0	O
contact	0	O
points	0	O
in	0	O
Wetteraukreis	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
the	0	O
surrounding	0	O
area	0	O
:	0	O

Niddatal	1	S-LOC
:	0	O

Self	0	O
help	0	O
group	0	O
for	0	O
coping	0	O
with	0	O
eating	0	O
disorders	0	O
,	0	O
meeting	0	O
every	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
from	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
rooms	0	O
of	0	O
active	1	B-ORG
citizens	1	E-ORG
in	0	O
Kaichen	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Nidda	1	S-LOC
:	0	O

Self	1	B-ORG
help	1	I-ORG
group	1	I-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
the	1	I-ORG
women	1	I-ORG
's	1	I-ORG
emergency	1	I-ORG
number	1	I-ORG
in	1	E-ORG
Borsdorf	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
meeting	0	O
every	0	O
Friday	0	O
from	0	O
7.30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
Weiherstraße	3	S-LOC
12	0	O
(	0	O
Tel	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

0	0	O
60	0	O
43/44	0	O
71	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Karben	1	S-LOC
:	0	O

Discussion	0	O
group	0	O
for	0	O
addicts	0	O
,	0	O
meeting	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
from	0	O
5	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
7	0	O
p.m.	0	O
and	0	O
from	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
10.30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Catholic	0	O
community	0	O
center	0	O
St.	1	B-LOC
Boniface	1	E-LOC
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Social	0	O
market	0	O
economy	0	O

In	0	O
view	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
ever	0	O
increasing	0	O
mountains	0	O
of	0	O
debt	0	O
,	0	O
Federal	0	O
Chancellor	0	O
Kohl	1	S-PER
appeals	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
public	0	O
that	0	O
still	0	O
remembers	0	O
that	0	O
after	0	O
reunification	0	O
nobody	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
worse	0	O
off	0	O
than	0	O
before	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
slogan	0	O
''	0	O
keep	0	O
moderation	0	O
!	0	O
''	0	O

had	0	O
already	0	O
issued	0	O
Ludwig	1	B-PER
Erhard	1	E-PER
decades	0	O
before	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
then	0	O
cost	0	O
the	0	O
Chancellor	2	B-LOC
's	2	I-LOC
Office	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
not	0	O
least	0	O
because	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
severe	0	O
economic	0	O
downturn	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
previously	0	O
prosperous	0	O
economy	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
basics	0	O
of	0	O
Erhard	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
''	0	O
Social	2	B-MISC
Market	2	I-MISC
Economy	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
along	0	O
with	0	O
other	0	O
economists	0	O
at	0	O
''	0	O
Freiburg	3	B-ORG
School	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
were	0	O
primarily	0	O
developed	0	O
by	0	O
Walter	4	B-PER
Eucken	4	E-PER
.	0	O

The	0	O
new	0	O
order	0	O
model	0	O
was	0	O
mainly	0	O
developed	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
basis	0	O
of	0	O
analyzes	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
central	0	O
administration	0	O
economy	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Eucken	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
investigation	0	O
shows	0	O
that	0	O
planned	0	O
and	0	O
market	0	O
economies	0	O
are	0	O
complex	0	O
systems	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
different	0	O
functional	0	O
mechanisms	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
exchanged	0	O
with	0	O
one	0	O
another	0	O
at	0	O
will	0	O
.	0	O

Proof	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
the	0	O
failure	0	O
of	0	O
all	0	O
previous	0	O
attempts	0	O
at	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
Third	1	B-MISC
Way	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
the	0	O
transformation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
GDR	2	B-MISC
economy	2	E-MISC
that	0	O
has	0	O
begun	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
private	0	O
''	0	O
black	0	O
markets	0	O
''	0	O
that	0	O
also	0	O
exist	0	O
in	0	O
planned	0	O
economies	0	O
complement	0	O
the	0	O
central	0	O
allocation	0	O
system	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
planned	0	O
bureaucracies	0	O
.	0	O

Under	0	O
the	0	O
conditions	0	O
of	0	O
free	0	O
exchange	0	O
relationships	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
superfluous	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
since	0	O
they	0	O
arise	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
certain	0	O
special	0	O
situation	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
transferred	0	O
seamlessly	0	O
into	0	O
''	0	O
normal	0	O
''	0	O
markets	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
same	0	O
applies	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
exchange	0	O
of	0	O
goods	0	O
with	0	O
other	0	O
state	0	O
trading	0	O
countries	0	O
.	0	O

As	0	O
soon	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
free	0	O
movement	0	O
of	0	O
goods	0	O
is	0	O
possible	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
previously	0	O
prescribed	0	O
trade	0	O
relations	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
replaced	0	O
by	0	O
those	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
rational	0	O
choice	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
establishment	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
organizational	0	O
model	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Freiburg	1	S-ORG
school	0	O
''	0	O
is	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
is	0	O
also	0	O
clear	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Eucken	2	B-PER
's	2	E-PER
principles	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
fact	0	O
dependent	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
social	0	O
''	0	O
state	0	O
of	0	O
nature	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Even	0	O
the	0	O
demand	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
necessary	0	O
dissolution	0	O
of	0	O
power	0	O
groups	0	O
is	0	O
practically	0	O
impracticable	0	O
in	0	O
today	0	O
's	0	O
Federal	1	B-LOC
Republic	1	E-LOC
;	0	O
at	0	O
least	0	O
as	0	O
long	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
rightly	0	O
assumed	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
accusation	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
group	0	O
anarchy	0	O
''	0	O
is	0	O
directed	0	O
first	0	O
at	0	O
workers	0	O
and	0	O
trade	0	O
unions	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
many	0	O
cases	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
still	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
fight	0	O
their	0	O
way	0	O
to	0	O
adjust	0	O
their	0	O
income	0	O
in	0	O
response	0	O
to	0	O
increased	0	O
costs	0	O
,	0	O
even	0	O
though	0	O
the	0	O
wage	0	O
cost	0	O
share	0	O
in	0	O
value	0	O
creation	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
only	0	O
an	0	O
average	0	O
of	0	O
20	0	O
%	0	O
.	0	O

Yet	0	O
:	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
a	0	O
matter	0	O
of	0	O
indifference	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
complexity	0	O
of	0	O
modern	0	O
societies	0	O
seems	0	O
to	0	O
overwhelm	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
social	1	B-MISC
market	1	I-MISC
economy	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
model	0	O
.	0	O

Its	0	O
purpose	0	O
was	0	O
precisely	0	O
to	0	O
reduce	0	O
complexity	0	O
through	0	O
frameworks	0	O
for	0	O
private	0	O
self	0	O
control	0	O
we	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
have	0	O
other	0	O
models	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

In	0	O
reality	0	O
,	0	O
Empress	0	O
Agnes	1	S-PER
wore	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Gisela	2	B-MISC
jewelry	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
The	0	O
long	0	O
standing	0	O
mystery	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
jewels	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
Salier	3	B-MISC
Empress	3	E-MISC
now	0	O
solved	0	O
/	0	O
A	0	O
dramatic	0	O
find	0	O
at	0	O
Mainz	4	B-LOC
Jewish	4	I-LOC
Ghetto	4	E-LOC

Few	0	O
archaeological	0	O
finds	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Middle	0	O
Ages	0	O
have	0	O
achieved	0	O
such	0	O
great	0	O
popularity	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
Adler	1	B-MISC
Pfauen	1	I-MISC
Fibel	1	E-MISC
from	0	O
a	0	O
treasure	0	O
trove	0	O
of	0	O
25	0	O
pieces	0	O
of	0	O
gold	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
was	0	O
found	0	O
by	0	O
chance	0	O
in	0	O
1880	0	O
during	0	O
sewer	0	O
work	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
basement	0	O
niche	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
burned	0	O
down	0	O
house	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
former	0	O
''	0	O
Judengasse	2	S-LOC
''	0	O
in	0	O
Mainz	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
only	0	O
after	0	O
adventurous	0	O
detours	0	O
now	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
shown	0	O
in	0	O
museum	0	O
showcases	0	O
.	0	O

To	0	O
this	0	O
day	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
considered	0	O
the	0	O
largest	0	O
and	0	O
most	0	O
important	0	O
find	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
kind	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
four	0	O
half	0	O
moon	0	O
earrings	0	O
,	0	O
nine	0	O
finger	0	O
rings	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
chest	0	O
hanging	0	O
(	0	O
Loros	1	S-MISC
)	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
jeweled	0	O
collar	0	O
(	0	O
Maniakion	2	S-MISC
)	0	O
both	0	O
replicas	0	O
of	0	O
Byzantine	0	O
emperor	0	O
's	0	O
insignia	0	O
among	0	O
eight	0	O
humpback	0	O
,	0	O
conical	0	O
and	0	O
disc	0	O
brooches	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
exceptionally	0	O
valuable	0	O
one	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
Eagle	3	B-MISC
peacock	3	I-MISC
motif	3	E-MISC
,	0	O
like	0	O
her	0	O
,	0	O
caught	0	O
the	0	O
eye	0	O
only	0	O
an	0	O
empress	0	O
could	0	O
have	0	O
adorned	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
historian	0	O
Otto	1	B-PER
von	1	I-PER
Falke	1	E-PER
came	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
view	0	O
in	0	O
1913	0	O
in	0	O
his	0	O
book	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
publication	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
inventory	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
assigned	0	O
them	0	O
as	0	O
emblem	0	O
of	0	O
empress	0	O
Gisela	1	S-PER
,	0	O
consort	0	O
Conrad	2	B-PER
II	2	E-PER
,	0	O
German	3	S-MISC
king	0	O
(	0	O
1024	0	O
1039	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
emperor	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
1027	0	O
)	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
family	0	O
of	0	O
Salier	4	S-PER
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
known	0	O
and	0	O
famous	0	O
under	0	O
the	0	O
name	0	O
''	0	O
Gisela	1	B-MISC
Fibel	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
.	0	O

Although	0	O
this	0	O
dating	0	O
was	0	O
lively	0	O
discussed	0	O
at	0	O
that	0	O
time	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
never	0	O
refuted	0	O
until	0	O
the	0	O
senior	0	O
curator	0	O
at	0	O
Roman	1	B-LOC
Germanic	1	I-LOC
Central	1	I-LOC
Museum	1	E-LOC
in	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Dr.	0	O
Mechthild	3	B-PER
SchulzI	3	I-PER
Dörrlamm	3	E-PER
,	0	O
inspired	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
years	0	O
of	0	O
preparations	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Salier	4	B-MISC
exhibition	4	E-MISC
in	0	O
Speyer	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
now	0	O
introduces	0	O
an	0	O
Empress	0	O
who	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
generation	0	O
younger	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
owner	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
special	0	O
piece	0	O
of	0	O
jewelry	0	O
:	0	O

Agnes	1	B-PER
von	1	I-PER
Poitou	1	E-PER
,	0	O
married	0	O
in	0	O
1043	0	O
to	0	O
Emperor	0	O
Heinrich	2	B-PER
III	2	I-PER
.	2	E-PER
in	0	O
Ingelheim	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
crowned	0	O
Empress	0	O
in	0	O
Mainz	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
secret	0	O
capital	0	O
of	0	O
empire	5	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
now	0	O
researched	0	O
affiliation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
is	0	O
based	0	O
on	0	O
new	0	O
,	0	O
well	0	O
datable	0	O
archaeological	0	O
finds	0	O
and	0	O
comparative	0	O
studies	0	O
with	0	O
Byzantine	0	O
and	0	O
Fatimid	0	O
jewelry	0	O
and	0	O
decorative	0	O
elements	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
in	0	O
question	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
Mechthild	1	B-PER
SchulzI	1	I-PER
Dörrlamm	1	E-PER
in	0	O
her	0	O
book	0	O
''	0	O
The	0	O
Mainzer	2	S-LOC
Treasure	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Empress	0	O
Agnes	3	S-PER
from	0	O
the	0	O
middle	0	O
11th	0	O
century	0	O
New	0	O
Investigations	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
so	0	O
called	0	O
''	0	O
Gisela	4	B-MISC
Schmuck	4	E-MISC
'	0	O
''	0	O
(	0	O
Jan	5	B-ORG
ThorbeckI	5	I-ORG
Verlag	5	E-ORG
,	0	O
Sigmaringen	6	S-LOC
1991	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
round	0	O
,	0	O
gold	0	O
enamelled	0	O
AdlerPfauen	1	B-MISC
Fibel	1	E-MISC
is	0	O
the	0	O
only	0	O
piece	0	O
that	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
acquired	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
Antiquities	0	O
Museum	0	O
shortly	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
was	0	O
discovered	0	O
in	0	O
1880	0	O
and	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
kept	0	O
there	0	O
ever	0	O
since	0	O
.	0	O

All	0	O
other	0	O
pieces	0	O
of	0	O
jewelry	0	O
are	0	O
now	0	O
in	0	O
Kunstgewerbemuseum	1	B-LOC
Berlin	1	E-LOC
after	0	O
many	0	O
turbulent	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
construction	0	O
workers	0	O
initially	0	O
kept	0	O
their	0	O
find	0	O
a	0	O
secret	0	O
in	0	O
1880	0	O
,	0	O
then	0	O
divided	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
among	0	O
themselves	0	O
and	0	O
sold	0	O
it	0	O
piece	0	O
by	0	O
piece	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
next	0	O
decades	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
pieces	0	O
of	0	O
jewelry	0	O
appeared	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
wide	0	O
variety	0	O
of	0	O
places	0	O
and	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
wide	0	O
variety	0	O
of	0	O
owners	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
meantime	0	O
,	0	O
some	0	O
parts	0	O
were	0	O
considered	0	O
completely	0	O
lost	0	O
,	0	O
other	0	O
parts	0	O
were	0	O
badly	0	O
damaged	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Second	1	B-MISC
World	1	I-MISC
War	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

The	0	O
Adler	1	B-MISC
Pfauen	1	I-MISC
Fibel	1	E-MISC
is	0	O
the	0	O
prototype	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
fibula	0	O
shape	0	O
,	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
only	0	O
three	0	O
are	0	O
known	0	O
so	0	O
far	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
chief	0	O
curator	0	O
reports	0	O
,	0	O
all	0	O
come	0	O
from	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
common	0	O
feature	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
three	0	O
disc	0	O
brooches	0	O
is	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
eagle	1	S-PER
is	0	O
represented	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
peacock	0	O
crown	0	O
of	0	O
spread	0	O
wings	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
mixture	0	O
of	0	O
eagle	1	S-PER
and	0	O
peacock	2	S-PER
has	0	O
a	0	O
deeply	0	O
Christian	0	O
meaning	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
eagle	1	S-PER
symbolizes	0	O
resurrection	0	O
and	0	O
ascension	0	O
Christ	2	S-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
peacock	0	O
symbolizes	0	O
eternal	0	O
life	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
crowned	0	O
bird	0	O
was	0	O
also	0	O
regarded	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
imperial	0	O
emblem	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
forerunner	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Hohenstaufen	0	O
imperial	1	B-MISC
eagle	1	E-MISC
is	0	O
also	0	O
an	0	O
indication	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
chronological	0	O
order	0	O
.	0	O

His	0	O
body	0	O
shape	0	O
in	0	O
frontal	0	O
view	0	O
,	0	O
only	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
in	0	O
profile	0	O
,	0	O
obviously	0	O
goes	0	O
back	0	O
to	0	O
Islamic	0	O
art	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
10th	0	O
century	0	O
.	0	O

From	0	O
a	0	O
stylistic	0	O
point	0	O
of	0	O
view	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
beautiful	0	O
and	0	O
''	0	O
highest	0	O
quality	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
three	0	O
eagle	1	B-MISC
brooches	1	E-MISC
has	0	O
new	0	O
dimensions	0	O
.	0	O

Instead	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
small	0	O
center	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
used	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
framed	0	O
with	0	O
wide	0	O
margins	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
dominant	0	O
large	0	O
motif	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
surrounded	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
narrow	0	O
border	0	O
.	0	O

Another	0	O
indication	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
dating	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
openwork	0	O
enamel	0	O
brooch	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
middle	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
11th	0	O
century	0	O
are	0	O
small	0	O
flower	0	O
stems	0	O
made	0	O
of	0	O
gold	0	O
wire	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
curves	0	O
and	0	O
pearl	0	O
wire	0	O
lines	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
ends	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
peacock	0	O
wheel	0	O
.	0	O

Where	0	O
and	0	O
by	0	O
whom	0	O
the	0	O
precious	0	O
jewelry	0	O
was	0	O
made	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
be	0	O
guessed	0	O
at	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
it	0	O
points	0	O
to	0	O
Byzantine	0	O
or	0	O
Italian	1	S-MISC
goldsmiths	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
perhaps	0	O
immigrated	0	O
at	0	O
that	0	O
time	0	O
or	0	O
were	0	O
resident	0	O
in	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
for	0	O
a	0	O
longer	0	O
time	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
Mainz	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
called	0	O
''	0	O
Diadem	2	B-LOC
of	2	I-LOC
the	2	I-LOC
Empire	2	E-LOC
''	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
High	0	O
Middle	0	O
Ages	0	O
,	0	O
was	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
stays	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
king	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
Salian	0	O
period	0	O
and	0	O
owned	0	O
jewelry	0	O
workshops	0	O
of	0	O
supraregional	0	O
importance	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
traces	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
can	0	O
still	0	O
be	0	O
traced	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
banks	3	B-LOC
of	3	I-LOC
the	3	I-LOC
Rhine	3	E-LOC
through	0	O
lead	0	O
waste	0	O
,	0	O
raw	0	O
castings	0	O
and	0	O
semi	0	O
finished	0	O
products	0	O
.	0	O

Since	0	O
the	0	O
vast	0	O
majority	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
pieces	0	O
of	0	O
jewelery	0	O
date	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
middle	0	O
third	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
11th	0	O
century	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
most	0	O
likely	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
ascribed	0	O
to	0	O
Agnes	1	B-PER
von	1	I-PER
Poitou	1	E-PER
,	0	O
says	0	O
Mechthild	2	B-PER
SchulzI	2	I-PER
Dörlamm	2	E-PER
,	0	O
especially	0	O
since	0	O
a	0	O
golden	0	O
finger	0	O
ring	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
image	0	O
of	0	O
her	0	O
husband	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
emperor	0	O
Heinrich	3	B-PER
III	3	I-PER
.	3	E-PER
,	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
preserved	0	O
underneath	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
deeds	0	O
of	0	O
donation	0	O
for	0	O
extensive	0	O
estates	0	O
and	0	O
possessions	0	O
issued	0	O
immediately	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
wedding	0	O
,	0	O
Henry	1	B-PER
III	1	E-PER
made	0	O
her	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
richly	0	O
endowed	0	O
queens	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
history	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
medieval	0	O
empire	2	S-LOC
;	0	O
whether	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
expression	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
affection	0	O
or	0	O
a	0	O
foresighted	0	O
,	0	O
independent	0	O
provision	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
foreign	0	O
''	0	O
ruler	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
known	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
unlikely	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
wealthy	0	O
empress	0	O
could	0	O
later	0	O
have	0	O
pledged	0	O
all	0	O
of	0	O
her	0	O
jewelry	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
Jewish	1	S-MISC
dealer	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
conceivable	0	O
that	0	O
Agnes	1	S-PER
as	0	O
regent	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
throne	0	O
in	0	O
1066	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
occasion	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
wedding	0	O
of	0	O
her	0	O
son	0	O
and	0	O
heir	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
throne	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
was	0	O
barely	0	O
16	0	O
years	0	O
old	0	O
,	0	O
Henry	2	B-PER
IV	2	E-PER
,	0	O
with	0	O
Bertha	3	B-PER
von	3	E-PER
Turin	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
who	0	O
was	0	O
almost	0	O
a	0	O
year	0	O
younger	0	O
officially	0	O
presented	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
to	0	O
her	0	O
daughter	0	O
in	0	O
law	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
gift	0	O
.	0	O

Bertha	1	S-PER
almost	0	O
belonged	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
family	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
young	0	O
girl	0	O
she	0	O
had	0	O
already	0	O
given	0	O
up	0	O
the	0	O
throne	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
withdrew	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
Italian	3	S-MISC
monastery	0	O
,	0	O
where	0	O
she	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
needed	0	O
the	0	O
representative	0	O
jewelry	0	O
.	0	O

When	0	O
Empress	0	O
Bertha	1	S-PER
died	0	O
in	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
in	0	O
1087	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
a	0	O
time	0	O
when	0	O
Heinrich	3	B-PER
IV	3	E-PER
was	0	O
equipping	0	O
his	0	O
third	0	O
Rome	4	B-LOC
campaign	4	E-LOC
and	0	O
was	0	O
again	0	O
struggling	0	O
with	0	O
financial	0	O
difficulties	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
his	0	O
numerous	0	O
military	0	O
campaigns	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
could	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
possible	0	O
that	0	O
under	0	O
these	0	O
circumstances	0	O
he	0	O
would	0	O
find	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
deceased	0	O
wife	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
reliable	0	O
one	0	O
,	0	O
rich	0	O
Jews	5	S-MISC
has	0	O
pledged	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
when	0	O
Heinrich	1	S-PER
returned	0	O
to	0	O
Mainz	2	S-LOC
ten	0	O
years	0	O
later	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
no	0	O
trace	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
a	0	O
year	0	O
earlier	0	O
,	0	O
almost	0	O
all	0	O
residents	0	O
of	0	O
Jewish	1	B-LOC
Quarter	1	E-LOC
had	0	O
died	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
pogrom	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
crusaders	0	O
,	0	O
including	0	O
as	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
handed	0	O
down	0	O
the	0	O
synagogue	0	O
ruler	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
set	0	O
fire	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
synagogue	0	O
and	0	O
house	0	O
two	0	O
days	0	O
after	0	O
his	0	O
forced	0	O
baptism	0	O
and	0	O
burned	0	O
himself	0	O
with	0	O
his	0	O
whole	0	O
family	0	O
in	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

Old	0	O
scorch	0	O
marks	0	O
are	0	O
said	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
visible	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
jewelry	0	O
was	0	O
surprisingly	0	O
discovered	0	O
after	0	O
800	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

Even	0	O
if	0	O
the	0	O
history	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
gold	0	O
jewelery	0	O
leaves	0	O
some	0	O
questions	0	O
unanswered	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
individual	0	O
pieces	0	O
have	0	O
a	0	O
special	0	O
cultural	0	O
and	0	O
historical	0	O
value	0	O
and	0	O
convey	0	O
,	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
framework	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
newly	0	O
gained	0	O
knowledge	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
lively	0	O
picture	0	O
of	0	O
medieval	0	O
splendor	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
imperial	0	O
court	0	O
but	0	O
above	0	O
all	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
Salian	0	O
empress	0	O
who	0	O
made	0	O
the	0	O
famous	0	O
''	0	O
Gisela	1	B-MISC
primer	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
has	0	O
really	0	O
worn	0	O
:	0	O

Agnes	1	B-PER
of	1	I-PER
Poitou	1	E-PER
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Doctors	1	S-ORG

Emergency	0	O
service	0	O
:	0	O

DRK	1	B-ORG
House	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Flachstrasse	2	B-LOC
1	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

46	0	O
10	0	O
10	0	O
;	0	O
fixed	0	O
emergency	0	O
doctor	0	O
's	0	O
office	0	O
hours	0	O
:	0	O

11	0	O
a.m.	0	O
to	0	O
1	0	O
p.m.	0	O
and	0	O
3	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
8	0	O
p.m	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Pharmacies	1	S-ORG

Sa	0	O
.	0	O
:	0	O

Pharmacy	1	B-ORG
on	1	I-ORG
the	1	I-ORG
market	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Marktstr	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC
12	0	O
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

30	0	O
65	0	O
09	0	O
.	0	O

Kohlheck	1	B-ORG
Pharmacy	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Eulenstr	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC
5	0	O
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

46	0	O
65	0	O
15	0	O
.	0	O

Merian	1	B-ORG
Pharmacy	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Kaiser	2	B-LOC
Friedrich	2	I-LOC
Ring	2	I-LOC
30	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

30	0	O
64	0	O
91	0	O
.	0	O

So	1	B-LOC
.	1	E-LOC
:	0	O

Elephant	1	B-ORG
Pharmacy	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Kirchgasse	2	S-LOC
18	0	O
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

30	0	O
33	0	O
48	0	O
.	0	O

ParacelsuI	1	B-ORG
pharmacy	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Schultheißstr	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC
32	0	O
a	0	O
,	0	O
Bierstadt	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
Tel	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

50	0	O
27	0	O
25	0	O
.	0	O

Sonnen	1	B-ORG
Apotheke	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Brunhildenstr	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC
25	0	O
,	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

76	0	O
15	0	O
92	0	O
.	0	O

Ophthalmologists	0	O

J.	1	B-PER
Litsch	1	E-PER
,	0	O
Mainzer	2	B-LOC
Str	2	I-LOC
.	2	E-LOC
36	0	O
,	0	O
Wiesbaden	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
Tel	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

06	0	O
11/30	0	O
34	0	O
45	0	O
(	0	O
practice	0	O
)	0	O
or	0	O
06	0	O
11/80	0	O
99	0	O
11	0	O
(	0	O
apartment	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

A	0	O
new	0	O
award	0	O
for	0	O
engagement	0	O
in	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
politics	0	O
City	1	B-LOC
of	1	I-LOC
Frankfurt	1	E-LOC
awards	0	O
''	0	O
Tony	2	B-MISC
Sender	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
Award	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
time	0	O
in	0	O
autumn	0	O
1992	0	O
/	0	O
Local	0	O
reference	0	O
is	0	O
in	0	O
demand	0	O

FRANKFURT	1	B-LOC
AM	1	E-LOC
As	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
German	0	O
city	0	O
Frankfurt	2	B-LOC
am	2	I-LOC
Main	2	E-LOC
to	0	O
receive	0	O
a	0	O
prize	0	O
for	0	O
engagement	0	O
in	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
politics	0	O
or	0	O
work	0	O
in	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
research	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
local	0	O
reference	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
newly	0	O
created	0	O
Tony	1	B-MISC
Sender	1	I-MISC
Prize	1	E-MISC
,	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
of	0	O
Frankfurt	2	S-LOC
would	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
honor	0	O
outstanding	0	O
innovative	0	O
achievements	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
field	0	O
of	0	O
employment	0	O
and	0	O
work	0	O
that	0	O
deals	0	O
with	0	O
cultural	0	O
or	0	O
social	0	O
issues	0	O
.	0	O

Frankfurterinnen	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
projects	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
city	0	O
or	0	O
women	0	O
who	0	O
dedicate	0	O
themselves	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
Frankfurt	2	S-MISC
topic	0	O
are	0	O
worthy	0	O
of	0	O
prizes	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Tony	1	B-MISC
Sender	1	I-MISC
Prize	1	E-MISC
is	0	O
endowed	0	O
with	0	O
20,000	0	O
Mark	2	S-MISC
and	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
awarded	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
time	0	O
on	0	O
November	0	O
27	0	O
,	0	O
1992	0	O
,	0	O
thereafter	0	O
every	0	O
two	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
Tony	1	B-MISC
Sender	1	I-MISC
Prize	1	E-MISC
,	0	O
the	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
department	0	O
would	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
draw	0	O
attention	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
40	0	O
years	0	O
after	0	O
Constitution	2	B-MISC
of	2	I-MISC
the	2	I-MISC
Federal	2	I-MISC
Republic	2	E-MISC
came	0	O
into	0	O
force	0	O
,	0	O
Basic	3	B-MISC
Law	3	I-MISC
Article	3	E-MISC
3.2	0	O
''	0	O
Men	0	O
and	0	O
women	0	O
have	0	O
equal	0	O
rights	0	O
''	0	O
is	0	O
still	0	O
being	0	O
violated	0	O
.	0	O

Women	0	O
continue	0	O
to	0	O
face	0	O
disadvantages	0	O
in	0	O
many	0	O
areas	0	O
of	0	O
daily	0	O
life	0	O
.	0	O

Who	0	O
was	0	O
the	0	O
woman	0	O
whose	0	O
name	0	O
the	0	O
award	0	O
will	0	O
again	0	O
make	0	O
known	0	O
beyond	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
limits	0	O
?	0	O

Tony	1	B-PER
Sender	1	E-PER
was	0	O
born	0	O
in	0	O
1888	0	O
in	0	O
what	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
the	0	O
Wiesbaden	2	S-MISC
district	0	O
of	0	O
Biebrich	3	S-LOC
as	0	O
the	0	O
daughter	0	O
of	0	O
well	0	O
off	0	O
parents	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Fin	1	B-MISC
de	1	E-MISC
siècle	0	O
and	0	O
her	0	O
social	0	O
class	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
life	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
sheltered	0	O
daughter	0	O
and	0	O
instruction	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
salon	0	O
sciences	0	O
''	0	O
lay	0	O
ahead	0	O
of	0	O
her	0	O
in	0	O
order	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
her	0	O
intended	0	O
place	0	O
in	0	O
bourgeois	0	O
society	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
wife	0	O
and	0	O
mother	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
already	0	O
at	0	O
secondary	1	B-ORG
school	1	I-ORG
for	1	I-ORG
girls	1	E-ORG
Tony	2	B-PER
Sender	2	E-PER
realized	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
restricted	0	O
to	0	O
''	0	O
children	0	O
,	0	O
kitchen	0	O
,	0	O
church	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
struggle	0	O
for	0	O
more	0	O
freedom	0	O
should	0	O
not	0	O
stop	0	O
in	0	O
her	0	O
life	0	O
.	0	O

Instead	0	O
of	0	O
working	0	O
on	0	O
her	0	O
trousseau	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
got	0	O
through	0	O
to	0	O
attend	0	O
a	0	O
commercial	0	O
college	0	O
and	0	O
thus	0	O
secured	0	O
her	0	O
independence	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
commercial	0	O
clerk	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
22	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
began	0	O
her	0	O
political	0	O
work	0	O
in	0	O
Paris	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
where	0	O
she	0	O
worked	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
correspondent	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
German	2	S-MISC
company	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
evening	0	O
besides	0	O
studying	0	O
socialist	0	O
theorists	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
involved	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
French	3	S-MISC
labor	0	O
movement	0	O
and	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
education	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
outbreak	0	O
of	0	O
First	2	B-MISC
World	2	I-MISC
War	2	E-MISC
put	0	O
an	0	O
abrupt	0	O
end	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
stay	0	O
in	0	O
Paris	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
which	0	O
promoted	0	O
their	0	O
emancipation	0	O
;	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
expelled	0	O
as	0	O
German	3	S-MISC
of	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

Returning	0	O
to	0	O
Frankfurt	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Tony	2	B-PER
Sender	2	E-PER
joined	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
democratic	0	O
war	0	O
opposition	0	O
and	0	O
became	0	O
a	0	O
vehement	0	O
campaigner	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
war	0	O
that	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
serve	0	O
to	0	O
defend	0	O
the	0	O
fatherland	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
to	0	O
conquer	0	O
new	0	O
sales	0	O
markets	0	O
and	0	O
to	0	O
oppress	0	O
previously	0	O
free	0	O
peoples	0	O
.	0	O

She	0	O
was	0	O
an	0	O
opponent	0	O
of	0	O
SPD	1	B-ORG
Burgfriedenspolitik	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
was	0	O
expelled	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
party	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
1917	0	O
co	0	O
founder	0	O
of	0	O
USPD	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
Independent	1	B-MISC
Social	1	I-MISC
Democrat	1	E-MISC
wrote	0	O
Frankfurt	2	B-MISC
City	2	I-MISC
History	2	E-MISC
during	0	O
the	0	O
November	0	O
Revolution	0	O
.	0	O

She	0	O
was	0	O
general	0	O
secretary	0	O
of	0	O
workers	1	B-ORG
'	1	I-ORG
council	1	E-ORG
and	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
introduction	0	O
of	0	O
women	0	O
's	0	O
suffrage	0	O
in	0	O
November	0	O
1918	0	O
a	0	O
member	0	O
of	0	O
Frankfurt	2	B-ORG
City	2	I-ORG
Council	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
young	0	O
Weimar	1	B-LOC
Republic	1	E-LOC
did	0	O
not	0	O
find	0	O
Tony	2	B-PER
Senders	2	E-PER
unreserved	0	O
approval	0	O
;	0	O
she	0	O
had	0	O
hoped	0	O
for	0	O
more	0	O
grassroots	0	O
democracy	0	O
from	0	O
revolution	3	S-MISC
:	0	O

the	0	O
implementation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
council	1	B-MISC
idea	1	E-MISC
in	0	O
politics	0	O
,	0	O
economics	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
companies	0	O
.	0	O

As	0	O
editor	0	O
of	0	O
USPD	1	B-ORG
daily	1	I-ORG
newspaper	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
Volksrecht	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
and	0	O
''	0	O
BetriebsratsI	3	B-ORG
Zeitschrift	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
of	0	O
German	4	B-ORG
Metal	4	I-ORG
Workers	4	I-ORG
Association	4	E-ORG
she	0	O
criticized	0	O
the	0	O
political	0	O
development	0	O
;	0	O
As	0	O
a	0	O
member	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
German	5	B-ORG
Reichstag	5	E-ORG
and	0	O
party	0	O
politician	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
did	0	O
her	0	O
best	0	O
to	0	O
actively	0	O
shape	0	O
politics	0	O
.	0	O

Faced	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
decision	0	O
to	0	O
either	0	O
submit	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
dictation	0	O
of	0	O
Lenin	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
and	0	O
host	0	O
USPD	2	S-ORG
in	0	O
Moscow	0	O
or	0	O
to	0	O
return	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
ranks	0	O
of	0	O
Social	3	B-ORG
Democrats	3	E-ORG
,	0	O
Tony	4	B-PER
Sender	4	E-PER
once	0	O
again	0	O
chose	0	O
the	0	O
freedom	0	O
this	0	O
time	0	O
not	0	O
to	0	O
let	0	O
the	0	O
party	0	O
's	0	O
strategy	0	O
be	0	O
determined	0	O
by	0	O
others	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
was	0	O
not	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
light	0	O
heart	0	O
that	0	O
she	0	O
decided	0	O
to	0	O
reunite	0	O
with	0	O
SPD	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
in	0	O
her	0	O
opinion	0	O
had	0	O
come	0	O
to	0	O
terms	0	O
too	0	O
much	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
bourgeois	0	O
republic	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

In	0	O
Parliament	0	O
she	0	O
emerged	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
recognized	0	O
specialist	0	O
in	0	O
economic	0	O
and	0	O
foreign	0	O
policy	0	O
issues	0	O
;	0	O
As	0	O
a	0	O
politician	0	O
and	0	O
editor	0	O
in	0	O
chief	0	O
of	0	O
SPD	1	B-ORG
magazine	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
Frauenwelt	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
campaigned	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
equal	0	O
participation	0	O
of	0	O
women	0	O
in	0	O
all	0	O
areas	0	O
of	0	O
life	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Jew	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
social	0	O
democrat	0	O
and	0	O
trade	0	O
unionist	0	O
,	0	O
was	0	O
targeted	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
National	2	B-MISC
Socialists	2	E-MISC
in	0	O
the	0	O
late	0	O
1920s	0	O
.	0	O

An	0	O
open	0	O
death	0	O
threat	0	O
prompted	0	O
her	0	O
to	0	O
flee	0	O
via	0	O
Czechoslovakia	1	S-LOC
to	0	O
Belgium	2	S-LOC
immediately	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
Reichstag	0	O
election	0	O
on	0	O
March	0	O
5	0	O
,	0	O
1933	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
1935	0	O
she	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
return	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
USA	1	B-LOC
stay	1	E-LOC
to	0	O
the	0	O
provincial	0	O
Narrow	2	B-LOC
Flanders	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
settled	0	O
in	0	O
New	3	B-LOC
York	3	E-LOC
and	0	O
soon	0	O
applied	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
UI	4	B-MISC
citizenship	4	E-MISC
.	0	O

The	0	O
United	1	B-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
in	0	O
the	0	O
era	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
reformist	0	O
''	0	O
New	2	B-MISC
Deal	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
seemed	0	O
to	0	O
offer	0	O
it	0	O
the	0	O
greatest	0	O
possible	0	O
guarantee	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
life	0	O
in	0	O
individual	0	O
and	0	O
political	0	O
freedom	0	O
and	0	O
without	0	O
being	0	O
forced	0	O
to	0	O
adhere	0	O
to	0	O
social	0	O
conventions	0	O
.	0	O

Tony	1	B-PER
Sender	1	E-PER
reached	0	O
a	0	O
final	0	O
professional	0	O
high	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
representative	0	O
first	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
UI	2	B-MISC
American	2	E-MISC
,	0	O
later	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
international	0	O
trade	3	B-ORG
union	3	I-ORG
federation	3	E-ORG
at	0	O
the	0	O
Economic	4	B-ORG
and	4	I-ORG
Social	4	I-ORG
Council	4	I-ORG
of	4	I-ORG
the	4	I-ORG
UN	4	E-ORG
.	0	O

She	0	O
did	0	O
her	0	O
main	0	O
work	0	O
in	0	O
Commission	1	B-ORG
on	1	I-ORG
the	1	I-ORG
Status	1	I-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Women	1	E-ORG
and	0	O
Human	2	B-ORG
Rights	2	I-ORG
Commission	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

Her	0	O
name	0	O
is	0	O
associated	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
fight	0	O
against	0	O
human	0	O
slavery	0	O
through	0	O
forced	0	O
labor	0	O
and	0	O
against	0	O
politically	0	O
motivated	0	O
deprivation	0	O
of	0	O
liberty	0	O
.	0	O

She	0	O
tirelessly	0	O
gathered	0	O
evidence	0	O
of	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
violations	0	O
and	0	O
fearlessly	0	O
charged	0	O
those	0	O
states	0	O
that	0	O
violated	0	O
human	0	O
and	0	O
civil	0	O
rights	0	O
.	0	O

Until	0	O
her	0	O
death	0	O
in	0	O
1964	0	O
,	0	O
Tony	1	B-PER
Sender	1	E-PER
held	0	O
steadfastly	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
women	0	O
and	0	O
men	0	O
can	0	O
achieve	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
performance	0	O
if	0	O
they	0	O
only	0	O
have	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
opportunities	0	O
and	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
hindered	0	O
by	0	O
social	0	O
norms	0	O
or	0	O
economic	0	O
disadvantages	0	O
.	0	O

Her	0	O
program	0	O
was	0	O
to	0	O
break	0	O
down	0	O
class	0	O
and	0	O
gender	0	O
barriers	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
them	0	O
disappear	0	O
completely	0	O
.	0	O

Her	0	O
goal	0	O
was	0	O
to	0	O
achieve	0	O
a	0	O
way	0	O
of	0	O
life	0	O
in	0	O
free	0	O
self	0	O
determination	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Medical	0	O
help	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
homeless	0	O
An	0	O
outpatient	0	O
clinic	0	O
treats	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Berbers	1	S-MISC
''	0	O
that	0	O
are	0	O
often	0	O
sent	0	O
away	0	O
in	0	O
medical	0	O
practices	0	O

FRANKFURT	1	B-LOC
AM	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
So	0	O
,	0	O
feet	0	O
stay	0	O
in	0	O
for	0	O
20	0	O
minutes	0	O
now	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

In	0	O
a	0	O
friendly	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
determined	0	O
tone	0	O
,	0	O
Klaus	1	B-PER
Hetzel	1	E-PER
,	0	O
nurse	0	O
and	0	O
hygiene	0	O
specialist	0	O
,	0	O
gives	0	O
his	0	O
instructions	0	O
.	0	O

Josef	1	B-PER
Schmidt	1	E-PER
(	0	O
name	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
the	2	I-ORG
Red	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

changed	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
homeless	0	O
,	0	O
obediently	0	O
puts	0	O
his	0	O
sore	0	O
legs	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
large	0	O
plastic	0	O
bucket	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
dark	0	O
purple	0	O
liquid.	0	O
''	0	O

Open	0	O
legs	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
explains	0	O
Klaus	1	B-PER
Hetzel	1	E-PER
,	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
common	0	O
disease	0	O
among	0	O
the	0	O
homeless.	0	O
''	0	O

The	0	O
''	0	O
Medical	1	B-ORG
Ambulance	1	I-ORG
for	1	I-ORG
Residents	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
in	0	O
Sachsenhausen	2	S-LOC
opened	0	O
its	0	O
doors	0	O
on	0	O
May	0	O
18th	0	O
.	0	O

Within	0	O
two	0	O
weeks	0	O
,	0	O
21	0	O
patients	0	O
were	0	O
at	0	O
Hetzel	1	S-PER
and	0	O
his	0	O
team	0	O
.	0	O

Almost	0	O
all	0	O
patients	0	O
,	0	O
says	0	O
the	0	O
nurse	0	O
,	0	O
complained	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
smoking	0	O
legs	0	O
''	0	O
or	0	O
''	0	O
lower	0	O
leg	0	O
ulcers	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
treated	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
potassium	0	O
permanganate	0	O
disinfectant	0	O
solution.	0	O
''	0	O

Other	0	O
doctors	0	O
suggest	0	O
other	0	O
means	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
reports	0	O
Hetzel	1	S-PER
.	0	O

But	0	O
he	0	O
can	0	O
show	0	O
and	0	O
prove	0	O
success	0	O
with	0	O
his	0	O
method	0	O
:	0	O

Hetzel	1	S-PER
documents	0	O
all	0	O
treatments	0	O
with	0	O
photos	0	O
or	0	O
video	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
homeless	0	O
could	0	O
see	0	O
for	0	O
themselves	0	O
what	0	O
the	0	O
regular	0	O
use	0	O
would	0	O
bring	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
newcomers	0	O
can	0	O
also	0	O
be	0	O
more	0	O
easily	0	O
convinced	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
purpose	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
undertaking	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
pictures	0	O
.	0	O

Mistrust	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
main	0	O
reason	0	O
why	0	O
most	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
homeless	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
undergo	0	O
''	0	O
normal	0	O
''	0	O
medical	0	O
therapy	0	O
,	0	O
explains	0	O
Hetzel.	1	S-PER
''	0	O

There	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
way	0	O
I	0	O
will	0	O
go	0	O
back	0	O
to	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
agrees	0	O
Josef	1	B-PER
Schmidt	1	E-PER
.	0	O

He	0	O
knows	0	O
what	0	O
he	0	O
's	0	O
talking	0	O
about	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
their	0	O
mostly	0	O
not	0	O
exactly	0	O
''	0	O
bourgeois	0	O
''	0	O
appearance	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Berbers	1	S-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
they	0	O
call	0	O
themselves	0	O
,	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
welcome	0	O
customers	0	O
in	0	O
medical	0	O
practices	0	O
.	0	O

Often	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
sent	0	O
away	0	O
with	0	O
excuses	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
problem	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
undersupply	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
homeless	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
medical	0	O
field	0	O
has	0	O
long	0	O
been	0	O
recognized	0	O
by	0	O
Hetzel	1	S-PER
at	0	O
his	0	O
other	0	O
job	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
homeless	0	O
food	0	O
counter	0	O
in	0	O
Affentorhaus	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Together	0	O
with	0	O
his	0	O
wife	0	O
Dagmar	1	S-PER
she	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
doctor	0	O
and	0	O
makes	0	O
the	0	O
diagnoses	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Medical	2	B-LOC
Ambulance	2	E-LOC
''	0	O
he	0	O
offered	0	O
one	0	O
hour	0	O
of	0	O
care	0	O
there	0	O
a	0	O
week	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
was	0	O
not	0	O
enough	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
above	0	O
all	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
necessary	0	O
facilities	0	O
were	0	O
missing	0	O
.	0	O

They	0	O
are	0	O
available	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
new	0	O
domicile	0	O
:	0	O

Three	0	O
rooms	0	O
,	0	O
fully	0	O
furnished	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
bathroom	0	O
with	0	O
everything	0	O
you	0	O
need	0	O
for	0	O
personal	0	O
hygiene	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
rooms	0	O
serves	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
treatment	0	O
room	0	O
,	0	O
another	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
office	0	O
(	0	O
''	0	O
finally	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
paperwork	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
at	0	O
home	0	O
''	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
finally	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
lounge	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
entrance	0	O
area	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
waiting	0	O
room	0	O
''	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
coffee	0	O
bar	0	O
and	0	O
intended	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
communication	0	O
center	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
carrier	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Medical	1	B-LOC
Ambulance	1	E-LOC
is	0	O
the	0	O
Working	2	B-ORG
Group	2	I-ORG
for	2	I-ORG
Evangelistic	2	I-ORG
Communication	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
AFEK	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
registered	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
non	0	O
profit	0	O
association	0	O
since	0	O
1984	0	O
and	0	O
is	0	O
financed	0	O
entirely	0	O
through	0	O
donations	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
manage	0	O
his	0	O
statutory	0	O
goal	0	O
of	0	O
looking	0	O
after	0	O
marginalized	0	O
groups	0	O
by	0	O
giving	0	O
''	0	O
help	0	O
on	0	O
self	1	B-MISC
help	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
seen	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Medical	1	B-MISC
Ambulance	1	E-MISC
project	0	O
.	0	O

Without	0	O
the	0	O
committed	0	O
help	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
formerly	0	O
homeless	0	O
people	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
rooms	0	O
would	0	O
hardly	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
renovated	0	O
so	0	O
quickly	0	O
and	0	O
cheaply.	0	O
''	0	O

That	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
completely	0	O
shabby	0	O
pub.	1	S-LOC
''	0	O

All	0	O
work	0	O
,	0	O
even	0	O
the	0	O
bricklaying	0	O
and	0	O
tiling	0	O
,	0	O
had	0	O
been	0	O
done	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
helpers.	0	O
''	0	O

If	0	O
they	0	O
have	0	O
a	0	O
goal	0	O
in	0	O
mind	0	O
,	0	O
then	0	O
they	0	O
become	0	O
aware	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
social	0	O
responsibility	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
explained	0	O
Hetzel	1	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
describes	0	O
himself	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
resolute	0	O
Christian	2	S-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
commitment	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
formerly	0	O
homeless	0	O
.	0	O

His	0	O
credo	0	O
is	0	O
therefore	0	O
an	0	O
old	0	O
Indian	1	B-MISC
prayer	1	E-MISC
that	0	O
hangs	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
poster	0	O
across	0	O
from	0	O
his	0	O
office	2	B-PER
chair	2	E-PER
:	0	O

''	0	O
Great	0	O
mind	0	O
,	0	O
save	0	O
me	0	O
from	0	O
judging	0	O
a	0	O
person	0	O
until	0	O
I	0	O
have	0	O
walked	0	O
half	0	O
a	0	O
moon	1	S-LOC
in	0	O
his	0	O
moccasins	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

Since	0	O
the	0	O
AFEK	1	S-ORG
talks	0	O
completely	0	O
about	0	O
donations	0	O
,	0	O
financial	0	O
help	0	O
in	0	O
particular	0	O
is	0	O
always	0	O
welcome	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
information	0	O
,	0	O
Klaus	1	B-PER
Hetzel	1	E-PER
can	0	O
call	0	O
62	0	O
35	0	O
59	0	O
from	0	O
Monday	0	O
to	0	O
Thursday	0	O
between	0	O
9	0	O
a.m.	0	O
and	0	O
5	0	O
p.m.	0	O
and	0	O
on	0	O
Fridays	0	O
between	0	O
9	0	O
a.m.	0	O
and	0	O
1	0	O
p.m	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Ludwig	1	B-PER
's	1	I-PER
linden	1	I-PER
tree	1	E-PER
and	0	O
a	0	O
lovely	0	O
maiden	0	O

AUERBACH	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
often	0	O
quoted	0	O
and	0	O
much	0	O
sung	0	O
''	0	O
Tree	1	B-MISC
in	1	I-MISC
the	1	I-MISC
Odenwald	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
like	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
repeatedly	0	O
mentioned	0	O
''	0	O
Siegfriedquelle	2	S-LOC
''	0	O
,	0	O
where	0	O
the	0	O
legendary	0	O
Recke	3	S-PER
died	0	O
:	0	O

nobody	0	O
is	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
say	0	O
and	0	O
prove	0	O
exactly	0	O
where	0	O
both	0	O
natural	0	O
monuments	0	O
are	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
found	0	O
.	0	O

Therefore	0	O
one	0	O
need	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
surprised	0	O
that	0	O
these	0	O
are	0	O
present	0	O
several	0	O
times	0	O
.	0	O

So	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
said	0	O
tree	0	O
in	0	O
Momart	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Kimbach	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Airlenbach	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
Olfen	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
also	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
vicinity	0	O
of	0	O
Prince	5	B-LOC
's	5	I-LOC
Camp	5	E-LOC
at	0	O
Auerbach	6	S-LOC
(	0	O
Bergstrasse	7	B-LOC
district	7	E-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

Perhaps	0	O
the	0	O
last	0	O
mentioned	0	O
place	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
regarded	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
real	0	O
''	0	O
one	0	O
,	0	O
because	0	O
a	0	O
linden	1	S-MISC
was	0	O
planted	0	O
there	0	O
in	0	O
1778	0	O
and	0	O
named	0	O
''	0	O
Tree	2	B-MISC
in	2	I-MISC
the	2	I-MISC
Odenwald	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Fürstenlager	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
former	0	O
summer	0	O
residence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Hessian	0	O
landgraves	0	O
,	0	O
with	0	O
its	0	O
friendly	0	O
park	0	O
interspersed	0	O
with	0	O
numerous	0	O
exotic	0	O
trees	0	O
,	0	O
also	0	O
seems	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
right	0	O
setting	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
legendary	0	O
Linden	2	S-MISC
.	0	O

Because	0	O
closely	0	O
connected	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Tree	1	B-MISC
in	1	I-MISC
the	1	I-MISC
Odenwald	1	E-MISC
''	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
graceful	0	O
Prince	2	B-LOC
's	2	I-LOC
Camp	2	E-LOC
is	0	O
a	0	O
love	0	O
romance	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
park	0	O
and	0	O
forest	0	O
scenery	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
opera	1	B-MISC
singer	1	E-MISC
,	0	O
later	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
Darmstädter	2	B-LOC
Hoftheater	2	E-LOC
and	0	O
master	0	O
of	0	O
local	0	O
storytelling	0	O
,	0	O
Ernst	3	B-PER
Pasqué	3	E-PER
,	0	O
traced	0	O
them	0	O
in	0	O
literary	0	O
terms	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
the	0	O
poet	0	O
was	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
do	0	O
this	0	O
is	0	O
easy	0	O
to	0	O
explain	0	O
:	0	O

He	0	O
lived	0	O
for	0	O
two	0	O
decades	0	O
(	0	O
1871	0	O
to	0	O
1892	0	O
)	0	O
at	0	O
Bergstrasse	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
,	0	O
through	0	O
his	0	O
good	0	O
relations	0	O
with	0	O
Grand	0	O
Duke	0	O
Ludwig	2	B-PER
IV	2	E-PER
,	0	O
learned	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
that	0	O
characterizes	0	O
the	0	O
originality	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
story	0	O
''	0	O
There	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
tree	0	O
in	0	O
Odenwald	3	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
''	0	O
Schauplatz	1	B-LOC
Fürstenlager	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
Landgraf	0	O
Friedrich	2	S-PER
got	0	O
to	0	O
know	0	O
Karoline	3	B-PER
Seitz	3	E-PER
from	0	O
Grasellenbach	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
a	0	O
girl	0	O
of	0	O
simple	0	O
origin	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
miraculous	0	O
way	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
married	0	O
her	0	O
and	0	O
had	0	O
a	0	O
happy	0	O
marriage	0	O
with	0	O
her	0	O
.	0	O

Pasqué	1	S-PER
portrayed	0	O
Karoline	2	S-PER
in	0	O
his	0	O
little	0	O
book	0	O
as	0	O
''	0	O
a	0	O
strikingly	0	O
beautiful	0	O
very	0	O
young	0	O
thing	0	O
of	0	O
about	0	O
17	0	O
years	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
blonde	0	O
whose	0	O
fine	0	O
,	0	O
naturally	0	O
ruffled	0	O
blonde	0	O
curls	0	O
peeked	0	O
out	0	O
a	0	O
little	0	O
too	0	O
curiously	0	O
under	0	O
the	0	O
velvet	0	O
cap	0	O
and	0	O
spread	0	O
out	0	O
on	0	O
her	0	O
white	0	O
forehead	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
this	0	O
chance	0	O
meeting	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
occasion	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
court	0	O
festival	0	O
in	0	O
Prince	1	B-LOC
's	1	I-LOC
Camp	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Karoline	2	S-PER
is	0	O
said	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
sung	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
folk	0	O
song	0	O
''	0	O
Es	0	O
stands	3	S-MISC
Baum	0	O
im	0	O
Odenwald	4	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
memory	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
festival	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
young	0	O
Linden	1	B-MISC
tree	1	E-MISC
was	0	O
planted	0	O
''	0	O
with	0	O
all	0	O
sorts	0	O
of	0	O
solemn	0	O
ceremonies	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
at	0	O
a	0	O
point	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
heights	0	O
from	0	O
which	0	O
one	0	O
had	0	O
a	0	O
wonderful	0	O
view	0	O
of	0	O
Schönberger	2	B-LOC
Valley	2	E-LOC
and	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
picturesque	0	O
castle	0	O
of	0	O
Counts	3	B-LOC
of	3	I-LOC
Erbach	3	I-LOC
Schönberg	3	E-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
hermit	1	S-MISC
spoke	0	O
''	0	O
to	0	O
forest	2	B-MISC
blessing	2	E-MISC
about	0	O
the	0	O
young	0	O
linden	3	B-PER
tree	3	E-PER
,	0	O
whom	0	O
he	0	O
inspired	0	O
by	0	O
Karolin	4	B-PER
's	4	E-PER
vocals	0	O
'christened	0	O
tree	5	S-PER
in	0	O
Odenwald	6	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
this	0	O
tree	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
exists	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
lightning	0	O
strike	0	O
destroyed	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
place	0	O
Count	0	O
Ludwig	1	B-PER
zu	1	I-PER
Erbach	1	I-PER
Schönberg	1	E-PER
(	0	O
1792	0	O
1863	0	O
)	0	O
planted	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
linden	2	B-MISC
tree	2	E-MISC
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
called	0	O
''	0	O
Ludwigslinde	3	S-MISC
''	0	O
since	0	O
then	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
tall	0	O
tree	0	O
of	0	O
powerful	0	O
shape	0	O
and	0	O
widely	0	O
branched	0	O
canopy	0	O
.	0	O

From	0	O
the	0	O
bench	1	B-LOC
under	1	I-LOC
the	1	I-LOC
linden	1	I-LOC
tree	1	E-LOC
you	0	O
can	0	O
enjoy	0	O
a	0	O
wonderful	0	O
view	0	O
over	0	O
the	0	O
valley	2	S-LOC
to	0	O
the	0	O
mountains	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Starkenburg	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Knodenkopf	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
directional	0	O
point	0	O
Krehberg	6	S-LOC
,	0	O
Märkerwald	7	S-LOC
,	0	O
Hemsberg	8	S-LOC
,	0	O
Vetzersberg	9	S-LOC
,	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Rhine	10	B-LOC
plain	10	E-LOC
to	0	O
the	0	O
Palatinate	11	B-LOC
Forest	11	E-LOC
.	0	O

Right	0	O
next	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Ludwigslinde	1	S-LOC
''	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
Schönberger	2	S-MISC
''	0	O
Herrenwingert	3	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
used	0	O
to	0	O
belong	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Counts	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Erbach	1	I-ORG
Schönberg	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
today	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
owned	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
State	2	B-ORG
Winery	2	I-ORG
Bergstrasse	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

There	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
quite	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
people	0	O
Bergstrasseers	0	O
and	0	O
strangers	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
fallen	0	O
in	0	O
love	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
place	0	O
at	0	O
''	0	O
Ludwigslinde	1	S-LOC
''	0	O
and	0	O
''	0	O
Herrenwingert	2	S-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

REINHARD	1	B-PER
TREBER	1	E-PER

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Contacts	0	O
to	0	O
top	0	O
class	0	O
wind	0	O
players	0	O
EpiphaniaI	1	B-MISC
Kantorin	1	E-MISC
has	0	O
been	0	O
promoting	0	O
classical	0	O
music	0	O
and	0	O
new	2	B-MISC
music	2	E-MISC
for	0	O
14	0	O
years	0	O

NORTHERN	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
has	0	O
been	0	O
a	0	O
cantor	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
Protestant	0	O
Epiphany	0	O
congregation	0	O
in	0	O
Nordend	2	S-LOC
for	0	O
14	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

All	0	O
kinds	0	O
of	0	O
things	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
built	0	O
up	0	O
there	0	O
.	0	O

She	0	O
was	0	O
particularly	0	O
fond	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
last	0	O
concert	0	O
in	0	O
April.	0	O
''	0	O

That	0	O
's	0	O
when	0	O
I	0	O
noticed	0	O
what	0	O
an	0	O
excellent	0	O
choir	0	O
we	0	O
now	0	O
have.	0	O
''	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
difficult	0	O
romantic	0	O
a	1	B-MISC
cappella	1	I-MISC
movements	1	E-MISC
,	0	O
the	0	O
singers	0	O
would	0	O
have	0	O
reacted	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
smallest	0	O
instruction	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
she	0	O
only	0	O
has	0	O
words	0	O
of	0	O
praise	0	O
for	0	O
her	0	O
orchestra	0	O
.	0	O

Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
only	0	O
mentions	0	O
in	0	O
passing	0	O
that	0	O
such	0	O
achievements	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
fall	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
sky	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
be	0	O
achieved	0	O
through	0	O
continuous	0	O
,	0	O
tenacious	0	O
rehearsal	0	O
work	0	O
.	0	O

Twice	0	O
a	0	O
year	0	O
mostly	0	O
around	0	O
Easter	1	S-MISC
and	0	O
during	0	O
Advent	0	O
choir	2	B-ORG
and	2	I-ORG
orchestra	2	E-ORG
of	0	O
Epiphany	3	B-LOC
community	3	E-LOC
give	0	O
their	0	O
big	0	O
concerts	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
year	0	O
the	0	O
cantor	0	O
had	0	O
chosen	0	O
an	0	O
interesting	0	O
mixture	0	O
of	0	O
romantic	0	O
a	0	O
cappella	0	O
singing	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
,	0	O
unaccompanied	0	O
pieces	0	O
for	0	O
choir	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
orchestral	0	O
works	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
20th	0	O
century	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
program	0	O
with	0	O
music	0	O
Johann	1	B-PER
Sebastian	1	I-PER
Bachs	1	E-PER
is	0	O
planned	0	O
for	0	O
Advent	0	O
.	0	O

These	0	O
concerts	0	O
cost	0	O
the	0	O
community	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
:	0	O

Posters	0	O
are	0	O
stuck	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
advertising	1	B-LOC
pillars	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
and	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
heavy	0	O
advertising	0	O
on	0	O
handouts	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
newspapers	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
church	0	O
at	0	O
Holzhausenstrasse	1	S-LOC
is	0	O
then	0	O
usually	0	O
packed	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
other	0	O
,	0	O
less	0	O
lavishly	0	O
announced	0	O
events	0	O
are	0	O
almost	0	O
always	0	O
well	0	O
attended	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
matinee	0	O
with	0	O
organ	0	O
and	0	O
violin	0	O
music	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
March	0	O
met	0	O
with	0	O
astonishing	0	O
public	0	O
interest	0	O
,	0	O
even	0	O
though	0	O
the	0	O
program	0	O
was	0	O
n't	0	O
about	0	O
Bach	1	S-PER
,	0	O
Mozart	2	S-PER
or	0	O
Mendelssohn	3	S-PER
,	0	O
but	0	O
exclusively	0	O
music	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
20th	0	O
century.	0	O
''	0	O

We	0	O
have	0	O
our	0	O
regular	0	O
audience	0	O
by	0	O
now	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
says	0	O
Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
,	0	O
not	0	O
without	0	O
pride	0	O
in	0	O
view	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
lively	0	O
musical	0	O
activity	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
cantor	0	O
has	0	O
something	0	O
without	0	O
which	0	O
nothing	0	O
works	0	O
in	0	O
concert	0	O
:	0	O

Relationships	0	O
.	0	O

When	0	O
it	0	O
comes	0	O
to	0	O
difficult	0	O
choral	0	O
and	0	O
orchestral	0	O
works	0	O
,	0	O
top	0	O
class	0	O
winds	0	O
are	0	O
particularly	0	O
important	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
has	0	O
excellent	0	O
contacts	0	O
with	0	O
them	0	O
.	0	O

Most	0	O
of	0	O
them	0	O
work	0	O
in	0	O
Radio	1	B-ORG
Symphony	1	I-ORG
Orchestra	1	E-ORG
and	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
help	0	O
out	0	O
in	0	O
Epiphany	2	B-LOC
Church.	2	E-LOC
''	0	O

Many	0	O
people	0	O
enjoy	0	O
making	0	O
music	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
choir	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
also	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
appear	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
soloist.	0	O
''	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
unusual	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
cantor	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
her	0	O
own	0	O
string	0	O
orchestra	0	O
.	0	O

Usually	0	O
the	0	O
musicians	0	O
who	0	O
are	0	O
needed	0	O
are	0	O
bought	0	O
together	0	O
for	0	O
church	0	O
concerts	0	O
.	0	O

Or	0	O
you	0	O
can	0	O
hire	0	O
a	0	O
whole	0	O
professional	0	O
orchestra	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
expensive	0	O
and	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
guarantee	0	O
a	0	O
good	0	O
concert	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
long	0	O
time.	0	O
''	0	O

The	0	O
orchestra	0	O
rehearses	0	O
as	0	O
often	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
choir	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
relationships	0	O
are	0	O
much	0	O
closer	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
result	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
musicians	0	O
motivate	0	O
each	0	O
other	0	O
at	0	O
concerts.	0	O
''	0	O

Elke	3	B-PER
Mattmüller	3	E-PER
gladly	0	O
accepts	0	O
that	0	O
very	0	O
heavy	0	O
romantic	0	O
chunks	0	O
,	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
German	1	B-MISC
Requiem	1	E-MISC
by	0	O
Brahms	2	S-PER
,	0	O
can	0	O
hardly	0	O
be	0	O
managed	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
orchestra	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
consists	0	O
mainly	0	O
of	0	O
amateurs	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
cantor	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
mixed	0	O
relationship	0	O
with	0	O
Johann	1	B-PER
Sebastian	1	I-PER
Bach	1	E-PER
,	0	O
despite	0	O
the	0	O
concerts	0	O
on	0	O
September	0	O
20th	0	O
and	0	O
December	0	O
6th	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
which	0	O
mainly	0	O
works	0	O
by	0	O
Thomaskantor	2	S-MISC
are	0	O
played	0	O
.	0	O

What	0	O
bothers	0	O
them	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
oversaturation	0	O
.	0	O

Every	0	O
other	0	O
year	0	O
cantatas	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Christmas	1	B-MISC
Oratorio	1	E-MISC
?	0	O

That	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
too	0	O
boring	0	O
for	0	O
Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller.	1	E-PER
''	0	O

Many	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
even	0	O
know	0	O
that	0	O
Bach	1	S-PER
was	0	O
not	0	O
the	0	O
only	0	O
one	0	O
who	0	O
composed	0	O
good	0	O
and	0	O
interesting	0	O
music.	0	O
''	0	O

During	0	O
her	0	O
14	0	O
years	0	O
of	0	O
work	0	O
,	0	O
apart	0	O
from	0	O
Mozart	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
''	0	O
Requiem	0	O
''	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Schicksalslied	0	O
''	0	O
by	0	O
Johannes	2	B-PER
Brahms	2	E-PER
,	0	O
she	0	O
has	0	O
not	0	O
performed	0	O
any	0	O
work	0	O
twice.	0	O
''	0	O

At	0	O
least	0	O
I	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
suggest	0	O
to	0	O
people	0	O
how	0	O
wide	0	O
the	0	O
range	0	O
of	0	O
different	0	O
pieces	0	O
is.	0	O
''	0	O

For	0	O
them	0	O
,	0	O
music	0	O
history	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
end	0	O
with	0	O
Anton	1	B-PER
Bruckner	1	E-PER
either	0	O
.	0	O

You	0	O
are	0	O
very	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
modern	0	O
music	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
cantor	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
difficult	0	O
time	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
choir.	0	O
''	0	O

I	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
NeuI	1	B-MISC
music	1	I-MISC
fans	1	E-MISC
out	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
singers	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
everyone	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
open	0	O
minded	0	O
about	0	O
it.	0	O
''	0	O

As	0	O
an	0	O
organist	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
devotes	0	O
herself	0	O
extensively	0	O
to	0	O
modern	0	O
music	0	O
.	0	O

Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
conducts	0	O
a	0	O
brilliantly	0	O
trained	0	O
,	0	O
70	0	O
member	0	O
church	0	O
choir	0	O
and	0	O
its	0	O
own	0	O
orchestra	0	O
,	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
free	0	O
hand	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
planning	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
her	0	O
church	0	O
music	0	O
budget	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
cause	0	O
her	0	O
any	0	O
worries	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
moment	0	O
.	0	O

Do	0	O
you	0	O
have	0	O
any	0	O
wishes	0	O
at	0	O
all	0	O
?	0	O
''	0	O

A	0	O
new	0	O
,	0	O
modern	0	O
organ	0	O
''	0	O
that	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
what	0	O
she	0	O
is	0	O
still	0	O
missing	0	O
for	0	O
musical	0	O
happiness	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
relatively	0	O
small	0	O
instrument	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
1950s	0	O
has	0	O
only	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
registers	0	O
and	0	O
outdated	0	O
technology.	0	O
''	0	O

The	0	O
new	0	O
intonation	0	O
two	0	O
years	0	O
ago	0	O
brought	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
in	0	O
terms	0	O
of	0	O
sound.	0	O
''	0	O

But	0	O
she	0	O
has	0	O
no	0	O
illusions	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
is	0	O
simply	0	O
no	0	O
money	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
organ	0	O
.	0	O

Elke	1	B-PER
Mattmüller	1	E-PER
has	0	O
built	0	O
up	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
in	0	O
Nordend	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
therefore	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
waste	0	O
any	0	O
thought	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
career	0	O
change.	0	O
''	0	O

In	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
church	0	O
I	0	O
would	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
start	0	O
all	0	O
over	0	O
again	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
bottom.	0	O
''	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O

Rehearsals	0	O
+	0	O
meetings	0	O

Accordion	1	B-ORG
Music	1	I-ORG
Association	1	I-ORG
''	1	I-ORG
Heiterkeit	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
Griesheim	2	S-LOC
:	0	O

Classes	0	O
for	0	O
accordion	0	O
students	0	O
are	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
2pm	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
Bürgerhaus	1	B-LOC
Griesheim	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Schwarzerlenweg	2	S-LOC
57	0	O
(	0	O
club	0	O
room	0	O
3	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
the	0	O
association	0	O
's	0	O
orchestra	0	O
rehearses	0	O
in	0	O
Club	1	B-LOC
Room	1	I-LOC
1	1	E-LOC
in	0	O
Griesheim	2	S-LOC
every	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
from	0	O
7	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
8.30	0	O
p.m	0	O
.	0	O

Bockenheim	1	B-ORG
Seniors	1	I-ORG
Working	1	I-ORG
Group	1	E-ORG
:	0	O

Members	0	O
meeting	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
club	0	O
afternoon	0	O
every	0	O
first	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
month	0	O
(	0	O
3	0	O
p.m.	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
social	0	O
station	0	O
at	0	O
Rohmerplatz	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
ground	2	B-LOC
floor	2	E-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

Athletics	1	B-ORG
Sports	1	I-ORG
Club	1	E-ORG
1990	0	O
Griesheim	2	S-LOC
:	0	O

Sports	0	O
badge	0	O
preparation	0	O
and	0	O
acceptance	0	O
in	0	O
weightlifting	0	O
after	0	O
prior	0	O
registration	0	O
every	0	O
Monday	0	O
,	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
and	0	O
Friday	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
6	0	O
p.m.	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
Griesheimer	1	B-LOC
Sporthalle	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Linkstraße	2	S-LOC
86	0	O
88	0	O
.	0	O

Contact	0	O
:	0	O

Klaus	1	B-PER
Samer	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC

37	0	O
19	0	O
74	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
Hugo	1	B-PER
Zingel	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC

38	0	O
42	0	O
27	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Bockenheimer	1	B-ORG
Male	1	I-ORG
Choir	1	E-ORG
1837	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
active	0	O
members	0	O
meet	0	O
for	0	O
choir	0	O
rehearsal	0	O
every	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
at	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
community	0	O
hall	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
evangelical	0	O
St.	1	B-LOC
Jakobskirche	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Grempstraße	2	S-LOC
41	0	O
.	0	O

Women	0	O
and	0	O
men	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
singing	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
community	0	O
can	0	O
take	0	O
part	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
rehearsal	0	O
without	0	O
obligation	0	O
.	0	O

Chairman	0	O
Wolfgang	1	B-PER
Ochs	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	2	B-LOC
.	2	E-LOC

76	0	O
67	0	O
43	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Bockenheimer	1	B-LOC
zither	1	I-LOC
wreath	1	E-LOC
1886	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
active	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
association	0	O
rehearse	0	O
every	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Bürgerertreff	1	B-LOC
Bockenheim	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
,	0	O
Schwälmer	2	B-LOC
Straße	2	E-LOC
28	0	O
.	0	O

Those	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
zither	1	B-LOC
game	1	E-LOC
will	0	O
receive	0	O
more	0	O
information	0	O
from	0	O
Rudi	2	B-PER
May	2	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

77	0	O
15	0	O
43	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Carrier	1	B-ORG
pigeon	1	I-ORG
club	1	I-ORG
''	1	I-ORG
Sport	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
Frankfurt	2	S-LOC
:	0	O

The	0	O
members	0	O
meet	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
club	0	O
evening	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
at	0	O
8	0	O
pm	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
restaurant	0	O
''	0	O
Zur	1	B-LOC
Krone	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
in	0	O
Seckbach	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Wilhelmshöher	3	B-LOC
Straße	3	E-LOC
165	0	O
.	0	O

Guests	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
carrier	1	B-MISC
pigeon	1	I-MISC
sport	1	E-MISC
are	0	O
welcome	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
BUND	1	B-ORG
local	1	I-ORG
association	1	E-ORG
2/9	0	O
has	0	O
association	0	O
meeting	0	O
every	0	O
third	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
month	0	O
at	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
Bürgerertreff	2	B-LOC
Bockenheim	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
Schwälmer	3	B-LOC
Straße	3	E-LOC
28	0	O
.	0	O

Choir	1	B-ORG
community	1	I-ORG
1857	1	I-ORG
Griesheim	1	E-ORG
:	0	O

The	0	O
active	0	O
members	0	O
meet	0	O
for	0	O
choir	0	O
rehearsals	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
(	0	O
7.45pm	0	O
to	0	O
9.15pm	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
Bürgerhaus	1	B-LOC
Griesheim	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Schwarzerlenweg	2	S-LOC
57	0	O
(	0	O
club	0	O
room	0	O
2	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Men	0	O
and	0	O
women	0	O
are	0	O
still	0	O
accepted	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
choir	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
more	0	O
information	0	O
,	0	O
see	0	O
Horst	1	B-PER
Seip	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

38	0	O
20	0	O
97	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

DLRG	1	B-ORG
Frankfurt	1	E-ORG
:	0	O

The	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
diving	0	O
group	0	O
meet	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
at	0	O
7.30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
for	0	O
training	0	O
in	0	O
Hallenbad	1	B-LOC
Sachsenhausen	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Textorstraße	2	S-LOC
42	0	O
.	0	O

Willi	1	B-PER
Vogt	1	I-PER
Tel	1	E-PER
provides	0	O
information	0	O
on	0	O
rescue	0	O
diver	0	O
training	0	O
.	0	O

58	0	O
66	0	O
23	0	O
.	0	O

Information	0	O
can	0	O
also	0	O
be	0	O
obtained	0	O
every	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
from	0	O
3	0	O
p.m.	0	O
to	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
DLRG	1	B-ORG
office	1	E-ORG
Tel	0	O
.	0	O

28	0	O
05	0	O
12	0	O
.	0	O

FKV	1	S-ORG
1911	0	O
and	0	O
Maagard	2	S-LOC
:	0	O

The	0	O
Frankfurter	1	B-ORG
Karnevalverein	1	I-ORG
1911	1	E-ORG
dance	0	O
corps	0	O
trains	0	O
every	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
,	0	O
7	0	O
to	0	O
8.30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
(	0	O
Minigarde	2	S-ORG
from	0	O
6	0	O
to	0	O
7	0	O
p.m.	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
club	0	O
house	0	O
,	0	O
Petterweilstraße	3	S-LOC
69	0	O
in	0	O
Bornheim	4	S-LOC
(	0	O
bunker	5	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

Girls	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
dancing	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
community	0	O
are	0	O
accepted	0	O
.	0	O

Contact	0	O
:	0	O

Manuela	1	B-PER
Koch	1	E-PER
,	0	O
Tel	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

0	0	O
61	0	O
87/34	0	O
56	0	O
.	0	O

Frankfurt	1	B-ORG
Canoe	1	I-ORG
Association	1	E-ORG
1913	0	O
:	0	O

The	0	O
association	0	O
invites	0	O
you	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
meeting	0	O
every	0	O
Thursday	0	O
,	0	O
from	0	O
6	0	O
p.m.	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Friedel	1	B-LOC
Construction	1	I-LOC
House	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
boathouse	0	O
at	0	O
Friedensbrücke	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

More	0	O
information	0	O
is	0	O
available	0	O
from	0	O
press	0	O
officer	0	O
Eckard	1	B-PER
Dünnemann	1	E-PER
on	0	O
Tel	0	O
.	0	O

88	0	O
98	0	O
81	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
6	0	O
p.m.	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Frankfurt	1	B-ORG
Carnival	1	I-ORG
Society	1	I-ORG
Red	1	I-ORG
White	1	E-ORG
:	0	O

The	0	O
''	0	O
regiment	0	O
daughters	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
association	0	O
train	0	O
every	0	O
Monday	0	O
at	0	O
8	0	O
pm	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Bürgerertreff	1	B-LOC
Bockenheim	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
in	0	O
Schwälmer	2	B-LOC
Straße	2	E-LOC
28	0	O
.	0	O

Frankfurter	1	B-ORG
Liedertafel	1	E-ORG
1827	0	O
:	0	O

For	0	O
the	0	O
choir	0	O
rehearsal	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
active	0	O
meet	0	O
every	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
(	0	O
7.45pm	0	O
to	0	O
9.45pm	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Bürgerertreff	1	B-LOC
Philanthropin	1	E-LOC
''	0	O
,	0	O
Hebelstraße	2	S-LOC
17	0	O
.	0	O

Men	0	O
and	0	O
women	0	O
who	0	O
are	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
singing	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
community	0	O
are	0	O
accepted	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
choir	0	O
.	0	O

Contact	0	O
:	0	O

Chairman	0	O
Hans	1	B-PER
Riebartsch	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Tel	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

31	0	O
34	0	O
61	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Frankfurter	1	B-ORG
Musikverein	1	E-ORG
:	0	O

The	0	O
minstrels	0	O
meet	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
orchestra	0	O
rehearsal	0	O
on	0	O
Thursdays	0	O
at	0	O
8	0	O
p.m.	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Josefsklause	1	S-LOC
''	0	O
in	0	O
Bornheim	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Berger	3	B-LOC
Straße	3	E-LOC
133	0	O
.	0	O
