-DOCSTART-	0	O
The	0	O
text	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
judgment	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
available	0	O
in	0	O
writing	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
message	0	O
was	0	O
already	0	O
published	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
communication	0	O
agency	0	O
that	0	O
hired	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

In	0	O
'81	0	O
the	0	O
then	0	O
Flemish	1	S-MISC
government	0	O
regularizes	0	O
the	0	O
situation	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
BPA	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
had	0	O
drawn	0	O
up	0	O
at	0	O
its	0	O
own	0	O
expense	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

Today	0	O
,	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
in	0	O
order	0	O
with	0	O
all	0	O
permits	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
BPA	0	O
with	0	O
which	0	O
they	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
obtained	0	O
was	0	O
controversial	0	O
because	0	O
business	0	O
manager	0	O
Christiane	2	B-PER
Vandenbussche	2	E-PER
her	0	O
position	0	O
as	0	O
alderman	0	O
of	0	O
...	0	O

At	0	O
first	0	O
instance	0	O
Vandenbussche	1	S-PER
was	0	O
convicted	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
early	0	O
1990s	0	O
for	0	O
conflict	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
but	0	O
later	0	O
acquitted	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
appeals	0	O
court	0	O
in	0	O
Ghent	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

SP	1	S-ORG
has	0	O
a	0	O
hard	0	O
time	0	O
(	0	O
Eric	2	S-PER
,	0	O
sd	0	O
)	0	O
Derycke	3	S-PER
wants	0	O
to	0	O
approve	0	O
BPA	4	S-MISC
on	0	O
condition	0	O
that	0	O
BPA	0	O
'	0	O
De	5	B-LOC
Hoogte	5	E-LOC
'	0	O
is	0	O
accepted	0	O
limitedly	0	O
(	0	O
mayor	0	O
of	0	O
Moorslede	6	S-LOC
Walter	7	B-PER
Ghekiere	7	E-PER
will	0	O
make	0	O
a	0	O
proposal	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Insufficient	0	O
to	0	O
pronounce	0	O
a	0	O
heavy	0	O
sentence	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
court	0	O
now	0	O
attaches	0	O
no	0	O
penalty	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
guilt	0	O
it	0	O
finds	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
quickly	0	O
grew	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
real	0	O
garden	0	O
center	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

Many	0	O
more	0	O
things	0	O
are	0	O
sold	0	O
than	0	O
you	0	O
would	0	O
expect	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
plant	0	O
nursery	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
abundantly	0	O
clear	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
fax	0	O
that	0	O
her	0	O
lawyer	0	O
wrote	0	O
to	0	O
her	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
and	0	O
which	0	O
was	0	O
confiscated	0	O
during	0	O
a	0	O
search	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
file	0	O
dates	0	O
back	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
late	0	O
1980s	0	O
.	0	O

Sybille	1	B-PER
Decoo	1	E-PER

allegedly	0	O
misused	0	O
Spatial	1	B-MISC
Planning	1	E-MISC
to	0	O
obtain	0	O
the	0	O
BPA	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
only	0	O
evidence	0	O
left	0	O
to	0	O
convict	0	O
Vandenbussche	1	S-PER
for	0	O
'interesting	0	O
'	0	O
was	0	O
her	0	O
presence	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
council	0	O
of	0	O
aldermen	0	O
when	0	O
Floralux	2	B-MISC
dossier	2	E-MISC
was	0	O
discussed	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
1998	0	O
the	0	O
Flemish	1	S-MISC
government	0	O
will	0	O
finalize	0	O
this	0	O
regularization	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
regional	0	O
plan	0	O
amendment	0	O
.	0	O

Guilt	0	O
but	0	O
no	0	O
fine	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

He	0	O
himself	0	O
dismissed	0	O
this	0	O
as	0	O
''	0	O
nonsense	0	O
and	0	O
apekool	0	O
of	0	O
quatongues	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

Figs	1	S-LOC
after	0	O
Easter	2	S-MISC
,	0	O
or	0	O
so	0	O
the	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
seems	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
thought	0	O
.	0	O

Antwerp	1	S-LOC
/	0	O
Brussels	2	S-LOC

Locally	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
suspected	0	O
that	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
financed	0	O
the	0	O
electoral	0	O
campaigns	0	O
of	0	O
Luc	2	B-PER
Martens	2	E-PER
,	0	O
which	0	O
still	0	O
drew	0	O
''	0	O
attention	0	O
''	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
matter	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
previous	0	O
government	0	O
.	0	O

Life	1	S-ORG

Vandenbussche	1	S-PER
itself	0	O
decided	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
court	0	O
wanted	0	O
to	0	O
condemn	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
political	0	O
mores	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

The	0	O
Court	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Cassation	1	E-ORG
broke	0	O
the	0	O
judgment	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
redone	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
appeals	0	O
court	0	O
of	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
essence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
judgment	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
Antwerp	1	S-LOC
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
passed	0	O
on	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
controversial	0	O
garden	0	O
center	0	O
Floralux	2	S-ORG
from	0	O
Moorslede	3	B-LOC
Dadizele	3	E-LOC
.	0	O

Business	0	O
manager	0	O
Christiane	1	B-PER
Vandenbussche	1	E-PER
is	0	O
found	0	O
guilty	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
conflict	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
(	0	O
'interest	0	O
interests	0	O
'	0	O
in	0	O
legal	0	O
language	0	O
)	0	O
but	0	O
receives	0	O
no	0	O
punishment	0	O
because	0	O
a	0	O
punishment	0	O
would	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
be	0	O
meaningful	0	O
after	0	O
all	0	O
these	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
certainly	0	O
the	0	O
interpretation	0	O
given	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
judgment	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
vicinity	0	O
of	0	O
Floralux	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
see	0	O
page	0	O
1	0	O
)	0	O
:	0	O
that	0	O
a	0	O
'	0	O
new	0	O
political	0	O
culture	0	O
'	0	O
has	0	O
dawned	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
political	0	O
mores	0	O
were	0	O
indeed	0	O
objectionable	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
fined	0	O
with	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
case	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
closure	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
case	0	O
.	0	O

What	0	O
went	0	O
on	0	O
for	0	O
years	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
controversial	0	O
'	0	O
CVP	1	B-ORG
file	1	E-ORG
'	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
given	0	O
the	0	O
cachet	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
old	0	O
cow	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
canal	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
court	0	O
decision	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
order	0	O
to	0	O
survive	0	O
,	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
wants	0	O
the	0	O
agricultural	0	O
land	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
converted	0	O
into	0	O
an	0	O
SME	0	O
zone	0	O
.	0	O

'Court	0	O
condemned	0	O
political	0	O
mores	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
'	0	O

The	0	O
lawyer	0	O
writes	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
(	0	O
...	0	O
)	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
then	0	O
clear	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
(	0	O
BPA	0	O
,	0	O
sd	0	O
)	0	O
was	0	O
only	0	O
realized	0	O
for	0	O
private	0	O
purposes	0	O
,	0	O
namely	0	O
for	0	O
your	0	O
company	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
college	0	O
of	0	O
aldermen	0	O
acts	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
pacesetter	0	O
for	0	O
this	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Nevertheless	0	O
,	0	O
she	0	O
insisted	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
VRT	1	B-ORG
radio	1	E-ORG
that	0	O
she	0	O
had	0	O
''	0	O
not	0	O
done	0	O
anything	0	O
wrong	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

It	0	O
also	0	O
appears	0	O
that	0	O
consultations	0	O
took	0	O
place	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
liberal	0	O
party	0	O
(	0	O
then	0	O
still	0	O
PVV	1	S-ORG
)	0	O
and	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
SP	2	S-ORG
:	0	O
''	0	O
Waltniel	3	S-PER
(	0	O
PVV	4	S-ORG
,	0	O
sd	0	O
)	0	O
is	0	O
for	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
Delcroix	1	S-LOC
concluded	0	O
:	0	O
''	0	O
Will	0	O
come	0	O
through	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

This	0	O
context	0	O
has	0	O
ensured	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
file	0	O
has	0	O
always	0	O
benefited	0	O
from	0	O
an	0	O
atmosphere	0	O
of	0	O
party	0	O
financing	0	O
in	0	O
exchange	0	O
for	0	O
regularization	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

Dossier	0	O
always	0	O
associated	0	O
with	0	O
party	0	O
financing	0	O
in	0	O
exchange	0	O
for	0	O
regularization	0	O

Floralux	1	S-ORG
obtains	0	O
a	0	O
permit	0	O
to	0	O
set	0	O
up	0	O
a	0	O
plant	0	O
nursery	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

The	0	O
Antwerp	1	S-LOC
court	0	O
rejected	0	O
the	0	O
document	0	O
as	0	O
evidence	0	O
but	0	O
did	0	O
read	0	O
it	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
hearing	0	O
.	0	O

What	0	O
those	0	O
political	0	O
mores	0	O
were	0	O
,	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
deduced	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Atoma	1	B-MISC
notebooks	1	E-MISC
that	0	O
Leo	2	B-PER
Delcroix	2	E-PER
kept	0	O
when	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
still	0	O
CVP	3	B-ORG
secretary	3	E-ORG
.	0	O

section	0	O

Sybille	1	B-PER
Decoo	1	E-PER

Business	0	O
manager	0	O
Floralux	1	S-PER
insists	0	O
she	0	O
did	0	O
nothing	0	O
wrong	0	O

About	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
it	0	O
said	0	O
:	0	O
''	0	O
They	0	O
want	0	O
regularization	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Verberckmoes	1	S-PER
is	0	O
a	0	O
former	0	O
Catholic	0	O
dissident	0	O
who	0	O
joined	0	O
the	0	O
liberal	0	O
ranks	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
enlargement	0	O
candidate	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
PVV	2	S-ORG
was	0	O
founded	0	O
and	0	O
almost	0	O
immediately	0	O
became	0	O
a	0	O
member	0	O
of	0	O
parliament	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Liberal	0	O
Minister	0	O
of	0	O
Justice	1	S-ORG
Marc	2	B-PER
Verwilghen	2	E-PER
is	0	O
not	0	O
a	0	O
candidate	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
local	0	O
VLD	3	B-ORG
list	3	E-ORG
in	0	O
the	0	O
upcoming	0	O
municipal	0	O
elections	0	O
in	0	O
Dendermonde	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

A	0	O
councilor	0	O
of	0	O
Inzet	1	S-LOC
:	0	O
''	0	O
The	0	O
intention	0	O
was	0	O
that	0	O
we	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
group	0	O
would	0	O
form	0	O
a	0	O
cartel	0	O
list	0	O
that	0	O
would	0	O
then	0	O
ask	0	O
the	0	O
voter	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
mandate	0	O
.	0	O

Rudy	1	B-PER
De	1	I-PER
Brandt	1	E-PER
admits	0	O
that	0	O
other	0	O
motives	0	O
may	0	O
have	0	O
played	0	O
a	0	O
major	0	O
role	0	O
as	0	O
well	0	O
.	0	O

Willy	1	B-PER
Van	1	I-PER
Damme	1	E-PER

''	0	O
He	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
commit	0	O
voter	0	O
fraud	0	O
and	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
candidate	0	O
and	0	O
then	0	O
not	0	O
sit	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
council	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
final	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Within	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	1	S-ORG
in	0	O
Dendermonde	2	S-LOC
there	0	O
is	0	O
great	0	O
dismay	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
proposal	0	O
had	0	O
reportedly	0	O
grown	0	O
quite	0	O
spontaneously	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
led	0	O
by	0	O
Mayor	0	O
Norbert	1	B-PER
De	1	I-PER
Batselier	1	E-PER
(	0	O
SP	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
local	0	O
VLD	1	B-ORG
chairman	1	E-ORG
Rudy	2	B-PER
De	2	I-PER
Brandt	2	E-PER
,	0	O
his	0	O
decision	0	O
is	0	O
irrevocable	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
is	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
cumulation	0	O
of	0	O
mandates	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
says	0	O
De	1	B-PER
Brandt	1	E-PER
.	0	O

For	0	O
example	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
the	0	O
proposal	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
joint	0	O
list	0	O
of	0	O
Stake	0	O
,	0	O
with	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	1	S-ORG
in	0	O
Dendermonde	2	S-LOC
forms	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
and	0	O
which	0	O
consists	0	O
of	0	O
SP	3	B-ORG
members	3	E-ORG
,	0	O
VU	4	B-ORG
members	4	E-ORG
and	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
independents	0	O
.	0	O

Marc	1	B-PER
Verwilghen	1	E-PER
no	0	O
candidate	0	O
in	0	O
Dendermonde	2	S-LOC

For	0	O
them	0	O
Marc	1	B-PER
Verwilghen	1	E-PER
is	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Frans	3	B-PER
Verberckmoes	3	E-PER
the	0	O
old	0	O
political	0	O
culture	0	O
detested	0	O
by	0	O
them	0	O
.	0	O

Willy	1	B-PER
Van	1	I-PER
Damme	1	E-PER

Verwilghen	1	S-PER
Fails	0	O
To	0	O
Convince	0	O
Local	0	O
VLD	2	S-ORG
To	0	O
Cartel	0	O
With	0	O
Bet	0	O
List	0	O
Of	0	O
De	3	B-ORG
Batselier	3	E-ORG

author	0	O

†	0	O

''	0	O
This	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
PVV	1	S-ORG
from	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
or	0	O
even	0	O
worse	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
an	0	O
VLD	2	B-ORG
member	2	E-ORG
from	0	O
the	0	O
vicinity	0	O
of	0	O
Verwilghen	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

VLD	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
currently	0	O
only	0	O
has	0	O
four	0	O
seats	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
council	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
therefore	0	O
in	0	O
danger	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
debacle	0	O
.	0	O

Verwilghen	1	S-PER
also	0	O
gave	0	O
that	0	O
official	0	O
reason	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
press	0	O
release	0	O
last	0	O
night	0	O
.	0	O

Dendermonde	1	S-ORG

According	0	O
to	0	O
several	0	O
sources	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
also	0	O
had	0	O
the	0	O
support	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
top	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
national	0	O
VLD	1	S-ORG
and	0	O
was	0	O
mainly	0	O
supported	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
Dendermondse	2	B-ORG
VLD	2	E-ORG
by	0	O
Marc	3	B-PER
Verwilghen	3	E-PER
.	0	O

Now	0	O
the	0	O
leadership	0	O
will	0	O
go	0	O
between	0	O
Hilde	1	B-PER
Dierickx	1	E-PER
and	0	O
ships	0	O
for	0	O
Finance	2	S-ORG
Marcel	3	B-PER
Borms	3	E-PER
.	0	O

Life	1	S-ORG

page	0	O

Some	0	O
may	0	O
now	0	O
drop	0	O
out	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

He	0	O
left	0	O
active	0	O
politics	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
years	0	O
ago	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
remains	0	O
an	0	O
influential	0	O
figure	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
local	0	O
liberal	0	O
party	0	O
,	0	O
including	0	O
through	0	O
his	0	O
son	0	O
Kristian	1	B-PER
Verberckmoes	1	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
councilor	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
local	0	O
branch	0	O
rejected	0	O
the	0	O
proposal	0	O
.	0	O

Some	0	O
liberals	0	O
have	0	O
already	0	O
taken	0	O
or	0	O
are	0	O
planning	0	O
to	0	O
move	0	O
towards	0	O
Commitment	1	S-MISC
.	0	O

This	0	O
(	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
circles	0	O
within	0	O
and	0	O
outside	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	1	S-ORG
)	0	O
was	0	O
mainly	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
initiative	0	O
of	0	O
Frans	2	B-PER
Verberckmoes	2	E-PER
,	0	O
former	0	O
VLD	0	O
representative	0	O
for	0	O
Dendermonde	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

†	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

From	0	O
our	0	O
employee	0	O

edition	0	O

Robert	1	B-PER
Verwilghen	1	E-PER
,	0	O
father	0	O
of	0	O
Marc	2	S-PER
,	0	O
grabbed	0	O
a	0	O
seat	0	O
next	0	O
to	0	O
him	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
insiders	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
quarrel	0	O
between	0	O
Marc	1	B-PER
Verwilghen	1	E-PER
and	0	O
its	0	O
predecessor	0	O
Frans	2	B-PER
Verberckmoes	2	E-PER
plays	0	O
a	0	O
major	0	O
role	0	O
here	0	O
.	0	O

Rudy	1	B-PER
De	1	I-PER
Brandt	1	E-PER
:	0	O
''	0	O
Indeed	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
people	0	O
had	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
applied	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
elections	0	O
,	0	O
pending	0	O
what	0	O
Marc	2	B-PER
Verwilghen	2	E-PER
would	0	O
do	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

publication	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Parents	0	O
who	0	O
were	0	O
lucky	0	O
enough	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
their	0	O
child	0	O
released	0	O
are	0	O
allowed	0	O
to	0	O
go	0	O
home	0	O
under	0	O
police	0	O
escort	0	O
.	0	O

Thank	1	B-PER
God	1	I-PER
.	1	E-PER
thank	0	O
you	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
she	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
little	0	O
sick	0	O
.	0	O

Distraught	0	O
parents	0	O
wait	0	O
helplessly	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
denouement	0	O
of	0	O
hostage	0	O
drama	0	O

The	0	O
child	0	O
is	0	O
barely	0	O
three	0	O
.	0	O

We	0	O
know	0	O
us	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
village	0	O
with	0	O
barely	0	O
2,300	0	O
inhabitants	0	O
.	0	O

'Dads	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
hurt	0	O
children	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
say	0	O
'	0	O

Dads	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
hurt	0	O
children	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
say	0	O
.	0	O

Cathy	1	B-PER
Galle	1	E-PER

Every	0	O
year	0	O
the	0	O
village	0	O
is	0	O
overrun	0	O
with	0	O
all	0	O
kinds	0	O
of	0	O
people	0	O
,	0	O
especially	0	O
tourists	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
come	0	O
to	0	O
walk	0	O
and	0	O
cycle	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
beautiful	0	O
surroundings	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
parents	0	O
also	0	O
receive	0	O
a	0	O
visit	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Portuguese	1	S-MISC
and	0	O
French	2	S-MISC
ambassador	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
representative	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Belgian	3	S-MISC
government	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

Colas	1	S-PER
:	0	O
''	0	O
A	0	O
child	0	O
of	0	O
that	0	O
age	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
really	0	O
realize	0	O
what	0	O
is	0	O
happening	0	O
to	0	O
him	0	O
yet	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
neighbor	0	O
's	0	O
daughter	0	O
is	0	O
there	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Cathy	1	B-PER
Galle	1	E-PER

According	0	O
to	0	O
law	0	O
enforcement	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
children	0	O
are	0	O
doing	0	O
fine	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
hostage	0	O
takers	0	O
have	0	O
never	0	O
had	0	O
them	0	O
.	0	O

My	0	O
daughter	0	O
kept	0	O
her	0	O
at	0	O
home	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

†	0	O

Shortly	0	O
after	0	O
seven	0	O
o'clock	0	O
suddenly	0	O
redemption	0	O
came	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

Every	0	O
now	0	O
and	0	O
then	0	O
applause	0	O
is	0	O
heard	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
cultural	0	O
center	0	O
.	0	O

They	0	O
have	0	O
slept	0	O
well	0	O
and	0	O
are	0	O
fed	0	O
on	0	O
time	0	O
.	0	O

Who	0	O
does	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
thing	0	O
?	0	O

But	0	O
nobody	0	O
knows	0	O
what	0	O
will	0	O
happen	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
worst	0	O
part	0	O
is	0	O
when	0	O
they	0	O
come	0	O
and	0	O
say	0	O
that	0	O
children	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
released	0	O
only	0	O
to	0	O
hear	0	O
that	0	O
your	0	O
child	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
there	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Then	0	O
you	0	O
just	0	O
die	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
respect	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
in	0	O
question	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
father	0	O
himself	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
entire	0	O
neighborhood	0	O
around	0	O
the	0	O
crèche	0	O
is	0	O
hermetically	0	O
sealed	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
course	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
afternoon	0	O
the	0	O
atmosphere	0	O
becomes	0	O
more	0	O
grim	0	O
.	0	O

Wasserbillig	1	S-LOC
is	0	O
in	0	O
fact	0	O
a	0	O
melting	0	O
pot	0	O
where	0	O
Portuguese	2	S-MISC
,	0	O
Italian	3	S-MISC
,	0	O
Polish	4	S-MISC
,	0	O
German	5	S-MISC
and	0	O
French	6	S-MISC
immigrants	0	O
once	0	O
who	0	O
came	0	O
here	0	O
to	0	O
work	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
steel	0	O
and	0	O
tire	0	O
industry	0	O
live	0	O
peacefully	0	O
next	0	O
to	0	O
each	0	O
other	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
residents	0	O
of	0	O
Wasserbillig	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
a	0	O
small	0	O
idyllic	0	O
Luxembourgish	2	S-MISC
village	0	O
,	0	O
glued	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
German	3	S-MISC
border	0	O
,	0	O
reacted	0	O
with	0	O
shock	0	O
.	0	O

After	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
shots	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
hostage	0	O
situation	0	O
was	0	O
over	0	O
.	0	O

Every	0	O
now	0	O
and	0	O
then	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
also	0	O
visited	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
circus	0	O
or	0	O
fair	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
few	0	O
days	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
municipal	0	O
nursery	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Rue	1	B-LOC
du	1	I-LOC
Bocksberg	1	E-LOC
is	0	O
completely	0	O
surrounded	0	O
by	0	O
special	0	O
intervention	0	O
troops	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Luxembourg	2	S-MISC
,	0	O
German	3	S-MISC
and	0	O
French	4	S-MISC
police	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

edition	0	O

''	0	O
Lots	0	O
of	0	O
distraught	0	O
tearful	0	O
faces	0	O
.	0	O

Everyone	0	O
is	0	O
getting	0	O
ready	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
second	0	O
scary	0	O
night	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
elderly	0	O
lady	0	O
looks	0	O
despairingly	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
white	0	O
building	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
distance	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

Some	0	O
parents	0	O
panic	0	O
and	0	O
fear	0	O
the	0	O
worst	0	O
,	0	O
others	0	O
try	0	O
to	0	O
keep	0	O
their	0	O
spirits	0	O
up	0	O
.	0	O

Let	0	O
's	0	O
hope	0	O
'they	0	O
'	0	O
are	0	O
right	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
describes	0	O
the	0	O
atmosphere	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
cultural	0	O
center	0	O
as	0	O
dramatic	0	O
.	0	O

These	0	O
are	0	O
defenseless	0	O
toddlers	0	O
and	0	O
preschoolers	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

page	0	O

author	0	O

†	0	O

The	0	O
industry	0	O
left	0	O
about	0	O
ten	0	O
years	0	O
ago	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
immigrants	0	O
stayed	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
large	0	O
bags	0	O
under	0	O
the	0	O
eyes	0	O
betray	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
a	0	O
sleepless	0	O
night	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
a	0	O
moment	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
worst	0	O
is	0	O
feared	0	O
when	0	O
news	0	O
comes	0	O
in	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
hostage	0	O
taker	0	O
has	0	O
brought	0	O
food	0	O
and	0	O
drink	0	O
for	0	O
three	0	O
days	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
was	0	O
glued	0	O
to	0	O
my	0	O
radio	0	O
.	0	O

Sad	0	O
because	0	O
a	0	O
niece	0	O
or	0	O
boyfriend	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
child	0	O
is	0	O
there	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

''	0	O
My	0	O
granddaughter	0	O
escaped	0	O
death	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
woman	0	O
sighs	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
young	0	O
man	0	O
sighs	0	O
deeply	0	O
.	0	O

From	0	O
our	0	O
reporter	0	O
on	0	O
site	0	O

†	0	O

Wasserbillig	0	O

Outside	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
about	0	O
fifty	0	O
villagers	0	O
who	0	O
wanted	0	O
to	0	O
support	0	O
the	0	O
affected	0	O
parents	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
route	1	B-LOC
du	1	I-LOC
Luxembourg	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
street	0	O
in	0	O
front	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
town	0	O
hall	0	O
,	0	O
was	0	O
transformed	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
boulevard	0	O
yesterday	0	O
,	0	O
along	0	O
which	0	O
hundreds	0	O
of	0	O
disaster	0	O
tourists	0	O
strolled	0	O
,	0	O
looking	0	O
at	0	O
jet	0	O
cars	0	O
(	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
twenty	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
press	0	O
people	0	O
(	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
a	0	O
hundred	0	O
)	0	O
instead	0	O
of	0	O
shop	0	O
windows	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
parents	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
kidnapped	0	O
children	0	O
are	0	O
taken	0	O
care	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
hundred	0	O
meters	0	O
further	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
cultural	0	O
center	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
ghost	0	O
,	0	O
on	0	O
what	0	O
could	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
a	0	O
beautiful	0	O
summer	0	O
vacation	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
1	0	O
&	0	O
amp	0	O
;	0	O
3	0	O
)	0	O

The	0	O
hostage	0	O
taker	0	O
starts	0	O
to	0	O
get	0	O
nervous	0	O
because	0	O
his	0	O
demands	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
met	0	O
soon	0	O
enough	0	O
.	0	O

Fortunately	0	O
their	0	O
child	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
hostages	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
parents	0	O
are	0	O
kept	0	O
informed	0	O
via	0	O
the	0	O
psychologists	0	O
.	0	O

Ramotti	1	S-PER
is	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
few	0	O
parents	0	O
who	0	O
still	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
say	0	O
something	0	O
.	0	O

Fatigue	0	O
is	0	O
also	0	O
taking	0	O
its	0	O
toll	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
General	1	S-ORG

And	0	O
that	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
happen	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
democracy	0	O
or…	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
rare	0	O
occasions	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
Belgian	1	S-MISC
monarchs	0	O
acted	0	O
headstrong	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
did	0	O
so	0	O
when	0	O
they	0	O
saw	0	O
their	0	O
own	0	O
position	0	O
in	0	O
jeopardy	0	O
:	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
royal	0	O
question	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
independence	0	O
of	0	O
Congo	2	S-LOC
or	0	O
the	0	O
state	0	O
reform	0	O
.	0	O

Not	0	O
in	0	O
Belgium	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
not	0	O
in	0	O
Laeken	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

page	0	O

He	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
allowed	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
an	0	O
opinion	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
own	0	O
and	0	O
all	0	O
his	0	O
actions	0	O
are	0	O
covered	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
government	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
in	0	O
turn	0	O
is	0	O
answerable	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
parliament	0	O
.	0	O

'My	0	O
kingdom	0	O
for	0	O
purple	0	O
...	0	O
'	0	O

Some	0	O
point	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
rising	0	O
influence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
(	0	O
Francophone	1	S-MISC
)	0	O
liberals	0	O
at	0	O
court	0	O
.	0	O

Karl	1	B-PER
van	1	I-PER
den	1	I-PER
Broeck	1	E-PER

It	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
simple	0	O
solution	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
legitimacy	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
exercise	0	O
of	0	O
power	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
very	0	O
great	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
precisely	0	O
why	0	O
democracy	0	O
is	0	O
'the	0	O
least	0	O
bad	0	O
form	0	O
of	0	O
government	0	O
'	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
transfer	0	O
of	0	O
power	0	O
takes	0	O
place	0	O
peacefully	0	O
and	0	O
those	0	O
in	0	O
power	0	O
have	0	O
legitimacy	0	O
that	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
changed	0	O
.	0	O

Officially	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
very	0	O
simple	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
king	0	O
is	0	O
an	0	O
empty	0	O
box	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
why	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
valuable	0	O
feature	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
civilized	0	O
society	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
transfer	0	O
of	0	O
power	0	O
happens	0	O
peacefully	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
Belgium	1	S-LOC
this	0	O
was	0	O
often	0	O
still	0	O
one	0	O
tendency	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
Christian	0	O
Democrat	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
a	0	O
monarchy	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
question	0	O
of	0	O
who	0	O
has	0	O
the	0	O
right	0	O
to	0	O
exercise	0	O
power	0	O
is	0	O
left	0	O
to	0	O
fate	0	O
:	0	O
whoever	0	O
is	0	O
born	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
king	0	O
's	0	O
sperm	0	O
becomes	0	O
king	0	O
himself	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

publication	0	O

Observers	0	O
point	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
something	0	O
fundamental	0	O
has	0	O
changed	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
since	0	O
the	0	O
purple	0	O
green	0	O
coalition	0	O
took	0	O
office	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Maybe	0	O
it	0	O
's	0	O
all	0	O
much	0	O
simpler	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
court	0	O
's	0	O
natural	0	O
ally	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Christian	0	O
Pillar	0	O
,	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
relegated	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
opposition	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
is	0	O
run	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
Republican	0	O
''	0	O
coalition	0	O
.	0	O

Opinion	0	O

In	0	O
a	0	O
modern	0	O
democracy	0	O
a	0	O
king	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
hold	0	O
his	0	O
own	0	O
if	0	O
he	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
offend	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
.	0	O

Those	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
relinquish	0	O
power	0	O
,	0	O
argue	0	O
.	0	O

Prince	0	O
Laurent	1	S-PER
's	0	O
crypto	0	O
masonic	0	O
education	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
striking	0	O
example	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

author	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
way	0	O
the	0	O
king	0	O
was	0	O
reduced	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
mouthpiece	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
majority	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Belgium	1	S-LOC
naturally	0	O
caused	0	O
problems	0	O
when	0	O
it	0	O
opted	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
'	0	O
constitutional	0	O
monarchy	0	O
'	0	O
in	0	O
1830	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
in	0	O
Great	1	B-LOC
Britain	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
in	0	O
the	2	B-LOC
Netherlands	2	E-LOC
(	0	O
Queen	0	O
Beatrix	3	S-PER
had	0	O
to	0	O
experience	0	O
that	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
of	0	O
course	0	O
also	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
in	0	O
Belgium	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
abortion	0	O
issue	0	O
confronted	0	O
the	0	O
monarch	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
dark	0	O
side	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
'	0	O
political	0	O
neutrality	0	O
'	0	O
:	0	O
his	0	O
religious	0	O
views	0	O
also	0	O
turned	0	O
out	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
hardly	0	O
acceptable	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
deeply	0	O
religious	0	O
monarch	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

The	0	O
CVP	1	S-ORG
reacts	0	O
furiously	0	O
and	0	O
accuses	0	O
the	0	O
king	0	O
of	0	O
partiality	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
knows	0	O
that	0	O
if	0	O
he	0	O
does	0	O
n't	0	O
sign	0	O
the	0	O
euthanasia	0	O
law	0	O
next	0	O
year	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
will	0	O
sign	0	O
his	0	O
death	0	O
warrant	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
king	0	O
found	0	O
himself	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
difficult	0	O
position	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
start	0	O
:	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
remain	0	O
in	0	O
popular	0	O
favor	0	O
to	0	O
maintain	0	O
his	0	O
power	0	O
and	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
resort	0	O
to	0	O
sofa	0	O
politics	0	O
,	0	O
twilight	0	O
zones	0	O
and	0	O
lobbying	0	O
to	0	O
exercise	0	O
some	0	O
power	0	O
as	0	O
well	0	O
.	0	O

in	0	O
a	0	O
monarchy	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
who	0	O
has	0	O
power	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
keep	0	O
power	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
King	0	O
Albert	1	S-PER
and	0	O
his	0	O
children	0	O
are	0	O
becoming	0	O
increasingly	0	O
'purple	0	O
green	0	O
'	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
cold	0	O
reminder	0	O
to	0	O
CVP	2	S-ORG
that	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
calling	0	O
the	0	O
shots	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
king	0	O
Albert	1	S-PER
?	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
The	0	O
ninety	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
grabbed	0	O
his	0	O
gun	0	O
and	0	O
shot	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
offered	0	O
no	0	O
resistance	0	O
when	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
arrested	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

author	0	O

The	0	O
room	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
corridor	0	O
where	0	O
the	0	O
facts	0	O
took	0	O
place	0	O
were	0	O
sealed	0	O
pending	0	O
the	0	O
possible	0	O
departure	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
public	0	O
prosecutor	0	O
's	0	O
office	0	O
of	0	O
Charleroi	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

Life	1	S-ORG

Shortly	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
,	0	O
four	0	O
teams	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
gendarmerie	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Charleroi	1	S-LOC
district	0	O
besieged	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
home	0	O
because	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
assumed	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
home	0	O
director	0	O
was	0	O
dead	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
other	0	O
residents	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
home	0	O
were	0	O
received	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
team	0	O
of	0	O
psychologists	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
94	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
resident	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
retirement	0	O
home	0	O
in	0	O
Aiseau	1	B-LOC
Presles	1	E-LOC
yesterday	0	O
morning	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
short	0	O
distance	0	O
put	0	O
a	0	O
bullet	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
owner	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
home	0	O
.	0	O

Then	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
locked	0	O
himself	0	O
in	0	O
his	0	O
room	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
gendarmerie	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
elderly	0	O
person	0	O
could	0	O
not	0	O
explain	0	O
his	0	O
act	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

The	0	O
perpetrator	0	O
was	0	O
eventually	0	O
overpowered	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
gendarmerie	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
KDM	1	S-ORG
)	0	O

The	0	O
man	0	O
was	0	O
grooming	0	O
the	0	O
shooter	0	O
when	0	O
a	0	O
heated	0	O
argument	0	O
developed	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

Elderly	0	O
man	0	O
shoots	0	O
rest	0	O
home	0	O
director	0	O

page	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

The	0	O
victim	0	O
had	0	O
been	0	O
hit	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
bullet	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
and	0	O
was	0	O
transferred	0	O
to	0	O
Fabiola	1	B-LOC
Hospital	1	E-LOC
of	0	O
Auvelais	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
manager	0	O
was	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
in	0	O
critical	0	O
condition	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
shooting	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
elderly	0	O
man	0	O
was	0	O
noticed	0	O
intermittently	0	O
as	0	O
he	0	O
moved	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
room	0	O
where	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
holed	0	O
up	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
hallway	0	O
.	0	O

Kristof	1	B-PER
Demasure	1	E-PER

He	0	O
seems	0	O
not	0	O
even	0	O
aware	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
behavior	0	O
,	0	O
nor	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
seriousness	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
facts	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
It	0	O
was	0	O
almost	0	O
certain	0	O
that	0	O
Baan	1	S-ORG
would	0	O
be	0	O
taken	0	O
over	0	O
.	0	O

As	0	O
a	0	O
result	0	O
,	0	O
Invensys	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
already	0	O
certain	0	O
of	0	O
10.8	0	O
percent	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
shares	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
thousand	0	O
people	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
leave	0	O
Baan	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

“	0	O
We	0	O
think	0	O
Invensys	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
the	0	O
right	0	O
company	0	O
to	0	O
restructure	0	O
Baan	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

publication	0	O

The	0	O
reorganization	0	O
costs	0	O
are	0	O
said	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
basis	0	O
for	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

By	0	O
the	0	O
way	0	O
,	0	O
Invensys	1	S-ORG
itself	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
doing	0	O
too	0	O
well	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
company	0	O
arose	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
merger	0	O
of	0	O
Siebe	1	S-ORG
and	0	O
BTR	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

edition	0	O

Invensys	1	S-ORG
can	0	O
make	0	O
good	0	O
use	0	O
of	0	O
Baan	2	S-PER
's	0	O
software	0	O
to	0	O
complement	0	O
its	0	O
plant	0	O
and	0	O
plant	0	O
control	0	O
systems	0	O
.	0	O

17	0	O

Invensys	1	S-ORG
offers	0	O
858	0	O
million	0	O
euros	0	O
for	0	O
Baan	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
or	0	O
2.85	0	O
euros	0	O
per	0	O
share	0	O
in	0	O
cash	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
hoped	0	O
that	0	O
next	0	O
year	0	O
the	0	O
losses	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
thing	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
.	0	O

Job	1	S-LOC
in	0	O
British	2	S-MISC
hands	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

section	0	O

The	0	O
hired	0	O
investment	0	O
bank	0	O
Lazard	1	B-ORG
Frères	1	E-ORG
has	0	O
been	0	O
peddling	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
software	0	O
company	0	O
since	0	O
January	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Only	0	O
no	0	O
one	0	O
seemed	0	O
to	0	O
want	0	O
the	0	O
ailing	0	O
venture	0	O
.	0	O

takeover	0	O

Baan	1	S-ORG
shares	0	O
rose	0	O
13	0	O
percent	0	O
to	0	O
EUR	0	O
2.97	0	O
on	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
Invensys	2	S-ORG
lost	0	O
13	0	O
percent	0	O
to	0	O
230	0	O
pence	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
8.8	0	O
percent	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
's	0	O
closing	0	O
price	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
founders	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
brothers	0	O
Jan	1	S-PER
and	0	O
Paul	2	B-PER
Baan	2	E-PER
,	0	O
have	0	O
agreed	0	O
to	0	O
sell	0	O
their	0	O
shares	0	O
to	0	O
Invensys	3	S-ORG
.	0	O

Concurrent	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
acquisition	0	O
of	0	O
Baan	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
British	2	S-MISC
company	0	O
reported	0	O
a	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
£	0	O
238	0	O
million	0	O
,	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
double	0	O
the	0	O
year	0	O
before	0	O
.	0	O

Baan	1	S-ORG
was	0	O
once	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
best	0	O
performing	0	O
stocks	0	O
in	0	O
Europe	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
but	0	O
has	0	O
lost	0	O
90	0	O
percent	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
value	0	O
in	0	O
two	0	O
years	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
ongoing	0	O
losses	0	O
and	0	O
management	0	O
problems	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

Other	0	O
top	0	O
people	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
will	0	O
also	0	O
do	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

Invensys	1	S-ORG
wants	0	O
to	0	O
thoroughly	0	O
reorganize	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
and	0	O
is	0	O
earmarking	0	O
400	0	O
million	0	O
euros	0	O
for	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
name	0	O
Baan	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
intended	0	O
to	0	O
remain	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
as	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
Invensys	2	B-ORG
Software	2	I-ORG
and	2	I-ORG
Systems	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

bloomberg	1	S-ORG

The	0	O
Dutch	1	S-MISC
software	0	O
maker	0	O
Baan	2	S-ORG
is	0	O
bought	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
British	3	S-MISC
Invensys	4	S-ORG
.	0	O

page	0	O

We	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
do	0	O
that	0	O
quickly	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Invensys	2	S-ORG
chairman	0	O
Allen	1	B-PER
Yurko	1	E-PER
.	0	O

The	1	B-ORG
Financial	1	I-ORG
Tomorrow	1	E-ORG

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

author	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Return	0	O
Elián	1	S-PER
to	0	O
Cuba	2	S-LOC
step	0	O
closer	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

In	0	O
the	0	O
Yugoslav	1	S-MISC
republic	0	O
of	0	O
Serbia	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
several	0	O
high	0	O
ranking	0	O
officials	0	O
and	0	O
criminals	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
murdered	0	O
in	0	O
recent	0	O
times	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
this	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
time	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
thing	0	O
has	0	O
happened	0	O
in	0	O
Montenegro	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
republic	0	O
in	0	O
Yugoslav	4	B-LOC
Federation	4	E-LOC
.	0	O

edition	0	O

The	0	O
return	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Cuban	1	S-MISC
boat	0	O
refugee	0	O
Elián	2	B-PER
González	2	E-PER
from	0	O
the	0	O
United	3	B-LOC
States	3	E-LOC
to	0	O
his	0	O
homeland	0	O
yesterday	0	O
came	0	O
one	0	O
step	0	O
closer	0	O
.	0	O

short	0	O

The	0	O
family	0	O
is	0	O
now	0	O
appealing	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Supreme	1	B-ORG
Court	1	E-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
Hammersmith	1	B-LOC
Bridge	1	E-LOC
to	0	O
the	0	O
west	0	O
of	0	O
London	2	S-LOC
was	0	O
damaged	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
bomb	0	O
explosion	0	O
yesterday	0	O
.	0	O

Bomb	0	O
explodes	0	O
under	0	O
London	1	S-LOC
bridge	0	O

Abroad	1	S-ORG

The	0	O
pro	0	O
western	0	O
Montenegro	1	S-LOC
tries	0	O
to	0	O
steer	0	O
an	0	O
independent	0	O
course	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Serbia	2	S-LOC
of	0	O
Slobodan	3	B-PER
Milosevic	3	I-PER
's	3	E-PER
.	0	O

There	0	O
were	0	O
no	0	O
casualties	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
huge	0	O
traffic	0	O
chaos	0	O
.	0	O

Police	0	O
discovered	0	O
a	0	O
small	0	O
explosive	0	O
attached	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
beam	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
bridge	0	O
connecting	0	O
both	0	O
banks	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Thames	1	B-LOC
River	1	E-LOC
River	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Northern	1	B-MISC
Ireland	1	E-MISC
unionists	0	O
point	0	O
the	0	O
finger	0	O
at	0	O
republican	0	O
splinter	0	O
movements	0	O
because	0	O
the	0	O
Irish	2	B-ORG
Republican	2	I-ORG
Army	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
IRA	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
also	0	O
committed	0	O
a	0	O
failed	0	O
attack	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
bridge	0	O
in	0	O
1996	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
are	0	O
considerable	0	O
tensions	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
republics	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
judge	0	O
's	0	O
ruling	0	O
was	0	O
the	0	O
latest	0	O
development	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
lawsuit	0	O
filed	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Elián	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
family	0	O
from	0	O
Miami	2	S-LOC
to	0	O
keep	0	O
the	0	O
child	0	O
in	0	O
U.S.	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
where	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
taken	0	O
care	0	O
of	0	O
after	0	O
his	0	O
dramatic	0	O
shipwreck	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
court	0	O
,	0	O
only	0	O
his	0	O
father	0	O
can	0	O
do	0	O
that	0	O
for	0	O
him	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

An	0	O
appeals	0	O
court	0	O
in	0	O
Atlanta	1	S-LOC
decided	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
six	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
boy	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
entitled	0	O
to	0	O
apply	0	O
for	0	O
asylum	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
US	2	S-LOC
himself	0	O
.	0	O

Montenegro	2	S-LOC
President	0	O
Djukanovic	1	S-PER
's	0	O
security	0	O
adviser	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
shot	0	O
dead	0	O
by	0	O
unknown	0	O
persons	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
Podgorica	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

publication	0	O

page	0	O

The	0	O
boy	0	O
must	0	O
remain	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
United	1	B-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
until	0	O
a	0	O
decision	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
made	0	O
in	0	O
that	0	O
case	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
police	0	O
found	0	O
Goran	1	B-PER
Zugic	1	E-PER
's	0	O
body	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
garden	0	O
near	0	O
his	0	O
home	0	O
after	0	O
a	0	O
local	0	O
resident	0	O
heard	0	O
gunshots	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Employee	0	O
of	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Montenegro	1	S-LOC
murdered	0	O

Police	0	O
are	0	O
investigating	0	O
whether	0	O
the	0	O
failed	0	O
attack	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
work	0	O
of	0	O
dissident	0	O
paramilitaries	0	O
from	0	O
Northern	1	B-LOC
Ireland	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
who	0	O
are	0	O
opposing	0	O
the	0	O
self	0	O
government	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
returned	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
province	0	O
this	0	O
week	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

section	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
In	0	O
the	0	O
evening	0	O
he	0	O
released	0	O
seventeen	0	O
children	0	O
and	0	O
two	0	O
supervisors	0	O
.	0	O

Wasserbillig	0	O

From	0	O
our	0	O
reporter	0	O
on	0	O
site	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
in	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
five	0	O
French	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
three	0	O
German	2	S-MISC
and	0	O
one	0	O
Italian	3	S-MISC
hostages	0	O
an	0	O
eight	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
Belgian	4	S-MISC
girl	0	O
was	0	O
also	0	O
held	0	O
.	0	O

At	0	O
half	0	O
past	0	O
eight	0	O
on	0	O
Thursday	0	O
morning	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
ultimatum	0	O
expired	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
Bejoui	1	S-PER
demanded	0	O
a	0	O
minibus	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
airport	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
plane	0	O
to	0	O
Libya	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
police	0	O
reportedly	0	O
intervened	0	O
because	0	O
the	0	O
hostage	0	O
taker	0	O
planned	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
some	0	O
children	0	O
with	0	O
him	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
possible	0	O
flight	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
man	0	O
kept	0	O
the	0	O
children	0	O
and	0	O
carers	0	O
captive	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
daycare	0	O
center	0	O
in	0	O
Wasserbillig	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
a	0	O
small	0	O
town	0	O
in	0	O
Grand	2	B-LOC
Duchy	2	I-LOC
of	2	I-LOC
Luxembourg	2	E-LOC
.	0	O

page	0	O

The	0	O
hostage	0	O
taking	0	O
of	0	O
twenty	0	O
five	0	O
children	0	O
and	0	O
two	0	O
supervisors	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Luxembourg	1	S-MISC
ended	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
hostages	0	O
just	0	O
after	0	O
seven	0	O
o'clock	0	O
last	0	O
night	0	O
.	0	O

Cathy	1	B-PER
Galle	1	E-PER

edition	0	O

Thirteen	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
children	0	O
are	0	O
of	0	O
Portuguese	1	S-MISC
descent	0	O
.	0	O

Page	0	O
3	0	O

Police	0	O
actions	0	O
were	0	O
initially	0	O
thwarted	0	O
because	0	O
the	0	O
hostage	0	O
closely	0	O
followed	0	O
coverage	0	O
on	0	O
television	0	O
and	0	O
radio	0	O
.	0	O

Yesterday	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
hostage	0	O
released	0	O
four	0	O
more	0	O
children	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
1	0	O
&	0	O
amp	0	O
;	0	O
3	0	O
)	0	O

Sniper	0	O
ends	0	O
hostage	0	O
crisis	0	O
in	0	O
Wasserbillig	1	S-LOC

An	1	B-PER
Bruyninckx	1	E-PER

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
latest	0	O
reports	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
had	0	O
two	0	O
gunshot	0	O
wounds	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
and	0	O
his	0	O
life	0	O
was	0	O
in	0	O
danger	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

section	0	O

publication	0	O

author	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

He	0	O
would	0	O
also	0	O
have	0	O
asked	0	O
60	0	O
million	0	O
Belgian	1	S-MISC
francs	0	O
(	0	O
1.5	0	O
million	0	O
euros	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
hostage	0	O
situation	0	O
started	0	O
around	0	O
3:30	0	O
am	0	O
on	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
afternoon	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
entered	0	O
the	0	O
daycare	0	O
center	0	O
armed	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
knife	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
pistol	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
grenade	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

The	0	O
hostage	0	O
taker	0	O
,	0	O
39	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
Negi	1	B-PER
Bejoui	1	E-PER
,	0	O
was	0	O
shot	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
sniper	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
In	0	O
April	0	O
last	0	O
year	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
commotion	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
file	0	O
when	0	O
Steve	1	B-PER
Stevaert	1	E-PER
(	0	O
SP	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
then	0	O
minister	0	O
of	0	O
Spatial	3	B-ORG
Planning	3	E-ORG
,	0	O
withdrew	0	O
the	0	O
BPA	4	S-MISC
in	0	O
question	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
auditor	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
Council	5	B-ORG
of	5	I-ORG
State	5	E-ORG
advised	0	O
it	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
destroyed	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Floralux	1	B-ORG
's	1	I-ORG
counsel	1	E-ORG
's	0	O
counsel	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
impose	0	O
a	0	O
sanction	0	O
because	0	O
after	0	O
all	0	O
these	0	O
years	0	O
it	0	O
would	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
make	0	O
sense	0	O
.	0	O

Page	0	O
7	0	O

The	0	O
Floralux	0	O
case	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
dragging	0	O
on	0	O
for	0	O
years	0	O
and	0	O
revolves	0	O
around	0	O
a	0	O
zoning	0	O
change	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
tailored	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
and	0	O
allowed	0	O
the	0	O
plant	0	O
grower	0	O
to	0	O
develop	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
supermarket	0	O
sized	0	O
garden	0	O
center	0	O
in	0	O
what	0	O
was	0	O
originally	0	O
an	0	O
agricultural	0	O
area	0	O
.	0	O

Floralux	1	S-ORG
must	0	O
therefore	0	O
neither	0	O
downsize	0	O
nor	0	O
pay	0	O
compensation	0	O
to	0	O
Dadiflor	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

A	0	O
fax	0	O
confiscated	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
High	1	B-ORG
Supervisory	1	I-ORG
Committee	1	E-ORG
from	0	O
its	0	O
lawyer	0	O
to	0	O
his	0	O
client	0	O
leaves	0	O
no	0	O
doubt	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
role	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
college	0	O
of	0	O
aldermen	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
matter	0	O
.	0	O

Business	0	O
manager	0	O
Christiane	1	B-PER
Vandenbussche	1	E-PER
was	0	O
suspected	0	O
of	0	O
having	0	O
become	0	O
CVP	0	O
ships	0	O
of	0	O
Spatial	2	B-ORG
Planning	2	E-ORG
in	0	O
order	0	O
to	0	O
realize	0	O
the	0	O
'	0	O
BPA	3	B-ORG
Kezelberg	3	E-ORG
'	0	O
in	0	O
question	0	O
herself	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Conflict	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
remains	0	O
unpunished	0	O

The	0	O
dossier	0	O
took	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
greater	0	O
dimension	0	O
because	0	O
it	0	O
involved	0	O
a	0	O
great	0	O
deal	0	O
of	0	O
political	0	O
lobbying	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
rather	0	O
a	0	O
symbolic	0	O
decision	0	O
,	0	O
because	0	O
the	0	O
more	0	O
important	0	O
regional	0	O
plan	0	O
had	0	O
already	0	O
been	0	O
adjusted	0	O
by	0	O
then	0	O
,	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
matter	0	O
was	0	O
definitively	0	O
regularized	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
1	0	O
&	0	O
amp	0	O
;	0	O
3	0	O
)	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

section	0	O

All	0	O
civil	0	O
claims	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
counterparty	0	O
,	0	O
competitor	0	O
Dadiflor	1	S-PER
,	0	O
have	0	O
also	0	O
been	0	O
dismissed	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

Sybille	1	B-PER
Decoo	1	E-PER

The	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	1	S-LOC
finds	0	O
that	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
controversial	0	O
garden	0	O
center	0	O
Floralux	2	S-ORG
there	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
conflict	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
West	3	B-MISC
Flemish	3	E-MISC
Dadizele	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
but	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
consider	0	O
it	0	O
necessary	0	O
to	0	O
punish	0	O
business	0	O
manager	0	O
Christiane	5	B-PER
Vandenbussche	5	E-PER
for	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

Antwerp	1	S-LOC
/	0	O
Dadizele	2	S-LOC

By	0	O
condemning	0	O
Floralux	1	S-ORG
for	0	O
'taking	0	O
interests	0	O
'	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
wanted	0	O
to	0	O
denounce	0	O
political	0	O
lobbying	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
just	0	O
like	0	O
the	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
Appeal	0	O
in	0	O
Ghent	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
it	0	O
also	0	O
ruled	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC
that	0	O
the	0	O
fax	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
excluded	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
file	0	O
because	0	O
it	0	O
falls	0	O
under	0	O
the	0	O
professional	0	O
secrecy	0	O
of	0	O
lawyers	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

Sybille	1	B-PER
Decoo	1	E-PER

For	0	O
example	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
file	0	O
showed	0	O
up	0	O
in	0	O
Leo	2	B-PER
Delcroix	2	E-PER
's	0	O
infamous	0	O
Atoma	1	B-MISC
notebooks	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

Antwerp	1	S-LOC
appeals	0	O
court	0	O
lets	0	O
business	0	O
manager	0	O
of	0	O
garden	0	O
center	0	O
Floralux	2	S-ORG
go	0	O
unpunished	0	O

Conflict	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
criminal	0	O
sense	0	O
would	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
proven	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

Own	0	O
reporting	0	O

Competitor	0	O
Dadiflor	1	S-PER
takes	0	O
courage	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
judgment	0	O
by	0	O
seeing	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
conviction	0	O
an	0	O
additional	0	O
argument	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
destruction	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
regional	0	O
plan	0	O
amendment	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Council	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
State	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
Ghent	1	S-MISC
Attorney	0	O
General	0	O
Frank	2	B-PER
Schins	2	E-PER
even	0	O
ruled	0	O
that	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
overlobbying	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
file	0	O
.	0	O

Christiane	1	B-PER
Vandenbussche	1	E-PER
decides	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
court	0	O
has	0	O
condemned	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
political	0	O
mores	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
''	0	O
but	0	O
she	0	O
still	0	O
thinks	0	O
she	0	O
did	0	O
''	0	O
nothing	0	O
wrong	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Last	0	O
year	0	O
,	0	O
then	0	O
CVP	1	B-ORG
minister	1	E-ORG
Luc	2	B-PER
Martens	2	E-PER
admitted	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
called	0	O
''	0	O
attention	0	O
''	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
Flemish	3	S-MISC
government	0	O
.	0	O

1	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
For	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
time	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
Giro	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
the	0	O
leader	0	O
ran	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
bit	0	O
of	0	O
trouble	0	O
yesterday	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
Abetone	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Casagrande	2	S-PER
had	0	O
impressed	0	O
last	0	O
Monday	0	O
and	0	O
also	0	O
in	0	O
Dolomites	3	S-LOC
the	0	O
leader	0	O
had	0	O
not	0	O
flinched	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
,	0	O
followed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
wheel	0	O
by	0	O
Tonkov	1	S-PER
,	0	O
again	0	O
reached	0	O
Garzelli	2	S-PER
and	0	O
co	0	O
and	0	O
sprinted	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
third	0	O
place	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
top	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
difference	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
leader	0	O
and	0	O
Garzelli	1	S-PER
is	0	O
only	0	O
25	0	O
seconds	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

On	0	O
the	0	O
contrary	0	O
,	0	O
Stefano	1	B-PER
Garzelli	1	E-PER
and	0	O
Gilberto	2	B-PER
Simoni	2	E-PER
made	0	O
it	0	O
clear	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
can	0	O
make	0	O
life	0	O
miserable	0	O
for	0	O
Casagrande	3	S-LOC
today	0	O
and	0	O
tomorrow	0	O
.	0	O

Later	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
also	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
with	0	O
Ivan	1	B-PER
Gotti	1	E-PER
.	0	O

Pratonevoso	1	S-PER

To	0	O
win	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
fear	0	O
no	0	O
one	0	O
and	0	O
I	0	O
will	0	O
attack	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
announced	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
now	0	O
really	0	O
feels	0	O
the	0	O
hot	0	O
breath	0	O
of	0	O
Stefano	1	B-PER
Garzelli	1	E-PER
in	0	O
the	0	O
neck	0	O
.	0	O

We	0	O
are	0	O
looking	0	O
forward	0	O
with	0	O
great	0	O
interest	0	O
to	0	O
today	0	O
's	0	O
queen	0	O
stage	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
climbs	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
col	0	O
d'Agnelli	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
2748	0	O
meters	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
Izoard	2	S-LOC
(	0	O
2361	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
tomorrow	0	O
's	0	O
climb	0	O
time	0	O
trial	0	O
over	0	O
the	0	O
Montgenèvre	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Sestriere	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

page	0	O

Thanks	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
support	0	O
of	0	O
Buenahora	1	S-PER
,	0	O
Casagrande	2	S-ORG
fixed	0	O
the	0	O
problem	0	O
a	0	O
little	0	O
later	0	O
.	0	O

Wednesday	0	O
was	0	O
too	0	O
much	0	O
for	0	O
Di	1	B-PER
Luca	1	E-PER
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

Casagrande	1	S-ORG
feels	0	O
hot	0	O
breath	0	O
from	0	O
Garzelli	2	S-PER

The	0	O
tastemaker	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
two	0	O
weeks	0	O
,	0	O
got	0	O
rid	0	O
of	0	O
tendonitis	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
where	0	O
I	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
a	0	O
difference	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
say	0	O
that	0	O
Casagrande	1	S-PER
spoke	0	O
optimistic	0	O
language	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
eve	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
drive	0	O
to	0	O
Pratonevoso	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Insofar	0	O
as	0	O
both	0	O
still	0	O
had	0	O
profit	0	O
ambitions	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
can	0	O
now	0	O
put	0	O
them	0	O
away	0	O
permanently	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

And	0	O
that	0	O
may	0	O
well	0	O
be	0	O
.	0	O

Own	0	O
reporting	0	O

I	0	O
'll	0	O
be	0	O
back	0	O
next	0	O
year	0	O
.	0	O

We	0	O
will	0	O
get	0	O
more	0	O
clarity	0	O
today	0	O
and	0	O
tomorrow	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
extremely	0	O
difficult	0	O
Alpine	1	B-MISC
stages	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

Garzelli	1	S-PER
and	0	O
Piepoli	2	S-PER
not	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
also	0	O
enjoys	0	O
the	0	O
advantage	0	O
of	0	O
being	0	O
the	0	O
better	0	O
time	0	O
trialist	0	O
among	0	O
the	0	O
favorites	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
means	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
now	0	O
really	0	O
dares	0	O
to	0	O
think	0	O
about	0	O
winning	0	O
the	0	O
race	0	O
.	0	O

Win	0	O
The	1	B-MISC
Giro	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

author	0	O

''	0	O
But	0	O
I	0	O
learned	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
Giro	1	S-MISC
.	0	O

Rosette	1	B-PER
jersey	1	I-PER
wearer	1	E-PER
has	0	O
n't	0	O
won	0	O
Giro	2	S-MISC
yet	0	O

Gonzales	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
Galdeano	1	E-PER
,	0	O
known	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
better	0	O
time	0	O
trialist	0	O
,	0	O
turned	0	O
it	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
real	0	O
time	0	O
trial	0	O
between	0	O
Genoa	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
Brescia	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

(	0	O
TL	0	O
)	0	O

Sport	0	O

Francesco	1	B-PER
Casagrande	1	E-PER
will	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
less	0	O
reassured	0	O
after	0	O
yesterday	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

publication	0	O

†	0	O

Building	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
solid	0	O
climbing	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Italian	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
everyone	0	O
became	0	O
more	0	O
and	0	O
more	0	O
convinced	0	O
that	0	O
Casagrande	2	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
had	0	O
set	0	O
the	0	O
Italian	3	S-MISC
round	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
main	0	O
goal	0	O
and	0	O
made	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
of	0	O
sacrifices	0	O
for	0	O
it	0	O
,	0	O
would	0	O
achieve	0	O
its	0	O
goal	0	O
.	0	O

Casagrande	3	S-PER
had	0	O
to	0	O
fit	0	O
under	0	O
Gilberto	1	B-PER
Simoni	1	E-PER
's	0	O
brusque	0	O
tempos	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
steepest	0	O
sections	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Pratonevoso	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

''	0	O
This	0	O
ride	0	O
is	0	O
more	0	O
important	0	O
to	0	O
me	0	O
than	0	O
the	0	O
next	0	O
two	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
win	0	O
today	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
written	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
control	0	O
sheet	0	O
that	0	O
morning	0	O
.	0	O

Because	0	O
no	0	O
matter	0	O
how	0	O
hard	0	O
the	0	O
sprinters	0	O
teams	0	O
were	0	O
chasing	0	O
the	0	O
Spaniard	1	S-MISC
in	0	O
the	0	O
group	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
still	0	O
had	0	O
almost	0	O
half	0	O
a	0	O
minute	0	O
left	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
finish	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
should	0	O
we	0	O
assume	0	O
that	0	O
dropping	0	O
out	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
while	0	O
and	0	O
constantly	0	O
clinging	0	O
to	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
sign	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
wall	0	O
?	0	O

Half	0	O
way	0	O
through	0	O
,	0	O
after	0	O
118	0	O
kilometers	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
singled	0	O
out	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
pack	0	O
,	0	O
ran	0	O
out	0	O
to	0	O
seven	0	O
minutes	0	O
and	0	O
brilliantly	0	O
resisted	0	O
the	0	O
pack	0	O
's	0	O
return	0	O
.	0	O

Especially	0	O
for	0	O
Garzelli	1	S-PER
the	0	O
stage	0	O
win	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
boost	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

And	0	O
the	0	O
Spaniard	1	S-MISC
from	0	O
the	0	O
Vitalicio	2	B-LOC
team	2	E-LOC
kept	0	O
its	0	O
word	0	O
.	0	O

On	0	O
Pratonevoso	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Dario	2	B-PER
Frigo	2	E-PER
got	0	O
into	0	O
trouble	0	O
very	0	O
early	0	O
on	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
promises	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
exciting	0	O
final	0	O
days	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
Italy	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

The	0	O
team	0	O
mate	0	O
of	0	O
Marco	1	B-PER
Pantani	1	E-PER
and	0	O
leader	0	O
of	0	O
Mercatone	2	B-ORG
Uno	2	E-ORG
in	0	O
this	0	O
Giro	3	S-MISC
left	0	O
all	0	O
his	0	O
competitors	0	O
behind	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
Pratonevoso	4	S-LOC
yesterday	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
thanks	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
bonus	0	O
,	0	O
crept	0	O
closer	0	O
to	0	O
Casagrande	5	S-LOC
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
pains	0	O
were	0	O
unbearable	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
young	0	O
Di	1	B-PER
Luca	1	E-PER
.	0	O

15	0	O

But	0	O
the	0	O
Tuscan	1	S-MISC
is	0	O
sometimes	0	O
said	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
week	0	O
too	0	O
long	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
Grand	0	O
Tour	0	O
.	0	O

Wednesday	0	O
Alvaro	1	B-PER
Gonzales	1	I-PER
de	1	I-PER
Galdeano	1	E-PER
made	0	O
it	0	O
his	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

So	0	O
it	0	O
did	0	O
n't	0	O
go	0	O
that	0	O
fast	0	O
.	0	O

Tony	1	B-PER
Landuyt	1	E-PER

Two	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
favorites	0	O
were	0	O
thrown	0	O
overboard	0	O
yesterday	0	O
.	0	O

They	0	O
quickly	0	O
followed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
footsteps	0	O
of	0	O
Simoni	1	S-PER
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
publication	0	O
date	0	O

But	0	O
the	0	O
more	0	O
Chernow	1	S-PER
wrote	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
more	0	O
enthusiastic	0	O
they	0	O
became	0	O
.	0	O

Both	0	O
initially	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
like	0	O
Chernow	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
plan	0	O
because	0	O
they	0	O
still	0	O
felt	0	O
too	0	O
''	0	O
young	0	O
and	0	O
healthy	0	O
''	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
biography	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
first	0	O
edition	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
500	0	O
page	0	O
book	0	O
Christo	1	B-PER
and	1	I-PER
Jeanne	1	I-PER
Claude	1	E-PER
a	0	O
biography	0	O
has	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
being	0	O
only	0	O
appeared	0	O
in	0	O
German	2	S-MISC
.	0	O

Biography	0	O
Christo	1	B-PER
published	1	E-PER

General	1	S-ORG

Culture	0	O

Earlier	0	O
this	0	O
week	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Bulgarian	1	B-MISC
American	1	E-MISC
artist	0	O
couple	0	O
Christo	2	S-PER
(	0	O
Javacheff	3	S-PER
)	0	O
and	0	O
Jeanne	4	B-PER
Claude	4	E-PER
presented	0	O
their	0	O
biography	0	O
published	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
publisher	0	O
Keipenheuer	6	B-ORG
Witsch	6	E-ORG
in	0	O
Cologne	5	S-LOC
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

page	0	O

The	0	O
author	0	O
Burt	1	B-PER
Chernow	1	E-PER
and	0	O
friend	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
house	0	O
of	0	O
Christo	2	B-PER
's	2	E-PER
wrote	0	O
the	0	O
biography	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
couple	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
Bulgaria	3	S-LOC
native	0	O
Christo	4	B-PER
Javacheff	4	E-PER
and	0	O
his	0	O
great	0	O
love	0	O
Jeanne	5	B-PER
Claude	5	I-PER
de	5	I-PER
Guillebon	5	E-PER
.	0	O

publication	0	O

They	0	O
especially	0	O
caused	0	O
a	0	O
sensation	0	O
in	0	O
1995	0	O
when	0	O
they	0	O
completely	0	O
wrapped	0	O
the	0	O
German	1	B-MISC
Reichstag	1	E-MISC
in	0	O
Berlin	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

edition	0	O

section	0	O

author	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

''	0	O
Germany	1	S-LOC
has	0	O
a	0	O
special	0	O
place	0	O
in	0	O
our	0	O
hearts	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
artists	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
presentation	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
artistic	0	O
couple	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
involved	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
art	0	O
of	0	O
wrapping	0	O
since	0	O
the	0	O
1960s	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
General	1	S-ORG

Peter	1	B-PER
Jan	1	I-PER
Bogaert	1	E-PER

(	0	O
PJB	0	O
)	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
government	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
raising	0	O
awareness	0	O
for	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
twenty	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Brussels	1	S-MISC
Environment	0	O
Minister	0	O
Didier	2	B-PER
Gosuin	2	E-PER
(	0	O
PRL/FDF	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
is	0	O
also	0	O
disappointed	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
meager	0	O
''	0	O
content	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
federal	0	O
ozone	0	O
plan	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
each	0	O
exceeding	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
European	1	S-MISC
health	0	O
standard	0	O
(	0	O
120	0	O
micrograms	0	O
of	0	O
ozone	0	O
per	0	O
cubic	0	O
meter	0	O
for	0	O
at	0	O
least	0	O
eight	0	O
hours	0	O
)	0	O
they	0	O
demand	0	O
50	0	O
million	0	O
Belgian	5	S-MISC
francs	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Belgian	2	S-MISC
state	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Brussels	3	B-ORG
Region	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
the	0	O
nineteen	0	O
Brussels	4	S-MISC
municipalities	0	O
.	0	O

Air	0	O
pollution	0	O
deserves	0	O
much	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
says	0	O
Gosuin	1	S-PER
,	0	O
announcing	0	O
structural	0	O
measures	0	O
itself	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
federal	0	O
ozone	0	O
plan	0	O
gets	0	O
a	0	O
serious	0	O
failing	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
environmental	0	O
movement	0	O
.	0	O

Environmental	0	O
movement	0	O
tightens	0	O
ozone	0	O
process	0	O

page	0	O

Two	0	O
Brussels	1	S-MISC
associations	0	O
,	0	O
Bral	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Inter	3	B-ORG
Environnement	3	E-ORG
,	0	O
are	0	O
fed	0	O
up	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
delays	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
authorities	0	O
and	0	O
are	0	O
going	0	O
to	0	O
court	0	O
for	0	O
summary	0	O
proceedings	0	O
.	0	O

Pages	0	O
2	0	O
and	0	O
7	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

publication	0	O

Before	0	O
the	0	O
summer	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
associations	0	O
are	0	O
requesting	0	O
concrete	0	O
measures	0	O
to	0	O
limit	0	O
car	0	O
traffic	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
cabinet	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Minister	0	O
of	0	O
Health	0	O
Magda	1	B-PER
Aelvoet	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Agalev	2	S-PER
)	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
respond	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
complaint	0	O
yesterday	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

General	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
1	0	O
&	0	O
amp	0	O
;	0	O
3	0	O
)	0	O

author	0	O

1	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

section	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Di	1	B-PER
Biase	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
11	0	O
.	0	O

Zabel	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3h15:58	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

Buenahora	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Col	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
08	0	O
8	0	O
.	0	O

Wüst	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
/	3	B-LOC
Festina	3	E-LOC
)	0	O
the	0	O
102.6	0	O
km	0	O
in	0	O
2h28:10	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

Plaza	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
31u08:55	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

Leoni	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Simoni	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
53	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Simoni	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Kadlec	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ch	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
...	0	O

Frigo	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4:34	0	O
10	0	O
.	0	O

43	0	O
.	0	O

Finot	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Fra	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
zt	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Zabel	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Blank	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4:39	0	O
11	0	O
.	0	O

Ullrich	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:33	0	O
10	0	O
.	0	O

Forconi	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:18	0	O
18	0	O
.	0	O

Merckx	1	S-ORG
all	0	O
zt	0	O

Sport	0	O

Tonkov	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Russian	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:41	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Verbrugghe	1	S-PER
17	0	O
.	0	O

Rebellion	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
10:21	0	O
.	0	O

Bracke	0	O
all	0	O
zt	0	O

Hruska	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ch	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
...	0	O

Guidi	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
10	0	O
.	0	O

Bruylandts	1	S-ORG
0:23	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Pantani	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
...	0	O

Fornaciari	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
13	0	O
.	0	O

Garzelli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
on	0	O
25	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Casero	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:42	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

McRae	1	S-PER
(	0	O
USA	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
19:00	0	O
19	0	O
.	0	O

Course	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ned	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

McRae	1	S-PER
(	0	O
VSt	0	O
)	0	O
1:47	0	O
14	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

Blank	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
10	0	O
.	0	O

Garzelli	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
/	0	O
Mercatone	3	B-LOC
Uno	3	E-LOC
)	0	O
the	0	O
173	0	O
km	0	O
in	0	O
4:42:32	0	O
(	0	O
avg	0	O
.	0	O
:	0	O
36.739	0	O
km	0	O
/	0	O
h	0	O
)	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

Lanfranchi	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
12:51	0	O
15	0	O
.	0	O

7th	0	O
stage	0	O
(	0	O
time	0	O
trial	0	O
)	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Plaza	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Spa	2	B-LOC
/	2	I-LOC
Festina	2	E-LOC
)	0	O
the	0	O
35.7	0	O
km	0	O
in	0	O
42:53	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

56	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

Beikirch	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
German	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
...	0	O

Boscardin	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Zwi	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
44	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Rous	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Fra	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
at	0	O
0:09	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Van	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
Wouwer	1	E-PER
0:13	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Petersen	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
all	0	O
zt	0	O

Tour	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
Italy	1	I-MISC
:	1	I-MISC
17th	1	E-MISC
ride	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Grand	1	B-MISC
Prix	1	I-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
Wallonia	1	E-MISC
(	0	O
category	0	O
1.2	0	O
)	0	O
:	0	O

Hruska	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ch	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
13:14	0	O
16	0	O
.	0	O

Rubiera	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4:45	0	O
12	0	O
.	0	O

Pena	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Col	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
16:59	0	O
18	0	O
.	0	O

1	0	O
.	0	O

16	0	O
.	0	O

Savoldelli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
19:08	0	O
20	0	O
.	0	O

Leoni	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Hoj	1	S-LOC
Den	2	S-LOC
)	3	S-LOC
2:12	0	O
10	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

Final	0	O
score	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Gotti	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:54	0	O
17	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

Tour	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
Italy	1	E-MISC
:	0	O

Klöden	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
at	0	O
0:42	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Piepoli	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
on	0	O
02	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

31	0	O
.	0	O

Gerosa	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
14	0	O
.	0	O

15	0	O

Casero	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:40	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Rittsel	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Swe	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:34	0	O
.	0	O

Gonzalez	1	B-ORG
de	1	I-ORG
Galdeano	1	E-ORG
...	0	O

Seville	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
15:24	0	O
17	0	O
.	0	O

Farazijn	1	S-PER
1:58	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Usov	1	S-PER
(	0	O
WRu	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Merckx	1	S-PER
7:32	0	O
...	0	O

Baguet	1	S-ORG
18	0	O
.	0	O

Savoldelli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
8:23	0	O
48	0	O
.	0	O

Rubiera	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
49	0	O
11	0	O
.	0	O

Rush	1	S-PER
2:06	0	O
9	0	O
.	0	O

Heppner	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:06	0	O
...	0	O

Piepoli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
6:13	0	O
14	0	O
.	0	O

Liese	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:11	0	O
8	0	O
.	0	O

Position	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

13	0	O
.	0	O

17th	0	O
stage	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Vermeersch	1	S-PER
2:02	0	O
8	0	O
.	0	O

Blaudzun	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:44	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Lafis	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Swe	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
15	0	O
.	0	O

Bölts	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:41	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Frigo	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:38	0	O
20	0	O
.	0	O

Kristensen	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
zt	0	O
...	0	O

34	0	O
.	0	O

Petersen	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Blaudzun	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:46	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Martinello	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Tour	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
Germany	1	E-MISC
:	0	O

Ullrich	1	S-ORG
18:04	0	O

Ullrich	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Dui	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
all	0	O
zt	0	O

Beikirch	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

18th	0	O
stage	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Belli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Gonzalez	1	B-MISC
de	1	I-MISC
Galdeano	1	E-MISC
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
/	0	O
Vitalicio	3	S-LOC
)	0	O
the	0	O
236	0	O
km	0	O
in	0	O
5:23:02	0	O
(	0	O
avg	0	O
:	0	O
43,834	0	O
km	0	O
/	0	O
h	0	O
)	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

Boogerd	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ned	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
zt	0	O
...	0	O

Petacchi	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Baranowski	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Poo	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
13	0	O
.	0	O

Castelblanco	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Col	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:24	0	O
19	0	O
.	0	O

Belli	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:11	0	O
5	0	O
.	0	O

Usov	1	S-PER
(	0	O
WRu	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

Casagrande	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Noe	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3:39	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Konyshev	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Russian	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Braikia	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
Den	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
9	0	O
.	0	O

Bölts	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:26	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Buenahora	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Col	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
3:43	0	O
8	0	O
.	0	O

Klöden	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
at	0	O
40	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Wüst	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4	0	O
.	0	O

Heppner	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ger	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
2:21	0	O
9	0	O
.	0	O

Casagrande	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
/	0	O
Vini	3	B-LOC
Caldirola	3	E-LOC
)	0	O
87u11:09	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Mattan	1	S-PER
19	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

De	1	B-PER
Jongh	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Ned	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
8	0	O
.	0	O

Elli	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
in	0	O
4:42:05	0	O
(	0	O
avg	0	O
.	0	O
41.732	0	O
km	0	O
/	0	O
h	0	O
)	0	O
2	0	O
.	0	O

Noe	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
12	0	O
9	0	O
.	0	O

6th	0	O
stage	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

Mancebo	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
20:36	0	O
.	0	O

Lanfranchi	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:12	0	O
12	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

Mancebo	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Spa	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
16	0	O
.	0	O

Tonkov	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Russian	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
6	0	O
.	0	O

De	1	B-PER
Clercq	1	E-PER
20	0	O
.	0	O

Conte	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
12	0	O
.	0	O

Gotti	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
4:25	0	O
9	0	O
.	0	O

Pieri	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Ita	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
7	0	O
.	0	O

Honchar	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Uk	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
1:51	0	O
15	0	O
.	0	O

70	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Svorada	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Ch	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
on	0	O
24	0	O
3	0	O
.	0	O

Honchar	1	S-PER
(	0	O
Uk	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
5:45	0	O
13	0	O
.	0	O

8th	0	O
stage	0	O
:	0	O
1	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Last	0	O
year	0	O
I	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
deal	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
problem	0	O
when	0	O
I	0	O
reconnected	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
competition	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	1	B-MISC
of	1	I-MISC
the	1	I-MISC
Walloon	1	I-MISC
Regions	1	E-MISC
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Question	0	O
marks	0	O
around	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
are	0	O
getting	0	O
bigger	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

publication	0	O

Are	0	O
they	0	O
wrong	0	O
?	0	O

†	0	O

I	0	O
just	0	O
hope	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
thing	0	O
will	0	O
happen	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
coming	0	O
days	0	O
,	0	O
although	0	O
I	0	O
must	0	O
confess	0	O
that	0	O
I	0	O
am	0	O
not	0	O
quite	0	O
sure	0	O
about	0	O
it	0	O
anymore	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Tour	1	S-MISC
is	0	O
approaching	0	O
fast	0	O
.	0	O

Cycling	1	S-ORG

†	0	O

There	0	O
are	0	O
even	0	O
those	0	O
who	0	O
are	0	O
already	0	O
betting	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
departure	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	2	S-MISC
on	0	O
July	0	O
1	0	O
in	0	O
Futuroscope	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
understand	0	O
why	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
noise	0	O
around	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
says	0	O
a	0	O
surprised	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
.	0	O

Sport	0	O

Ief	1	B-PER
Vertommen	1	E-PER

''	0	O
I	0	O
am	0	O
not	0	O
well	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
stated	0	O
an	0	O
otherwise	0	O
serene	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
.	0	O

Own	0	O
reporting	0	O

As	0	O
a	0	O
direct	0	O
preparation	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	2	S-MISC
,	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
actually	0	O
preferred	0	O
to	0	O
drive	0	O
the	0	O
Dauphiné	3	S-LOC
(	0	O
June	0	O
4	0	O
11	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
Route	4	S-LOC
du	5	B-LOC
Sud	5	E-LOC
(	0	O
June	0	O
17	0	O
20	0	O
)	0	O
instead	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	6	B-MISC
of	6	I-MISC
Luxembourg	6	E-MISC
(	0	O
June	0	O
8	0	O
11	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	7	B-MISC
of	7	I-MISC
Switzerland	7	E-MISC
(	0	O
13	0	O
to	0	O
20	0	O
June	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O
June	0	O
22	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Kempenaar	1	S-MISC
was	0	O
satisfied	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
test	0	O
in	0	O
view	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	2	B-MISC
de	2	I-MISC
France	2	E-MISC
which	0	O
is	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
more	0	O
important	0	O
to	0	O
him	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
As	0	O
far	0	O
as	0	O
I	0	O
know	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
still	0	O
regular	0	O
riders	0	O
who	0	O
tinker	0	O
with	0	O
their	0	O
program	0	O
.	0	O

Van	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
Wouwer	1	E-PER
knew	0	O
early	0	O
on	0	O
that	0	O
Elli	2	S-PER
would	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
man	0	O
to	0	O
beat	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

I	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
panic	0	O
yet	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
there	0	O
will	0	O
now	0	O
be	0	O
no	0	O
more	0	O
obstacles	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
way	0	O
of	0	O
my	0	O
preparation	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
At	0	O
least	0	O
a	0	O
lot	0	O
less	0	O
than	0	O
expected	0	O
.	0	O

After	0	O
117	0	O
km	0	O
he	0	O
called	0	O
it	0	O
quits	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
thing	0	O
may	0	O
be	0	O
clear	0	O
from	0	O
all	0	O
this	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
'	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	B-PER
story	1	E-PER
'	0	O
is	0	O
far	0	O
from	0	O
in	0	O
sight	0	O
.	0	O

15	0	O

A	0	O
few	0	O
more	0	O
matches	0	O
were	0	O
needed	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
World	1	B-MISC
Cup	1	E-MISC
before	0	O
the	0	O
déclic	0	O
announced	0	O
itself	0	O
.	0	O

Frank	1	B-PER
Vandenbroucke	1	E-PER
specifies	0	O
in	0	O
GP	2	B-ORG
Wallonie	2	E-ORG
:	0	O
'	0	O
I	0	O
'm	0	O
not	0	O
doing	0	O
well	0	O
'	0	O

Simply	0	O
because	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
more	0	O
recovery	0	O
time	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
combination	0	O
.	0	O

Belgians	1	S-MISC
that	0	O
are	0	O
already	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
Dave	2	B-PER
Bruylants	2	E-PER
,	0	O
second	0	O
yesterday	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
Kurt	3	B-PER
Van	3	I-PER
de	3	I-PER
Wauwer	3	E-PER
,	0	O
third	0	O
.	0	O

Ief	1	B-PER
Vertommen	1	E-PER

Before	0	O
the	0	O
start	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
race	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
said	0	O
reaching	0	O
top	0	O
condition	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
matter	0	O
of	0	O
days	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
barely	0	O
two	0	O
climbs	0	O
further	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
found	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
back	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
pack	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
subsequent	0	O
assignment	0	O
therefore	0	O
surprised	0	O
no	0	O
one	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

Meanwhile	0	O
,	0	O
Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
has	0	O
also	0	O
understood	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
is	0	O
currently	0	O
not	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
position	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
any	0	O
demands	0	O
in	0	O
connection	0	O
with	0	O
his	0	O
preparation	0	O
program	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Tour	2	S-MISC
.	0	O

edition	0	O

†	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
condition	0	O
is	0	O
good	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
not	0	O
great	0	O
.	0	O

Then	0	O
I	0	O
was	0	O
regularly	0	O
driven	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
quarter	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
hour	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

Yesterday	0	O
he	0	O
gave	0	O
up	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
only	0	O
Belgian	1	S-MISC
races	0	O
he	0	O
would	0	O
ride	0	O
on	0	O
Belgian	2	S-MISC
soil	0	O
.	0	O

While	0	O
Alberto	1	B-PER
Elli	1	E-PER
from	0	O
the	0	O
Telekom	2	B-ORG
team	2	E-ORG
of	0	O
Walter	3	B-PER
Godefroot	3	E-PER
wrote	0	O
the	0	O
Wallonia	4	B-MISC
GP	4	E-MISC
(	0	O
1.2	0	O
)	0	O
to	0	O
his	0	O
name	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
freshly	0	O
washed	0	O
and	0	O
dressed	0	O
Frank	5	B-PER
Vandenbroucke	5	E-PER
in	0	O
the	0	O
company	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
Italian	6	S-MISC
friend	0	O
Sara	7	S-PER
was	0	O
already	0	O
thinking	0	O
about	0	O
how	0	O
to	0	O
proceed	0	O
with	0	O
him	0	O
now	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
now	0	O
I	0	O
will	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
accept	0	O
the	0	O
arrangement	0	O
as	0	O
proposed	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
team	0	O
management	0	O
.	0	O

names	0	O

Vandenbroucke	1	S-PER
:	0	O
''	0	O
I	0	O
am	0	O
not	0	O
panicking	0	O
yet	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
there	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
no	0	O
more	0	O
obstacles	0	O
in	0	O
my	0	O
Tour	2	B-MISC
preparation	2	E-MISC
''	0	O

Not	0	O
that	0	O
I	0	O
'm	0	O
sick	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
I	0	O
just	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
have	0	O
any	0	O
acceleration	0	O
in	0	O
my	0	O
legs	0	O
.	0	O

Bruylants	1	S-PER
,	0	O
only	0	O
fourteen	0	O
days	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
race	0	O
again	0	O
,	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
pay	0	O
for	0	O
his	0	O
attempt	0	O
to	0	O
retrieve	0	O
Elli	2	S-PER
with	0	O
cramps	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
New	0	O
are	0	O
director	0	O
Patrice	1	B-PER
Toye	1	E-PER
(	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
award	0	O
winning	0	O
film	0	O
Rosie	2	S-MISC
)	0	O
and	0	O
Marion	3	B-PER
Oprel	3	E-PER
,	0	O
girlfriend	0	O
of	0	O
Marianne	4	B-PER
'De	4	I-PER
Mol	4	E-PER
)	0	O
Dupont	5	S-PER
.	0	O

short	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

Agalev	1	S-PER
says	0	O
it	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
turn	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC
into	0	O
an	0	O
open	0	O
,	0	O
bustling	0	O
metropolis	0	O
again	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

Several	0	O
people	0	O
in	0	O
their	0	O
twenties	0	O
have	0	O
already	0	O
registered	0	O
and	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
included	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
detailed	0	O
lists	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
announced	0	O
later	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
senior	0	O
party	0	O
Becoming	1	B-ORG
Worthy	1	E-ORG
(	0	O
WOW	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
will	0	O
participate	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
,	0	O
district	0	O
and	0	O
provincial	0	O
council	0	O
elections	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	3	S-LOC
on	0	O
8	0	O
October	0	O
.	0	O

WOW	1	S-ORG
participates	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC

Journal	1	S-ORG

There	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
moment	0	O
of	0	O
doubt	0	O
about	0	O
this	0	O
when	0	O
a	0	O
municipal	0	O
councilor	0	O
switched	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	1	S-ORG
and	0	O
his	0	O
colleague	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
provincial	0	O
council	0	O
defected	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Vlaams	2	B-LOC
Blok	2	E-LOC
.	0	O

Singer	0	O
,	0	O
showman	0	O
and	0	O
presenter	0	O
Marcel	1	B-PER
Vanthilt	1	E-PER
will	0	O
be	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
list	0	O
of	0	O
Agalev	3	S-PER
in	0	O
the	0	O
next	0	O
municipal	0	O
elections	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

page	0	O

†	0	O

He	0	O
gets	0	O
31st	0	O
place	0	O
and	0	O
is	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
so	0	O
called	0	O
cordon	0	O
culturel	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
green	0	O
list	0	O
.	0	O

Number	0	O
one	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
list	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
province	0	O
is	0	O
Frans	1	B-PER
Verbergt	1	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
a	0	O
county	0	O
councilor	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
VLD	2	S-ORG
for	0	O
ten	0	O
years	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
list	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
municipality	0	O
is	0	O
headed	0	O
by	0	O
André	1	B-PER
Crahay	1	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
former	0	O
bank	0	O
clerk	0	O
who	0	O
is	0	O
relatively	0	O
new	0	O
to	0	O
politics	0	O
.	0	O

'	0	O
We	0	O
are	0	O
the	0	O
alternative	0	O
'	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
slogan	0	O
with	0	O
which	0	O
WOW	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
going	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
elections	0	O
in	0	O
Antwerp	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Vanthilt	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
far	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
only	0	O
BV	2	S-ORG
on	0	O
the	0	O
Antwerp	3	B-MISC
Agalev	3	I-MISC
list	3	E-MISC
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Actress	0	O
Jeanine	1	B-PER
Bisschops	1	E-PER
and	0	O
author	0	O
Tom	2	B-PER
Lanoye	2	E-PER
had	0	O
previously	0	O
pledged	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
That	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
happen	0	O
with	0	O
scare	0	O
makers	0	O
and	0	O
pessimists	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
party	0	O
states	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
we	0	O
are	0	O
more	0	O
interested	0	O
in	0	O
green	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
color	0	O
of	0	O
hope	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

section	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

At	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
level	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
party	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
implement	0	O
universal	0	O
suffrage	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Antwerp	1	S-LOC
district	0	O
the	0	O
Greens	0	O
hope	0	O
to	0	O
become	0	O
the	0	O
largest	0	O
party	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
,	0	O
Agalev	1	B-ORG
Antwerp	1	E-ORG
comes	0	O
out	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
list	0	O
of	0	O
Known	2	B-MISC
Flemings	2	E-MISC
that	0	O
subscribe	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
party	0	O
program	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
list	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Cahay	1	S-PER
,	0	O
his	0	O
party	0	O
presents	0	O
itself	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
link	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
ages	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
means	0	O
that	0	O
young	0	O
people	0	O
also	0	O
get	0	O
a	0	O
chance	0	O
.	0	O

Artists	0	O
for	0	O
Agalev	1	S-PER

publication	0	O

Georges	1	B-PER
Carpenter	1	E-PER

The	0	O
actresses	0	O
Sarah	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
Bosschere	1	E-PER
,	0	O
Veerle	2	B-PER
Dobbelaere	2	E-PER
and	0	O
Patricia	3	B-PER
Goemaere	3	E-PER
,	0	O
writer	0	O
Kristien	4	B-PER
Hemmerechts	4	E-PER
,	0	O
musician	0	O
and	0	O
concert	0	O
organizer	0	O
Paul	5	B-PER
Ambach	5	E-PER
,	0	O
actor	0	O
Pol	6	B-PER
Goossen	6	E-PER
,	0	O
authors	0	O
Paul	7	B-PER
Mennes	7	E-PER
,	0	O
Bart	8	B-PER
Moeyaert	8	E-PER
and	0	O
Jeroen	9	B-PER
Olyslaeghers	9	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
actor	0	O
Carl	10	B-PER
Ridders	10	E-PER
signed	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
program	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
''	0	O
Let	0	O
's	0	O
leave	0	O
that	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
mediators	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
called	0	O
yesterday	0	O

First	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	1	S-MISC
troops	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
leave	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
in	0	O
Addis	2	B-LOC
Abeba	2	E-LOC
they	0	O
do	0	O
n't	0	O
listen	0	O
to	0	O
that	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

Abroad	1	S-ORG

Observers	0	O
do	0	O
say	0	O
that	0	O
Ethiopian	1	S-MISC
troops	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
withdrawn	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
western	0	O
cities	0	O
Barentu	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
Tessenay	3	S-LOC
captured	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
latest	0	O
offensive	0	O
.	0	O

Eritrea	1	S-LOC
wants	0	O
people	0	O
to	0	O
adhere	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
four	0	O
point	0	O
plan	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Organization	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
African	2	I-ORG
Unity	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

That	0	O
includes	0	O
sending	0	O
international	0	O
observers	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
disputed	0	O
border	0	O
zone	0	O
.	0	O

Asmara	1	S-LOC
will	0	O
not	0	O
hear	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
file	0	O
until	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	2	S-MISC
troops	0	O
are	0	O
withdrawn	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
would	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
go	0	O
back	0	O
to	0	O
our	0	O
positions	0	O
of	0	O
May	0	O
6	0	O
,	0	O
1998	0	O
(	0	O
the	0	O
start	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
war	0	O
,	0	O
MR	0	O
)	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	1	S-MISC
minister	0	O
.	0	O

Ethiopia	1	S-LOC
did	0	O
this	0	O
after	0	O
it	0	O
recaptured	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
territory	0	O
lost	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
Eritrean	2	S-MISC
raid	0	O
in	0	O
'98	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
Addis	1	B-LOC
Abeba	1	E-LOC
now	0	O
wants	0	O
guarantees	0	O
that	0	O
its	0	O
troops	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
penetrated	0	O
deeply	0	O
into	0	O
Eritrea	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
will	0	O
withdraw	0	O
.	0	O

Opposing	0	O
views	0	O
on	0	O
when	0	O
Ethiopian	1	S-MISC
troops	0	O
should	0	O
withdraw	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Eritrea	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
says	0	O
the	0	O
BBC	2	B-ORG
correspondent	2	E-ORG
in	0	O
Asmara	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
is	0	O
very	0	O
humiliated	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	4	S-MISC
statement	0	O
.	0	O

Eritrea	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
Ethiopia	2	S-LOC
disagree	0	O
on	0	O
file	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
current	0	O
situation	0	O
is	0	O
widely	0	O
interpreted	0	O
as	0	O
one	0	O
where	0	O
Ethiopia	1	S-LOC
can	0	O
dictate	0	O
the	0	O
law	0	O
because	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
recent	0	O
military	0	O
successes	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
is	0	O
unacceptable	0	O
to	0	O
Asmara	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Eritrea	1	S-LOC
called	0	O
the	0	O
whole	0	O
thing	0	O
curious	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
BCC	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
Eritrean	2	S-MISC
town	0	O
Zenefe	3	S-LOC
remains	0	O
occupied	0	O
by	0	O
Ethiopian	4	S-MISC
soldiers	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

''	0	O
But	0	O
then	0	O
we	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
sure	0	O
that	0	O
Eritrea	1	S-LOC
does	0	O
n't	0	O
repeat	0	O
the	0	O
madness	0	O
of	0	O
just	0	O
invading	0	O
a	0	O
neighboring	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

From	0	O
the	0	O
news	0	O
agencies	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Ethiopia	1	S-LOC
the	0	O
clatter	0	O
of	0	O
arms	0	O
is	0	O
over	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
Eritrea	2	S-LOC
does	0	O
not	0	O
share	0	O
that	0	O
opinion	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
exactly	0	O
where	0	O
the	0	O
shoe	0	O
pinches	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

page	0	O

edition	0	O

It	0	O
was	0	O
not	0	O
immediately	0	O
clear	0	O
what	0	O
guarantees	0	O
Addis	1	B-LOC
Abeba	1	E-LOC
wants	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
's	0	O
a	0	O
bit	0	O
like	0	O
clapping	0	O
with	0	O
one	0	O
hand	0	O
:	0	O
Ethiopia	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
Eritrea	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
at	0	O
war	0	O
for	0	O
two	0	O
years	0	O
,	0	O
are	0	O
sitting	0	O
around	0	O
the	0	O
negotiating	0	O
table	0	O
in	0	O
Algiers	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

Algiers	1	S-LOC

Ouyahia	1	S-PER
called	0	O
the	0	O
statement	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	2	S-MISC
Secretary	0	O
of	0	O
State	0	O
Seyoum	3	B-PER
Mesfin	3	E-PER
that	0	O
the	0	O
war	0	O
was	0	O
over	0	O
''	0	O
an	0	O
encouraging	0	O
thing	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
,	0	O
cartographers	0	O
should	0	O
redraw	0	O
the	0	O
border	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
financial	0	O
compensation	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
losses	0	O
on	0	O
both	0	O
sides	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
finally	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
in	0	O
depth	0	O
investigation	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
causes	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
conflict	0	O
is	0	O
also	0	O
desirable	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Algerian	1	S-MISC
Justice	0	O
Minister	0	O
Ahmed	2	B-PER
Ouyahia	2	E-PER
has	0	O
been	0	O
trying	0	O
since	0	O
Tuesday	0	O
to	0	O
mediate	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
conflict	0	O
between	0	O
Ethiopia	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Eritrea	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
which	0	O
flared	0	O
up	0	O
again	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
last	0	O
three	0	O
weeks	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	5	S-MISC
army	0	O
crossed	0	O
the	0	O
border	0	O
.	0	O

Martin	1	B-PER
Rabaey	1	E-PER

''	0	O
How	0	O
can	0	O
they	0	O
say	0	O
the	0	O
war	0	O
is	0	O
over	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

We	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
close	0	O
a	0	O
ceasefire	0	O
as	0	O
long	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
Ethiopian	1	S-MISC
soldiers	0	O
are	0	O
within	0	O
100	0	O
km	0	O
of	0	O
Asmara	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Eritrean	3	S-MISC
presidential	0	O
adviser	0	O
Yemane	4	B-PER
Gebremeskel	4	E-PER
.	0	O

And	0	O
Addis	1	B-LOC
Abeba	1	E-LOC
only	0	O
wants	0	O
that	0	O
if	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
international	0	O
guarantees	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Belga	1	S-ORG
/	0	O
Own	0	O
messaging	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

Tax	0	O
reform	0	O
should	0	O
also	0	O
end	0	O
discrimination	0	O
between	0	O
married	0	O
people	0	O
and	0	O
cohabitants	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

ACW	1	B-ORG
chairman	1	E-ORG
Theo	2	B-PER
Rombouts	2	E-PER
wants	0	O
the	0	O
coming	0	O
tax	0	O
reform	0	O
to	0	O
mainly	0	O
benefit	0	O
people	0	O
with	0	O
low	0	O
incomes	0	O
.	0	O

Wages	0	O
have	0	O
fallen	0	O
below	0	O
half	0	O
the	0	O
national	0	O
income	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
longer	0	O
acceptable	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

Journal	1	S-ORG

Some	0	O
should	0	O
definitely	0	O
go	0	O
to	0	O
social	0	O
security	0	O
and	0	O
some	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
saved	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
his	0	O
speech	0	O
in	0	O
Mechelen	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Cortebeeck	2	S-PER
stated	0	O
that	0	O
in	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
social	0	O
benefits	0	O
,	0	O
wages	0	O
have	0	O
also	0	O
fallen	0	O
behind	0	O
.	0	O

Therefore	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
next	0	O
inter	0	O
sectoral	0	O
negotiations	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Christian	0	O
trade	0	O
union	0	O
will	0	O
promote	0	O
gradual	0	O
wage	0	O
increases	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
best	0	O
and	0	O
most	0	O
tried	0	O
and	0	O
tested	0	O
means	0	O
of	0	O
sharing	0	O
the	0	O
fruits	0	O
of	0	O
growth	0	O
.	0	O

Financial	0	O
participation	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
close	0	O
the	0	O
pay	0	O
gap	0	O
,	0	O
believes	0	O
Cortebeeck	1	S-PER
.	0	O

The	0	O
Christian	0	O
union	0	O
is	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
gradual	0	O
increase	0	O
in	0	O
wages	0	O
and	0	O
social	0	O
benefits	0	O
,	0	O
ACV	1	B-ORG
chairman	1	E-ORG
Luc	2	B-PER
Cortebeeck	2	E-PER
stated	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
Rerum	3	B-MISC
Novarum	3	I-MISC
speech	3	E-MISC
.	0	O

Mechelen	1	S-LOC
/	0	O
Brussels	2	S-LOC

This	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
accompanied	0	O
by	0	O
an	0	O
increase	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
net	0	O
income	0	O
of	0	O
low	0	O
income	0	O
single	0	O
earners	0	O
and	0	O
of	0	O
families	0	O
with	0	O
dependent	0	O
children	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
have	0	O
not	0	O
sacrificed	0	O
for	0	O
years	0	O
to	0	O
put	0	O
the	0	O
money	0	O
for	0	O
pensions	0	O
and	0	O
health	0	O
care	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
hands	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
private	0	O
sector	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
ACV	1	B-ORG
chairman	1	E-ORG
said	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
urged	0	O
the	0	O
government	0	O
not	0	O
to	0	O
simply	0	O
enrich	0	O
private	0	O
companies	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
insurance	0	O
sector	0	O
by	0	O
entrusting	0	O
them	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
fruits	0	O
of	0	O
deleveraging	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Cortebeeck	1	S-PER
,	0	O
not	0	O
all	0	O
new	0	O
government	0	O
revenue	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
reserved	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
aging	0	O
population	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
profit	0	O
participation	0	O
,	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
employee	0	O
's	0	O
income	0	O
is	0	O
made	0	O
dependent	0	O
on	0	O
too	0	O
many	0	O
arbitrary	0	O
decisions	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
why	0	O
the	0	O
ACW	1	S-ORG
defends	0	O
an	0	O
increase	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
deductible	0	O
professional	0	O
expenses	0	O
for	0	O
wage	0	O
earners	0	O
and	0	O
wage	0	O
earners	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
higher	0	O
first	0	O
tax	0	O
free	0	O
bracket	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
labor	0	O
income	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Georges	1	B-PER
Carpenter	1	E-PER

ACW	1	B-ORG
chairman	1	E-ORG
Theo	2	B-PER
Rombouts	2	E-PER
also	0	O
argued	0	O
in	0	O
his	0	O
speech	0	O
in	0	O
Wemmel	3	S-LOC
for	0	O
a	0	O
tax	0	O
reduction	0	O
that	0	O
should	0	O
focus	0	O
primarily	0	O
on	0	O
incomes	0	O
from	0	O
work	0	O
and	0	O
especially	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
longer	0	O
incomes	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
available	0	O
resources	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
better	0	O
used	0	O
to	0	O
strengthen	0	O
the	0	O
foundations	0	O
of	0	O
society	0	O
,	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
education	0	O
and	0	O
care	0	O
,	0	O
public	0	O
transport	0	O
and	0	O
roads	0	O
,	0	O
food	0	O
safety	0	O
,	0	O
etc	0	O
.	0	O
Improvement	0	O
for	0	O
low	0	O
incomes	0	O
can	0	O
only	0	O
come	0	O
through	0	O
raising	0	O
the	0	O
minimum	0	O
subsistence	0	O
level	0	O
,	0	O
guaranteed	0	O
income	0	O
and	0	O
social	0	O
benefits	0	O
.	0	O

Profit	0	O
sharing	0	O
presupposes	0	O
power	0	O
sharing	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
we	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
allowed	0	O
that	0	O
,	0	O
Cortebeeck	1	S-PER
said	0	O
,	0	O
because	0	O
the	0	O
employers	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
know	0	O
about	0	O
a	0	O
previously	0	O
negotiated	0	O
CAO	2	S-MISC
on	0	O
the	0	O
matter	0	O
.	0	O

ACV	1	S-ORG
prefers	0	O
wage	0	O
increase	0	O
to	0	O
profit	0	O
participation	0	O

The	0	O
union	0	O
leader	0	O
stated	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
active	0	O
welfare	0	O
state	0	O
also	0	O
has	0	O
its	0	O
downsides	0	O
.	0	O

Finally	0	O
,	0	O
Rombouts	1	S-PER
asked	0	O
for	0	O
tax	0	O
incentives	0	O
to	0	O
start	0	O
living	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
more	0	O
environmentally	0	O
friendly	0	O
way	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
self	0	O
employed	0	O
have	0	O
already	0	O
been	0	O
served	0	O
with	0	O
1.5	0	O
billion	0	O
francs	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
social	0	O
benefit	0	O
recipients	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
disabled	0	O
,	0	O
handicapped	0	O
and	0	O
unemployed	0	O
in	0	O
financial	0	O
need	0	O
receive	0	O
nothing	0	O
and	0	O
are	0	O
falling	0	O
further	0	O
and	0	O
further	0	O
behind	0	O
.	0	O

Rerum	1	B-MISC
Novarum	1	I-MISC
speeches	1	E-MISC
point	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
dark	0	O
side	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
active	0	O
welfare	0	O
state	0	O

edition	0	O

publication	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
union	0	O
leader	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
catch	0	O
up	0	O
in	0	O
wages	0	O
and	0	O
benefits	0	O
is	0	O
preferable	0	O
to	0	O
letting	0	O
employees	0	O
participate	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
profit	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
company	0	O
.	0	O

Cortebeeck	1	S-PER
likes	0	O
a	0	O
tax	0	O
reform	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
is	0	O
opposed	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
general	0	O
tax	0	O
cut	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
any	0	O
case	0	O
,	0	O
this	0	O
formula	0	O
requires	0	O
participation	0	O
in	0	O
determining	0	O
the	0	O
profit	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
On	0	O
Sunday	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
ridge	0	O
of	0	O
high	0	O
pressure	0	O
builds	0	O
up	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
southwest	0	O
,	0	O
gradually	0	O
stabilizing	0	O
the	0	O
atmosphere	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

A	0	O
few	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
could	0	O
develop	0	O
very	0	O
locally	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
loose	0	O
shower	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
west	0	O
towards	0	O
evening	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

section	0	O

The	0	O
third	0	O
factor	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
cold	0	O
front	0	O
approaching	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
west	0	O
.	0	O

Furthermore	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
thermal	0	O
furrow	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
located	0	O
in	0	O
our	0	O
environment	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
will	0	O
,	0	O
however	0	O
,	0	O
become	0	O
less	0	O
warm	0	O
from	0	O
Sunday	0	O
onwards	0	O
.	0	O

Eddy	1	B-PER
DeMey	1	E-PER

Sunny	0	O
this	0	O
morning	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Sunny	0	O
this	0	O
morning	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
pressure	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
colder	0	O
air	0	O
causes	0	O
strong	0	O
upward	0	O
movements	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

Summer	0	O
hot	0	O
.	0	O

Tomorrow	0	O
increasing	0	O
chance	0	O
of	0	O
rain	0	O
and	0	O
thunderstorms	0	O
,	0	O
followed	0	O
by	0	O
cooling	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
month	0	O
of	0	O
May	0	O
was	0	O
warmer	0	O
than	0	O
usual	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
wind	0	O
is	0	O
generally	0	O
weak	0	O
and	0	O
blows	0	O
mainly	0	O
from	0	O
south	0	O
southwest	0	O
directions	0	O
.	0	O

Temperatures	0	O
of	0	O
25	0	O
degrees	0	O
and	0	O
more	0	O
are	0	O
achievable	0	O
this	0	O
afternoon	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

tomorrow	0	O
thunderstorm	0	O

The	0	O
sun	0	O
thus	0	O
becomes	0	O
decidedly	0	O
master	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
situation	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
mercury	0	O
goes	0	O
on	0	O
an	0	O
adventure	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
are	0	O
almost	0	O
no	0	O
clouds	0	O
here	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
many	0	O
places	0	O
the	0	O
mercury	0	O
hardly	0	O
drops	0	O
below	0	O
20	0	O
degrees	0	O
before	0	O
midnight	0	O
.	0	O

After	0	O
the	0	O
weekend	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
weather	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
looking	0	O
bad	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
not	0	O
completely	0	O
steadfast	0	O
.	0	O

86	0	O
liters	0	O
of	0	O
precipitation	0	O
fell	0	O
in	0	O
20	0	O
days	0	O
compared	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
normal	0	O
62	0	O
liters	0	O
in	0	O
15	0	O
days	0	O
.	0	O

19.1	0	O
(	0	O
standard	0	O
17.2	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Warm	0	O
and	0	O
initially	0	O
stable	0	O
air	0	O
is	0	O
supplied	0	O
from	0	O
France	3	S-LOC
on	0	O
the	0	O
flank	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
more	0	O
or	0	O
less	0	O
stationary	0	O
ridge	0	O
above	0	O
Central	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
Eastern	2	B-LOC
Europe	2	E-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
flow	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
anticyclonic	0	O
today	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
cyclonic	0	O
tomorrow	0	O
.	0	O

min	0	O
.	0	O
11.3	0	O
(	0	O
standard	0	O
8.3	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

Max	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

A	0	O
single	0	O
shower	0	O
can	0	O
have	0	O
hail	0	O
on	0	O
board	0	O
and	0	O
locally	0	O
discharge	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
water	0	O
that	0	O
nuisance	0	O
occurs	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
night	0	O
from	0	O
Saturday	0	O
to	0	O
Sunday	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
cold	0	O
front	0	O
will	0	O
move	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
afternoon	0	O
also	0	O
cumulus	0	O
clouds	0	O
.	0	O

Later	0	O
also	0	O
cumulus	0	O
clouds	0	O
and	0	O
tonight	0	O
a	0	O
small	0	O
chance	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
shower	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
sun	0	O
shone	0	O
little	0	O
(	0	O
less	0	O
than	0	O
159	0	O
hours	0	O
)	0	O
against	0	O
normal	0	O
199	0	O
hours	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

Tonight	0	O
it	0	O
will	0	O
stay	0	O
warm	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
long	0	O
time	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
other	0	O
words	0	O
it	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
ideal	0	O
garden	0	O
or	0	O
terrace	0	O
weather	0	O
.	0	O

As	0	O
a	0	O
result	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
chance	0	O
of	0	O
thunderstorms	0	O
increases	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
afternoon	0	O
and	0	O
evening	0	O
progresses	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

As	0	O
a	0	O
thermal	0	O
furrow	0	O
approaches	0	O
west	0	O
of	0	O
France	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
atmosphere	0	O
becomes	0	O
somewhat	0	O
unstable	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
afternoon	0	O
,	0	O
creating	0	O
a	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
cumulus	0	O
clouds	0	O
.	0	O

Meanwhile	1	S-PER

Tomorrow	0	O
increasing	0	O
chance	0	O
of	0	O
rain	0	O
and	0	O
thunderstorms	0	O
,	0	O
followed	0	O
by	0	O
cooling	0	O
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
Is	0	O
that	0	O
health	0	O
standard	0	O
often	0	O
exceeded	0	O
?	0	O

More	0	O
interesting	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
new	0	O
Dutch	1	S-MISC
initiative	0	O
of	0	O
toll	0	O
booths	0	O
and	0	O
road	0	O
pricing	0	O
around	0	O
the	0	O
major	0	O
Dutch	2	S-MISC
cities	0	O
.	0	O

Two	0	O
Brussels	1	S-MISC
environmental	0	O
groups	0	O
,	0	O
Bral	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Inter	3	B-ORG
Environnement	3	E-ORG
...	0	O

Because	0	O
studies	0	O
show	0	O
that	0	O
car	0	O
traffic	0	O
is	0	O
responsible	0	O
for	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
70	0	O
percent	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
high	0	O
ozone	0	O
concentrations	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
neighboring	0	O
countries	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
working	0	O
on	0	O
such	0	O
measures	0	O
for	0	O
some	0	O
time	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
Belgium	1	S-LOC
is	0	O
lagging	0	O
behind	0	O
.	0	O

page	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
different	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
old	0	O
ozone	0	O
plan	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
announced	0	O
in	0	O
1996	0	O
.	0	O

French	1	S-MISC
cities	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
Paris	2	S-LOC
work	0	O
with	0	O
alternating	0	O
driving	0	O
bans	0	O
,	0	O
whereby	0	O
even	0	O
or	0	O
odd	0	O
number	0	O
plates	0	O
are	0	O
not	0	O
allowed	0	O
to	0	O
drive	0	O
during	0	O
ozone	0	O
peaks	0	O
.	0	O

author	0	O

''	0	O
A	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
German	1	S-MISC
states	0	O
are	0	O
already	0	O
introducing	0	O
temporary	0	O
speed	0	O
limits	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
's	0	O
too	0	O
bad	0	O
.	0	O

Peter	1	B-PER
Jan	1	I-PER
Bogaert	1	E-PER

For	0	O
Brussels	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
these	0	O
measures	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
combined	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
rapid	0	O
development	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
real	0	O
Brussels	2	S-MISC
suburban	0	O
network	0	O
with	0	O
large	0	O
transfer	0	O
parking	0	O
spaces	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Last	0	O
year	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
exceeded	0	O
in	0	O
Brussels	1	S-LOC
in	0	O
27	0	O
days	0	O
.	0	O

If	0	O
you	0	O
are	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
right	0	O
,	0	O
what	0	O
will	0	O
you	0	O
do	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
money	0	O
if	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
exceeded	0	O
?	0	O

During	0	O
days	0	O
with	0	O
high	0	O
ozone	0	O
peaks	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
populations	0	O
at	0	O
risk	0	O
are	0	O
asked	0	O
to	0	O
stay	0	O
indoors	0	O
until	0	O
the	0	O
'danger	0	O
'	0	O
has	0	O
passed	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

Which	0	O
measures	0	O
apply	0	O
abroad	0	O
?	0	O

This	0	O
means	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
elderly	0	O
,	0	O
children	0	O
or	0	O
persons	0	O
with	0	O
asthma	0	O
problems	0	O
always	0	O
ran	0	O
serious	0	O
health	0	O
risks	0	O
.	0	O

Opinion	0	O

†	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
considerable	0	O
amount	0	O
,	0	O
precisely	0	O
to	0	O
force	0	O
the	0	O
policy	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
structural	0	O
measures	0	O
as	0	O
quickly	0	O
as	0	O
possible	0	O
.	0	O

If	0	O
we	0	O
do	0	O
receive	0	O
money	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
will	0	O
transfer	0	O
it	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
fund	0	O
with	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
for	0	O
example	0	O
,	0	O
I	0	O
can	0	O
help	0	O
finance	0	O
the	0	O
Brussels	1	S-LOC
suburban	0	O
network	0	O
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
announced	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
maximum	0	O
speed	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
limited	0	O
.	0	O

They	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
the	0	O
rates	0	O
high	0	O
enough	0	O
to	0	O
keep	0	O
a	0	O
large	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
cars	0	O
off	0	O
the	0	O
road	0	O
.	0	O

edition	0	O

†	0	O

'The	0	O
federal	0	O
ozone	0	O
plan	0	O
deeply	0	O
disappoints	0	O
us	0	O
'	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

This	0	O
also	0	O
conflicts	0	O
with	0	O
Article	0	O
23	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Constitution	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
guarantees	0	O
'human	0	O
dignity	0	O
'	0	O
for	0	O
everyone	0	O
.	0	O

Given	0	O
the	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
overages	0	O
in	0	O
1999	0	O
,	0	O
you	0	O
can	0	O
get	0	O
rich	0	O
quick	0	O
.	0	O

Another	0	O
study	0	O
found	0	O
that	0	O
1,200	0	O
people	0	O
died	0	O
in	0	O
Belgium	1	S-LOC
during	0	O
the	0	O
1994	0	O
heat	0	O
wave	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
result	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
high	0	O
ozone	0	O
concentrations	0	O
during	0	O
that	0	O
period	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
federal	0	O
government	0	O
has	0	O
just	0	O
released	0	O
its	0	O
ozone	0	O
plan	0	O
.	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Ceustermans	1	S-PER
:	0	O
''	0	O
Each	0	O
time	0	O
the	0	O
so	0	O
called	0	O
European	2	S-MISC
health	0	O
standard	0	O
of	0	O
120	0	O
micrograms	0	O
ozone	0	O
per	0	O
cubic	0	O
meter	0	O
in	0	O
Brussels	3	S-LOC
is	0	O
exceeded	0	O
for	0	O
at	0	O
least	0	O
eight	0	O
hours	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
ask	0	O
for	0	O
compensation	0	O
of	0	O
50	0	O
million	0	O
Belgian	4	S-MISC
francs	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
piece	0	O
of	0	O
work	0	O
disappoints	0	O
us	0	O
.	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

†	0	O

†	0	O

''	0	O
It	0	O
's	0	O
not	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
money	0	O
for	0	O
us	0	O
,	0	O
let	0	O
that	0	O
be	0	O
clear	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
case	0	O
will	0	O
appear	0	O
before	0	O
the	0	O
Court	0	O
of	0	O
First	0	O
Instance	0	O
in	0	O
summary	0	O
proceedings	0	O
on	0	O
9	0	O
June	0	O
.	0	O

Satisfied	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
work	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
green	0	O
ministers	0	O
Magda	1	B-PER
Aelvoet	1	E-PER
and	0	O
Isabelle	2	B-PER
Durant	2	E-PER
?	0	O

The	0	O
emphasis	0	O
is	0	O
on	0	O
information	0	O
and	0	O
awareness	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
few	0	O
measures	0	O
to	0	O
limit	0	O
car	0	O
traffic	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
summer	0	O
months	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
unacceptable	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
government	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
or	0	O
hardly	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
intervene	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
knowledge	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
green	0	O
ministers	0	O
have	0	O
not	0	O
(	0	O
yet	0	O
)	0	O
got	0	O
it	0	O
through	0	O
.	0	O

section	0	O

What	0	O
exactly	0	O
is	0	O
your	0	O
requirement	0	O
?	0	O

(	0	O
PJB	0	O
)	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
edition	0	O

page	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
his	0	O
own	0	O
account	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
made	0	O
a	0	O
total	0	O
of	0	O
fifteen	0	O
telephone	0	O
calls	0	O
,	0	O
including	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
cabinets	0	O
and	0	O
departments	0	O
of	0	O
Traffic	1	B-ORG
,	1	I-ORG
Economic	1	I-ORG
Affairs	1	I-ORG
and	1	I-ORG
Finance	1	E-ORG
.	0	O

My	0	O
assignment	0	O
was	0	O
limited	0	O
to	0	O
signaling	0	O
possible	0	O
political	0	O
problems	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
According	0	O
to	0	O
Gantman	1	S-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
corporate	0	O
tax	0	O
change	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
gains	0	O
tax	0	O
regime	0	O
was	0	O
abnormally	0	O
slow	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Larmuseau	2	S-PER
.	0	O

Larmuseau	1	S-PER
replied	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
find	0	O
Gantman	2	B-PER
's	2	E-PER
's	0	O
question	0	O
unjustified	0	O
and	0	O
credible	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O

''	0	O
It	0	O
was	0	O
so	0	O
long	0	O
ago	0	O
,	0	O
I	0	O
hardly	0	O
remember	0	O
anything	0	O
about	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

Hendrik	1	B-PER
Larmuseau	1	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
former	0	O
adviser	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
socio	0	O
economic	0	O
cabinet	0	O
of	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
Jean	2	B-PER
Luc	2	I-PER
Dehaene	2	E-PER
(	0	O
CVP	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
stated	0	O
on	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
before	0	O
the	0	O
ship	0	O
credit	0	O
investigation	0	O
committee	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
Antwerp	4	S-MISC
lawyer	0	O
André	5	B-PER
Gantman	5	E-PER
was	0	O
also	0	O
active	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
's	0	O
cabinet	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
lobbyist	0	O
for	0	O
shipowner	0	O
Rosenfeld	6	S-PER
.	0	O

section	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
him	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
received	0	O
no	0	O
response	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
of	1	B-ORG
Finance	1	E-ORG
cabinet	0	O
.	0	O

†	0	O

†	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O

†	0	O

†	0	O

General	1	S-ORG

Larmuseau	1	S-PER
had	0	O
two	0	O
further	0	O
meetings	0	O
with	0	O
Gantman	2	S-PER
in	0	O
the	0	O
spring	0	O
of	0	O
1994	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
result	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
investigation	0	O
,	0	O
was	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
inform	0	O
the	0	O
lawyer	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
amendment	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
law	0	O
was	0	O
proceeding	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
normal	0	O
procedures	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
After	0	O
all	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
cabinet	0	O
you	0	O
are	0	O
constantly	0	O
approached	0	O
by	0	O
all	0	O
kinds	0	O
of	0	O
people	0	O
who	0	O
need	0	O
something	0	O
.	0	O

Gantman	1	S-PER
lobbied	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
Dehaene	2	S-PER

Karel	1	B-PER
De	1	I-PER
Gucht	1	E-PER
:	0	O
'	0	O
Did	0	O
you	0	O
do	0	O
this	0	O
for	0	O
every	0	O
stranger	0	O
?	0	O
†	0	O

''	0	O
He	0	O
complained	0	O
about	0	O
this	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Did	0	O
you	0	O
do	0	O
this	0	O
for	0	O
every	0	O
stranger	0	O
?	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
asked	0	O
the	0	O
witness	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
Larmuseau	1	S-PER
could	0	O
hardly	0	O
remember	0	O
anything	0	O
about	0	O
that	0	O
working	0	O
group	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Larmuseau	1	S-PER
,	0	O
Gantman	2	S-PER
first	0	O
appeared	0	O
in	0	O
his	0	O
office	0	O
in	0	O
April	0	O
1994	0	O
,	0	O
without	0	O
having	0	O
made	0	O
a	0	O
prior	0	O
telephone	0	O
appointment	0	O
.	0	O

Brussels	1	S-LOC

''	0	O
It	0	O
seemed	0	O
like	0	O
an	0	O
important	0	O
problem	0	O
,	0	O
I	0	O
judged	0	O
it	0	O
my	0	O
duty	0	O
to	0	O
check	0	O
it	0	O
.	0	O

publication	0	O
date	0	O

I	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
participate	0	O
in	0	O
negotiations	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
tax	0	O
problem	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
also	0	O
personally	0	O
informed	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
Dehaene	1	S-PER
of	0	O
the	0	O
problem	0	O
raised	0	O
by	0	O
Gantman	2	S-PER
.	0	O

author	0	O

The	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
's	0	O
cabinet	0	O
adviser	0	O
immediately	0	O
sprang	0	O
into	0	O
action	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
have	0	O
passively	0	O
attended	0	O
one	0	O
or	0	O
two	0	O
meetings	0	O
at	0	O
most	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
then	0	O
minister	0	O
of	0	O
Finance	1	S-ORG
Philippe	2	B-PER
Maystadt	2	E-PER
(	0	O
PSC	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
blocked	0	O
the	0	O
file	0	O
,	0	O
Gantman	4	S-PER
seemed	0	O
to	0	O
insinuate	0	O
.	0	O

Georges	1	B-PER
Carpenter	1	E-PER

Commissioner	0	O
Karel	1	B-PER
De	1	I-PER
Gucht	1	E-PER
(	0	O
VLD	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
was	0	O
amazed	0	O
at	0	O
so	0	O
much	0	O
zeal	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
GT	1	S-MISC
)	0	O

Friday	0	O
,	0	O
June	0	O
2	0	O
,	0	O
2000	0	O

Journal	1	S-ORG

Own	0	O
reporting	0	O

During	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
period	0	O
Larmuseau	1	S-PER
was	0	O
also	0	O
a	0	O
member	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
inter	0	O
cabinet	0	O
group	0	O
around	0	O
ABC	2	B-ORG
Containerline	2	E-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
was	0	O
created	0	O
specifically	0	O
to	0	O
solve	0	O
the	0	O
tax	0	O
problems	0	O
that	0	O
arose	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
context	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
proposed	0	O
takeover	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
shipping	0	O
company	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
American	3	S-MISC
scammer	0	O
Gary	4	B-PER
Blonder	4	E-PER
.	0	O

-DOCSTART-	0	O
17	0	O

The	0	O
International	1	B-ORG
Monetary	1	I-ORG
Fund	1	E-ORG
should	0	O
listen	0	O
more	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
people	0	O
and	0	O
impose	0	O
its	0	O
will	0	O
less	0	O
on	0	O
countries	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
IMF	1	S-ORG
often	0	O
tends	0	O
to	0	O
admonish	0	O
countries	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
lessons	0	O
learned	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
financial	0	O
crises	0	O
in	0	O
Asia	2	S-LOC
is	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
needs	0	O
to	0	O
listen	0	O
better	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
IMF	1	S-ORG
itself	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
driving	0	O
force	0	O
behind	0	O
such	0	O
changes	0	O
.	0	O

Köhler	1	S-PER
has	0	O
also	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
would	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
talk	0	O
about	0	O
an	0	O
Asian	2	B-ORG
Monetary	2	I-ORG
Fund	2	E-ORG
,	0	O
a	0	O
plan	0	O
about	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
large	0	O
industrialized	0	O
countries	0	O
and	0	O
those	0	O
responsible	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
IMF	3	S-ORG
have	0	O
been	0	O
squabbling	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
long	0	O
time	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
led	0	O
to	0	O
calls	0	O
within	0	O
the	0	O
fund	0	O
for	0	O
policy	0	O
changes	0	O
.	0	O

People	0	O
