Melbourne	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Australia	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
General	1	S-ORG
State	0	O
Lawyer	0	O
,	0	O
Daryl	2	B-PER
Williams	2	E-PER
,	0	O
stressed	0	O
today	0	O
the	0	O
need	0	O
to	0	O
take	0	O
measures	0	O
to	0	O
protect	0	O
the	0	O
Australian	3	S-MISC
judicial	0	O
system	0	O
against	0	O
a	0	O
website	0	O
that	0	O
makes	0	O
it	0	O
impossible	0	O
to	0	O
comply	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
basic	0	O
principles	0	O
of	0	O
Act	4	S-MISC
.	0	O

Lawyer	0	O
General	1	S-ORG
's	0	O
request	0	O
takes	0	O
place	0	O
after	0	O
a	0	O
judge	0	O
from	0	O
Supreme	2	B-ORG
Court	2	E-ORG
of	0	O
the	0	O
state	0	O
of	0	O
Victoria	3	S-LOC
(	0	O
Australia	4	S-LOC
)	0	O
was	0	O
forced	0	O
to	0	O
dissolve	0	O
a	0	O
popular	0	O
jury	0	O
and	0	O
suspend	0	O
the	0	O
process	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
argument	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
defense	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
people	0	O
who	0	O
composed	0	O
it	0	O
could	0	O
have	0	O
obtained	0	O
information	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
defendant	0	O
through	0	O
the	0	O
CrimeNet	5	S-ORG
page	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
website	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
in	0	O
existence	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
month	0	O
,	0	O
during	0	O
which	0	O
time	0	O
it	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
visited	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
a	0	O
million	0	O
times	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
provides	0	O
information	0	O
on	0	O
thousands	0	O
of	0	O
crimes	0	O
and	0	O
criminals	0	O
already	0	O
prosecuted	0	O
or	0	O
still	0	O
being	0	O
persecuted	0	O
,	0	O
data	0	O
that	0	O
comes	0	O
from	0	O
newspaper	0	O
articles	0	O
and	0	O
court	0	O
files	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
his	0	O
part	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
General	0	O
Counsel	0	O
of	0	O
Victoria	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Rob	2	B-PER
Hulls	2	E-PER
,	0	O
indicated	0	O
that	0	O
there	0	O
is	0	O
no	0	O
one	0	O
to	0	O
control	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
information	0	O
contained	0	O
in	0	O
CrimeNet	3	S-ORG
is	0	O
true	0	O
.	0	O

Hulls	1	S-PER
pointed	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
legal	0	O
system	0	O
of	0	O
Commonwealth	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
on	0	O
which	0	O
Australian	3	S-MISC
justice	0	O
is	0	O
based	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
essential	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
person	0	O
be	0	O
judged	0	O
solely	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
basis	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
evidence	0	O
presented	0	O
before	0	O
the	0	O
judge	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
aforementioned	0	O
website	0	O
is	0	O
also	0	O
considered	0	O
the	0	O
cause	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
premature	0	O
conclusion	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
murder	0	O
case	0	O
recently	0	O
tried	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
of	0	O
Melbourne	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
capital	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
state	0	O
of	0	O
Victoria	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

Izquierda	1	B-ORG
Unida	1	I-ORG
de	1	I-ORG
Santander	1	E-ORG
today	0	O
presented	0	O
its	0	O
new	0	O
quarterly	0	O
bulletin	0	O
''	0	O
Ciudad	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
publication	0	O
of	0	O
which	0	O
10,000	0	O
copies	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
distributed	0	O
preferably	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
neighborhoods	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
municipality	0	O
where	0	O
the	0	O
collation	0	O
has	0	O
the	0	O
greatest	0	O
citizen	0	O
support	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
spokesperson	0	O
for	0	O
IU	1	B-ORG
Municipal	1	I-ORG
Political	1	I-ORG
Council	1	E-ORG
in	0	O
Santander	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Ernesto	3	B-PER
Gómez	3	I-PER
de	3	I-PER
la	3	I-PER
Hera	3	E-PER
,	0	O
explained	0	O
today	0	O
at	0	O
a	0	O
press	0	O
conference	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
bulletin	0	O
seeks	0	O
,	0	O
rather	0	O
than	0	O
inform	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
open	0	O
spaces	0	O
for	0	O
debate	0	O
and	0	O
serve	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
seed	0	O
of	0	O
political	0	O
mobilization	0	O
''	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
.	0	O

Gómez	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
la	1	I-PER
Hera	1	E-PER
commented	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
contents	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
publication	0	O
''	0	O
Ciudad	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
respond	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
program	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
led	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
candidate	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
elections	0	O
of	0	O
1999	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
IU	3	S-ORG
lost	0	O
its	0	O
representation	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
City	0	O
Council	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
he	0	O
hoped	0	O
that	0	O
its	0	O
dissemination	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
broader	0	O
once	0	O
the	0	O
coalition	0	O
solves	0	O
its	0	O
economic	0	O
crisis	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
the	0	O
moment	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
Ciudad	1	S-LOC
''	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
distributed	0	O
preferentially	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
neighborhoods	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
IU	2	S-ORG
voters	0	O
,	0	O
among	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
municipal	0	O
spokesman	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
coalition	0	O
cited	0	O
the	0	O
north	0	O
side	0	O
of	0	O
Alta	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Cazoña	4	S-LOC
streets	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
area	0	O
between	0	O
Castilla	5	S-LOC
and	0	O
Hermida	6	S-LOC
streets	0	O
.	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Ciudad	1	S-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
bulletin	0	O
made	0	O
up	0	O
of	0	O
two	0	O
pages	0	O
folded	0	O
in	0	O
half	0	O
,	0	O
hits	0	O
the	0	O
streets	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
first	0	O
issue	0	O
criticizing	0	O
the	0	O
construction	0	O
works	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
underground	0	O
car	0	O
parks	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
inconvenience	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
causing	0	O
to	0	O
residents	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
way	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
they	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
exploited	0	O
.	0	O

Gómez	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
la	1	I-PER
Hera	1	E-PER
believes	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
PP	2	S-ORG
's	0	O
policy	0	O
of	0	O
making	0	O
money	0	O
from	0	O
absolutely	0	O
everything	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
money	0	O
is	0	O
distributed	0	O
mainly	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
friends	0	O
''	0	O
has	0	O
turned	0	O
Santander	3	S-LOC
into	0	O
''	0	O
a	0	O
trap	0	O
full	0	O
of	0	O
holes	0	O
,	0	O
when	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
cities	0	O
of	0	O
Western	4	B-LOC
Europe	4	E-LOC
are	0	O
trying	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
their	0	O
helmets	0	O
more	0	O
livable	0	O
cities	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
his	0	O
opinion	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
City	0	O
Council	0	O
's	0	O
reasons	0	O
for	0	O
carrying	0	O
out	0	O
these	0	O
works	0	O
are	0	O
''	0	O
financial	0	O
,	0	O
mercenary	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
they	0	O
have	0	O
nothing	0	O
to	0	O
do	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
of	0	O
Santander	1	S-LOC
or	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
well	0	O
being	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
vast	0	O
majority	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
population	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

EFE	1	S-ORG
Cantabria	2	B-LOC
Frankfurt	2	E-LOC
(	0	O
RFA	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFECOM	4	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
German	1	S-MISC
telephony	0	O
group	0	O
Deutsche	2	B-ORG
Telekom	2	E-ORG
has	0	O
acquired	0	O
the	0	O
remaining	0	O
50	0	O
percent	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Swiss	3	S-MISC
telecommunications	0	O
operator	0	O
Multilink	4	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
until	0	O
now	0	O
owned	0	O
France	5	B-ORG
Telecom	5	E-ORG
,	0	O
and	0	O
has	0	O
become	0	O
its	0	O
sole	0	O
owner	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
German	6	S-MISC
company	0	O
reported	0	O
today	0	O
,	0	O
Thursday	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
return	0	O
,	0	O
Deutsche	1	B-ORG
Telekom	1	E-ORG
will	0	O
sell	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
French	2	S-MISC
consortium	0	O
its	0	O
25	0	O
per	0	O
cent	0	O
stake	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
British	3	S-MISC
MetroHoldings	4	S-ORG
joint	0	O
venture	0	O
.	0	O

Multilink	1	S-ORG
was	0	O
created	0	O
in	0	O
1998	0	O
and	0	O
offers	0	O
telephone	0	O
and	0	O
data	0	O
transmission	0	O
services	0	O
in	0	O
Switzerland	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
abroad	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
having	0	O
its	0	O
own	0	O
urban	0	O
fiber	0	O
optic	0	O
network	0	O
.	0	O

Deutsche	1	B-ORG
Telekom	1	E-ORG
described	0	O
this	0	O
purchase	0	O
,	0	O
whose	0	O
price	0	O
was	0	O
not	0	O
specified	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
another	0	O
step	0	O
towards	0	O
its	0	O
internationalization	0	O
through	0	O
majority	0	O
acquisitions	0	O
aimed	0	O
at	0	O
having	0	O
control	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
management	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
companies	0	O
.	0	O

====================================================	0	O
==========	0	O

-	0	O

Merida	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Junta	1	B-ORG
de	1	I-ORG
Extremadura	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Juan	2	B-PER
Carlos	2	I-PER
Rodríguez	2	I-PER
Ibarra	2	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
receive	0	O
relatives	0	O
of	0	O
several	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
convicted	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Lasa	4	B-PER
Zabala	4	E-PER
''	0	O
process	0	O
,	0	O
including	0	O
Lourdes	5	B-PER
Díez	5	I-PER
Urraca	5	E-PER
,	0	O
wife	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
former	0	O
civil	0	O
governor	0	O
of	0	O
Guipúzcoa	6	S-LOC
Julen	7	B-PER
Elgorriaga	7	E-PER
;	0	O
and	0	O
Antonio	8	B-PER
Rodríguez	8	I-PER
Galindo	8	E-PER
,	0	O
brother	0	O
of	0	O
general	0	O
Enrique	9	B-PER
Rodríguez	9	I-PER
Galindo	9	E-PER
.	0	O

(	0	O
with	0	O
photo	0	O
)	0	O
(	0	O
FULL	0	O
ASSEMBLY	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Merida	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Assembly	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Extremadura	1	E-ORG
Plenary	0	O
will	0	O
debate	0	O
,	0	O
among	0	O
others	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
non	0	O
law	0	O
proposal	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
groups	0	O
of	0	O
PSOE	2	B-ORG
NI	2	E-ORG
,	0	O
PP	3	S-ORG
and	0	O
Mixto	4	B-ORG
Deputies	4	I-ORG
of	4	I-ORG
IU	4	E-ORG
in	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
central	0	O
government	0	O
is	0	O
urged	0	O
to	0	O
enact	0	O
a	0	O
Ministerial	5	B-MISC
Order	5	E-MISC
that	0	O
includes	0	O
the	0	O
regionalization	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
base	0	O
area	0	O
for	0	O
corn	0	O
cultivation	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
ENTREPRENEURS	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Merida	1	S-ORG
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
Economy	1	B-ORG
,	1	I-ORG
Industry	1	I-ORG
.	1	I-ORG
Trade	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Manuel	2	B-PER
Amigo	2	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
presidents	0	O
of	0	O
Caja	3	B-ORG
Extremadura	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
Caja	4	B-ORG
Badajoz	4	E-ORG
,	0	O
Jesús	5	B-PER
Medina	5	E-PER
and	0	O
José	6	B-PER
Manuel	6	I-PER
Sánchez	6	I-PER
Rojas	6	E-PER
,	0	O
respectively	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
sign	0	O
a	0	O
collaboration	0	O
agreement	0	O
to	0	O
finance	0	O
business	0	O
projects	0	O
of	0	O
young	0	O
entrepreneurs	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
CARLOS	1	B-PER
V	1	E-PER
CONGRESS	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Jaraíz	1	B-PER
de	1	I-PER
la	1	I-PER
Vera	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Cáceres	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Hoffmeyer	1	S-LOC
''	0	O
will	0	O
host	0	O
the	0	O
inauguration	0	O
and	0	O
first	0	O
session	0	O
of	0	O
Congress	2	B-MISC
of	2	I-MISC
Modern	2	I-MISC
History	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
Carlos	3	B-PER
.	3	E-PER
and	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
era	0	O
.	0	O
1500	0	O
1558	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
is	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
commemorative	0	O
acts	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
V	0	O
Centenary	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
birth	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
emperor	0	O
.	0	O

Informative	0	O
agenda	0	O
:	0	O
10:00	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Junta	1	B-ORG
de	1	I-ORG
Extremadura	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Juan	2	B-PER
Carlos	2	I-PER
Rodríguez	2	I-PER
Ibarra	2	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
receive	0	O
relatives	0	O
of	0	O
several	0	O
of	0	O
those	0	O
convicted	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Lasa	4	B-PER
Zabala	4	E-PER
''	0	O
process	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
Government	3	B-ORG
Presidency	3	E-ORG
headquarters	0	O
in	0	O
Extremadura	0	O
.	0	O

10:00	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
Economy	1	B-ORG
,	1	I-ORG
Industry	1	I-ORG
.	1	I-ORG
Trade	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Manuel	2	B-PER
Amigo	2	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
presidents	0	O
of	0	O
Caja	3	B-ORG
Extremadura	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
Caja	4	B-ORG
Badajoz	4	E-ORG
,	0	O
Jesús	5	B-PER
Medina	5	E-PER
and	0	O
José	6	B-PER
Manuel	6	I-PER
Sánchez	6	I-PER
Rojas	6	E-PER
,	0	O
respectively	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
sign	0	O
a	0	O
collaboration	0	O
agreement	0	O
.	0	O

10:00	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Jaraíz	1	B-LOC
de	1	I-LOC
la	1	I-LOC
Vera	1	E-LOC
(	0	O
Cáceres	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Congress	1	S-MISC
''	0	O
Carlos	2	B-PER
.	2	E-PER
and	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
epoch	0	O
.	0	O
1500	0	O
1558	0	O
''	0	O
will	0	O
begin	0	O
.	0	O

10:00	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
Housing	1	B-ORG
,	1	I-ORG
Urbanism	1	I-ORG
.	1	I-ORG
Transportes	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Javier	2	B-PER
Corominas	2	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
deliver	0	O
94	0	O
special	0	O
regime	0	O
homes	0	O
built	0	O
by	0	O
''	3	B-ORG
Magenta	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
La	4	B-LOC
Corchera	4	E-LOC
''	0	O
.	0	O

10:30	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Plasencia	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Cáceres	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
mayor	0	O
,	0	O
José	1	B-PER
Luis	1	I-PER
Díez	1	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
speak	0	O
on	0	O
various	0	O
matters	0	O
of	0	O
municipal	0	O
interest	0	O
.	0	O

11:00	0	O
a.m.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

A	0	O
session	0	O
of	0	O
Plenary	1	S-ORG
of	0	O
Assembly	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
Extremadura	2	E-ORG
will	0	O
be	0	O
held	0	O
.	0	O

12:00	0	O
p.m.	0	O
Montijo	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Badajoz	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Minister	0	O
of	0	O
Culture	0	O
,	0	O
Francisco	1	B-PER
Muñoz	1	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
inaugurate	0	O
the	0	O
local	0	O
IV	2	B-MISC
Book	2	I-MISC
Fair	2	E-MISC
.	0	O

12:00	0	O
p.m.	0	O
Azuaga	1	S-LOC
(	0	O
Badajoz	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Inauguration	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
XIX	0	O
Extremadura	1	B-LOC
Southern	1	I-LOC
Countryside	1	I-LOC
Trade	1	I-LOC
Fair	1	E-LOC
(	0	O
FECSUR	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

12:30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Plenary	0	O
Session	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
City	0	O
Council	0	O
will	0	O
discuss	0	O
issues	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
reclassification	0	O
of	0	O
land	0	O
surrounding	0	O
the	0	O
School	1	S-ORG
''	2	B-ORG
Salesianos	2	E-ORG
''	0	O
.	0	O

8:30	0	O
p.m.	0	O
Caceres	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Minister	0	O
of	0	O
Culture	0	O
,	0	O
Francisco	1	B-PER
Muñoz	1	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
attend	0	O
the	0	O
presentation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
book	0	O
''	0	O
Beings	2	B-MISC
.	2	I-MISC
Stars	2	E-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
analyzes	0	O
the	0	O
origins	0	O
of	0	O
Universe	3	S-MISC
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
data	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
The	4	B-MISC
First	4	I-MISC
Settlers	4	I-MISC
of	4	I-MISC
Extremadura	4	E-MISC
''	0	O
research	0	O
project	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

:	0	O
h.	0	O
Merida	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

Public	0	O
television	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
information	0	O
society	0	O
,	0	O
regional	0	O
financing	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
contents	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
extracurricular	0	O
day	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
creation	0	O
of	0	O
an	0	O
Consultative	1	B-ORG
Council	1	E-ORG
are	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
issues	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
negotiated	0	O
starting	0	O
tomorrow	0	O
by	0	O
PP	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Junta	3	B-ORG
de	3	I-ORG
Extremadura	3	E-ORG
to	0	O
reach	0	O
a	0	O
regional	0	O
pact	0	O
on	0	O
13	0	O
issues	0	O
of	0	O
interest	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

:	0	O
h.	0	O
Caceres	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
activities	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
Agora	1	B-ORG
.	1	E-ORG
The	0	O
peninsular	0	O
debate	0	O
''	0	O
will	0	O
continue	0	O
.	0	O

By	0	O
Caius	1	B-PER
Apicius	1	E-PER
Madrid	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

A	0	O
vice	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
anyone	0	O
who	0	O
considers	0	O
himself	0	O
a	0	O
gastronome	0	O
and	0	O
aspires	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
recognized	0	O
as	0	O
such	0	O
should	0	O
never	0	O
incur	0	O
is	0	O
that	0	O
of	0	O
jingoism	0	O
,	0	O
understood	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
excessive	0	O
and	0	O
inopportune	0	O
display	0	O
of	0	O
patriotism	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
gastronome	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
stateless	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
must	0	O
flee	0	O
like	0	O
the	0	O
plague	0	O
of	0	O
chauvinism	0	O
.	0	O

Years	0	O
ago	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
travel	0	O
books	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Nobel	1	B-MISC
Prize	1	I-MISC
winner	1	I-MISC
for	1	I-MISC
Literature	1	E-MISC
Camilo	2	B-PER
José	2	I-PER
Cela	2	E-PER
affirmed	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
patriot	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
who	0	O
is	0	O
proud	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
place	0	O
where	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
born	0	O
and	0	O
defends	0	O
it	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
attitude	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
he	0	O
is	0	O
right	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
the	0	O
patriotic	0	O
at	0	O
that	0	O
time	0	O
,	0	O
Cela	3	S-PER
used	0	O
the	0	O
word	0	O
'nationalist	0	O
'	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
that	0	O
proclaims	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
wind	0	O
.	0	O
It	0	O
is	0	O
clear	0	O
that	0	O
his	0	O
native	0	O
land	0	O
is	0	O
superior	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
others	0	O
in	0	O
everything	0	O
,	0	O
something	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
Cela	4	S-PER
said	0	O
he	0	O
could	0	O
well	0	O
be	0	O
wrong	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
matter	0	O
of	0	O
food	0	O
,	0	O
chauvinism	0	O
abounds	0	O
too	0	O
much	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
has	0	O
no	0	O
problem	0	O
accepting	0	O
that	0	O
everyone	0	O
defends	0	O
the	0	O
cuisine	0	O
and	0	O
products	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
land	0	O
...	0	O
as	0	O
long	0	O
as	0	O
that	0	O
defense	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
imply	0	O
contempt	0	O
for	0	O
being	0	O
foreign	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
gastronomic	0	O
customs	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
homeland	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
case	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
will	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
go	0	O
from	0	O
Cela	1	S-PER
to	0	O
Antonio	2	B-PER
Machado	2	E-PER
and	0	O
remember	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
despise	0	O
what	0	O
you	0	O
ignore	0	O
...	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
problem	0	O
with	0	O
gastronomic	0	O
chauvinism	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
let	0	O
's	0	O
not	0	O
fool	0	O
ourselves	0	O
,	0	O
with	0	O
any	0	O
other	0	O
is	0	O
precisely	0	O
that	0	O
:	0	O
ignorance	0	O
.	0	O

Of	0	O
course	0	O
that	0	O
same	0	O
ignorance	0	O
can	0	O
make	0	O
many	0	O
fall	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
opposite	0	O
defect	0	O
:	0	O
the	0	O
,	0	O
let	0	O
's	0	O
say	0	O
,	0	O
papanatismo	0	O
that	0	O
makes	0	O
everything	0	O
foreign	0	O
better	0	O
for	0	O
these	0	O
citizens	0	O
.	0	O

Neither	0	O
.	0	O

A	0	O
gastronome	0	O
is	0	O
something	0	O
like	0	O
a	0	O
traveller	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
a	0	O
traveler	0	O
,	0	O
not	0	O
a	0	O
tourist	0	O
;	0	O
a	0	O
traveler	0	O
,	0	O
let	0	O
's	0	O
say	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
style	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
19th	0	O
century	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
person	0	O
full	0	O
of	0	O
curiosity	0	O
and	0	O
freed	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
far	0	O
as	0	O
possible	0	O
,	0	O
from	0	O
prejudices	0	O
,	0	O
willing	0	O
to	0	O
accept	0	O
the	0	O
good	0	O
things	0	O
of	0	O
others	0	O
without	0	O
denying	0	O
their	0	O
own	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
that	0	O
universality	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
gastronome	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
who	0	O
universalized	0	O
gastronomy	0	O
were	0	O
the	0	O
Romans	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
imply	0	O
the	0	O
renunciation	0	O
of	0	O
one	0	O
's	0	O
own	0	O
.	0	O

Much	0	O
less	0	O
the	0	O
absurd	0	O
hodgepodge	0	O
,	0	O
that	0	O
cuisine	0	O
that	0	O
today	0	O
we	0	O
call	0	O
'fusion	0	O
'	0	O
,	0	O
always	0	O
very	0	O
defensible	0	O
.	0	O
when	0	O
it	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
lead	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
in	0	O
so	0	O
many	0	O
cases	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
'	0	O
confusion	0	O
'	0	O
cooking	0	O
.	0	O

We	0	O
will	0	O
always	0	O
insist	0	O
that	0	O
a	0	O
kitchen	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
truly	0	O
great	0	O
,	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
faithful	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
land	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
also	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
time	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
it	0	O
must	0	O
,	0	O
of	0	O
course	0	O
,	0	O
be	0	O
open	0	O
to	0	O
foreign	0	O
incorporations	0	O
.	0	O

What	0	O
would	0	O
European	0	O
cuisine	0	O
be	0	O
,	0	O
for	0	O
example	0	O
,	0	O
without	0	O
potatoes	0	O
;	0	O
or	0	O
Mediterranean	0	O
cuisine	0	O
without	0	O
tomatoes	0	O
,	0	O
both	0	O
products	0	O
that	0	O
reached	0	O
the	0	O
Old	1	B-LOC
World	1	E-LOC
less	0	O
than	0	O
five	0	O
centuries	0	O
ago	0	O
...	0	O

Imagine	0	O
that	0	O
among	0	O
those	0	O
Spaniards	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
were	0	O
the	0	O
ones	0	O
who	0	O
brought	0	O
these	0	O
American	2	S-MISC
gifts	0	O
to	0	O
Europe	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
gastronomic	0	O
chauvinism	0	O
would	0	O
have	0	O
prevailed	0	O
:	0	O
potatoes	0	O
and	0	O
tomatoes	0	O
would	0	O
have	0	O
remained	0	O
botanical	0	O
curiosities	0	O
.	0	O

There	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
can	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
universal	0	O
kitchen	0	O
;	0	O
remember	0	O
that	0	O
horror	0	O
known	0	O
as	0	O
'international	0	O
cuisine	0	O
'	0	O
so	0	O
common	0	O
in	0	O
hotel	0	O
restaurants	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
neither	0	O
can	0	O
there	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
kitchen	0	O
closed	0	O
in	0	O
on	0	O
itself	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
possible	0	O
to	0	O
wonder	0	O
,	0	O
faced	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
food	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
spice	0	O
,	0	O
where	0	O
does	0	O
this	0	O
come	0	O
from	0	O
?	0	O
,	0	O
without	0	O
first	0	O
investigating	0	O
what	0	O
is	0	O
really	0	O
important	0	O
:	0	O
is	0	O
he	0	O
rich	0	O
?	0	O

Well	0	O
,	0	O
if	0	O
he	0	O
's	0	O
rich	0	O
...	0	O
go	0	O
ahead	0	O
,	0	O
wherever	0	O
he	0	O
comes	0	O
from	0	O
.	0	O

Of	0	O
course	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
must	0	O
study	0	O
how	0	O
we	0	O
adapt	0	O
this	0	O
new	0	O
product	0	O
to	0	O
our	0	O
most	0	O
established	0	O
culinary	0	O
uses	0	O
.	0	O

Thus	0	O
,	0	O
our	0	O
cuisine	0	O
evolves	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
enriched	0	O
.	0	O

Otherwise	0	O
,	0	O
closing	0	O
in	0	O
on	0	O
itself	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
ends	0	O
up	0	O
weakening	0	O
and	0	O
becoming	0	O
extinct	0	O
;	0	O
inbreeding	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
good	0	O
for	0	O
almost	0	O
anything	0	O
.	0	O

So	0	O
keep	0	O
an	0	O
open	0	O
mind	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
your	0	O
senses	0	O
even	0	O
more	0	O
so	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
,	0	O
paraphrasing	0	O
Shakespeare	1	S-PER
in	0	O
'	0	O
Hamlet	2	S-MISC
'	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
more	0	O
rich	0	O
things	0	O
in	0	O
Earth	3	S-LOC
than	0	O
your	0	O
wisdom	0	O
,	0	O
or	0	O
your	0	O
personal	0	O
experience	0	O
,	0	O
reaches	0	O
.	0	O

Do	0	O
not	0	O
become	0	O
eunuchs	0	O
of	0	O
taste	0	O
for	0	O
mere	0	O
chauvinism	0	O
:	0	O
so	0	O
many	0	O
rich	0	O
things	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
lost	0	O
...	0	O

Alcorcón	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

From	0	O
today	0	O
until	0	O
June	0	O
28	0	O
,	0	O
Museum	1	S-LOC
Art	2	S-ORG
in	3	B-LOC
glass	3	E-LOC
of	0	O
Alcorcón	4	S-LOC
hosts	0	O
an	0	O
exhibition	0	O
of	0	O
glass	0	O
sculptures	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
artist	0	O
Romanian	5	S-MISC
Edward	6	B-PER
Leibovtiz	6	E-PER
,	0	O
made	0	O
up	0	O
of	0	O
35	0	O
pieces	0	O
of	0	O
different	0	O
formats	0	O
and	0	O
whose	0	O
size	0	O
ranges	0	O
between	0	O
40	0	O
centimeters	0	O
and	0	O
2	0	O
meters	0	O
of	0	O
some	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
figures	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
pieces	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
exhibition	0	O
,	0	O
organized	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Department	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Culture	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
have	0	O
a	0	O
figurative	0	O
character	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
them	0	O
faces	0	O
,	0	O
bodies	0	O
and	0	O
different	0	O
fantasies	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
appreciated	0	O
,	0	O
even	0	O
showing	0	O
erotic	0	O
aspects	0	O
.	0	O

Edward	1	B-PER
Leibovitz	1	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
currently	0	O
resides	0	O
in	0	O
Belgium	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
has	0	O
exhibited	0	O
in	0	O
his	0	O
30	0	O
years	0	O
of	0	O
work	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
contemporary	0	O
glass	0	O
sculptor	0	O
in	0	O
numerous	0	O
European	0	O
,	0	O
American	0	O
and	0	O
Asian	0	O
museums	0	O
in	0	O
countries	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
Japan	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
Germany	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
France	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
Belgium	6	S-LOC
or	0	O
Israel	7	S-LOC
.	0	O

Those	0	O
attending	0	O
the	0	O
exhibition	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
will	0	O
open	0	O
this	0	O
afternoon	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
enjoy	0	O
the	0	O
different	0	O
works	0	O
by	0	O
Leibovitz	1	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
points	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
I	0	O
like	0	O
to	0	O
work	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
composition	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
piece	0	O
and	0	O
I	0	O
try	0	O
to	0	O
convey	0	O
the	0	O
fantasy	0	O
of	0	O
life	0	O
with	0	O
an	0	O
absurd	0	O
aspect	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
inauguration	0	O
,	0	O
scheduled	0	O
for	0	O
8:00	0	O
pm	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
attended	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
artist	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
Councilor	0	O
for	0	O
Culture	0	O
,	0	O
Francisco	1	B-PER
Torres	1	E-PER
,	0	O
from	0	O
whose	0	O
Council	2	S-ORG
an	0	O
invitation	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
sent	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
ambassadors	0	O
of	0	O
Belgium	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
Israel	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
Romania	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
consulates	0	O
that	0	O
,	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
municipal	0	O
sources	0	O
,	0	O
have	0	O
confirmed	0	O
their	0	O
presence	0	O
through	0	O
different	0	O
representatives	0	O
.	0	O

Madrid	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFECOM	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
maximum	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
Terra	1	S-ORG
for	0	O
the	0	O
exchange	0	O
of	0	O
shares	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
including	0	O
the	0	O
options	0	O
on	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
workers	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
company	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
exceed	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
yesterday	0	O
's	0	O
closing	0	O
price	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
stock	0	O
market	0	O
(	0	O
50.9	0	O
pesetas	0	O
per	0	O
share	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
2,887	0	O
billion	0	O
pesetas	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
stated	0	O
in	0	O
an	0	O
explanatory	0	O
note	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Telefónica	1	S-ORG
group	0	O
to	0	O
National	2	B-ORG
Securities	2	I-ORG
Market	2	I-ORG
Commission	2	E-ORG
on	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
increases	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
submitted	0	O
for	0	O
approval	0	O
by	0	O
General	3	B-ORG
Shareholders	3	I-ORG
'	3	I-ORG
Meeting	3	E-ORG
in	0	O
June	0	O
to	0	O
carry	0	O
out	0	O
the	0	O
operation	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
subsidiary	0	O
Terra	4	B-ORG
Network	4	E-ORG
on	0	O
the	0	O
purchase	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	5	S-ORG
,	0	O
Internet	6	S-ORG
's	0	O
American	0	O
portal	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
that	0	O
note	0	O
of	0	O
clarification	0	O
,	0	O
Telefónica	1	S-ORG
indicates	0	O
that	0	O
these	0	O
are	0	O
maximum	0	O
capital	0	O
increases	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
cover	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
exchange	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
has	0	O
been	0	O
carried	0	O
out	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
says	0	O
,	0	O
taking	0	O
into	0	O
account	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
American	0	O
company	0	O
has	0	O
112,192,815	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
options	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
acquisition	0	O
of	0	O
assets	0	O
amounting	0	O
to	0	O
9.7	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
,	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
employees	0	O
have	0	O
stock	0	O
option	0	O
plans	0	O
for	0	O
23,640,000	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
at	0	O
closing	0	O
with	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
there	0	O
may	0	O
be	0	O
an	0	O
additional	0	O
7,440,000	0	O
stock	0	O
options	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
note	0	O
states	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
maximum	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
shares	0	O
that	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
issued	0	O
in	0	O
total	0	O
for	0	O
their	0	O
exchange	0	O
with	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
will	0	O
not	0	O
exceed	0	O
158,568,703	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
exchanged	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
maximum	0	O
of	0	O
2.15	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Spanish	0	O
company	0	O
each	0	O
.	0	O

Regarding	0	O
the	0	O
issuance	0	O
of	0	O
38,346,984	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
warrants	0	O
(	0	O
rights	0	O
)	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
purchase	0	O
of	0	O
options	0	O
on	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
employees	0	O
and	0	O
which	0	O
could	0	O
entail	0	O
a	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
82.45	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
text	0	O
clarifies	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
maximum	0	O
number	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
already	0	O
included	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
35.48	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
submitted	0	O
for	0	O
approval	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
shareholders	0	O
meeting	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
as	0	O
of	0	O
yesterday	0	O
would	0	O
amount	0	O
to	0	O
300,514	0	O
million	0	O
pesetas	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
carried	0	O
out	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
62	0	O
euros	0	O
higher	0	O
than	0	O
the	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
days	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
stock	0	O
market	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
agreed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
is	0	O
signed	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
Terra	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
currently	0	O
listed	0	O
below	0	O
62	0	O
euros	0	O
could	0	O
cause	0	O
the	0	O
operator	0	O
's	0	O
shareholders	0	O
not	0	O
to	0	O
attend	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
would	0	O
force	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
to	0	O
also	0	O
subscribe	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
how	0	O
it	0	O
appears	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	3	S-ORG
.	0	O

This	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
explains	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
result	0	O
of	0	O
dividing	0	O
the	0	O
amount	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
committed	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
2,200	0	O
million	0	O
euros	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
issue	0	O
.	0	O

Madrid	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
maximum	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
Terra	1	S-ORG
for	0	O
the	0	O
exchange	0	O
of	0	O
shares	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
including	0	O
the	0	O
options	0	O
on	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
workers	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
company	0	O
,	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
exceed	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
which	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
yesterday	0	O
's	0	O
closing	0	O
price	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
stock	0	O
market	0	O
(	0	O
50.9	0	O
pesetas	0	O
per	0	O
share	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
2,887	0	O
billion	0	O
pesetas	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
stated	0	O
in	0	O
an	0	O
explanatory	0	O
note	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Telefónica	1	S-ORG
group	0	O
to	0	O
National	2	B-ORG
Securities	2	I-ORG
Market	2	I-ORG
Commission	2	E-ORG
on	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
increases	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
submitted	0	O
for	0	O
approval	0	O
by	0	O
General	3	B-ORG
Shareholders	3	I-ORG
'	3	I-ORG
Meeting	3	E-ORG
in	0	O
June	0	O
to	0	O
carry	0	O
out	0	O
the	0	O
operation	0	O
of	0	O
its	0	O
subsidiary	0	O
Terra	4	B-ORG
Network	4	E-ORG
on	0	O
the	0	O
purchase	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	5	S-ORG
,	0	O
Internet	6	S-ORG
's	0	O
American	0	O
portal	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
that	0	O
note	0	O
of	0	O
clarification	0	O
,	0	O
Telefónica	1	S-ORG
indicates	0	O
that	0	O
these	0	O
are	0	O
maximum	0	O
capital	0	O
increases	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
cover	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
exchange	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
has	0	O
been	0	O
carried	0	O
out	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
says	0	O
,	0	O
taking	0	O
into	0	O
account	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
American	0	O
company	0	O
has	0	O
112,192,815	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
options	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
acquisition	0	O
of	0	O
assets	0	O
amounting	0	O
to	0	O
9.7	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
addition	0	O
,	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
employees	0	O
have	0	O
stock	0	O
option	0	O
plans	0	O
for	0	O
23,640,000	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
at	0	O
closing	0	O
with	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
there	0	O
may	0	O
be	0	O
an	0	O
additional	0	O
7,440,000	0	O
stock	0	O
options	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
note	0	O
states	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
maximum	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
shares	0	O
that	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
issued	0	O
in	0	O
total	0	O
for	0	O
their	0	O
exchange	0	O
with	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
will	0	O
not	0	O
exceed	0	O
158,568,703	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
exchanged	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
maximum	0	O
of	0	O
2.15	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Spanish	0	O
company	0	O
each	0	O
.	0	O

Regarding	0	O
the	0	O
issuance	0	O
of	0	O
38,346,984	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
warrants	0	O
(	0	O
rights	0	O
)	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
purchase	0	O
of	0	O
options	0	O
on	0	O
shares	0	O
of	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
employees	0	O
and	0	O
which	0	O
could	0	O
entail	0	O
a	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
82.45	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
text	0	O
clarifies	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
maximum	0	O
number	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
already	0	O
included	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
340,922,712	0	O
shares	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
35.48	0	O
million	0	O
shares	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
submitted	0	O
for	0	O
approval	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
shareholders	0	O
meeting	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
as	0	O
of	0	O
yesterday	0	O
would	0	O
amount	0	O
to	0	O
300,514	0	O
million	0	O
pesetas	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
carried	0	O
out	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
62	0	O
euros	0	O
higher	0	O
than	0	O
the	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
days	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
stock	0	O
market	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
agreed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
as	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
price	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
is	0	O
signed	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
Terra	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
currently	0	O
listed	0	O
below	0	O
62	0	O
euros	0	O
could	0	O
cause	0	O
the	0	O
operator	0	O
's	0	O
shareholders	0	O
not	0	O
to	0	O
attend	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
would	0	O
force	0	O
Telefónica	2	S-ORG
to	0	O
also	0	O
subscribe	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
how	0	O
it	0	O
appears	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
with	0	O
Lycos	3	S-ORG
.	0	O

This	0	O
increase	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
explains	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
result	0	O
of	0	O
dividing	0	O
the	0	O
amount	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
committed	0	O
increase	0	O
of	0	O
2,200	0	O
million	0	O
euros	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
issue	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
DUKE	1	B-LOC
LUGO	1	E-LOC
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Padron	1	S-LOC
Lugo	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Infanta	0	O
Elena	1	S-PER
and	0	O
her	0	O
husband	0	O
Jaime	2	B-PER
de	2	I-PER
Marichalar	2	E-PER
,	0	O
dukes	0	O
of	0	O
Lugo	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
begin	0	O
a	0	O
two	0	O
day	0	O
visit	0	O
to	0	O
Galicia	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
expected	0	O
to	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
addition	0	O
to	0	O
inaugurating	0	O
a	0	O
classroom	0	O
of	0	O
Cela	5	B-ORG
Foundation	5	E-ORG
,	0	O
participate	0	O
in	0	O
an	0	O
act	0	O
of	0	O
declaration	0	O
of	0	O
support	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Roman	0	O
wall	0	O
of	0	O
Lugo	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
World	0	O
Heritage	0	O
Site	0	O
.	0	O

(	0	O
XUNTA	1	B-ORG
COUNCIL	1	E-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Xunta	1	S-ORG
will	0	O
report	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
agreements	0	O
reached	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
council	0	O
of	0	O
Galician	2	B-ORG
Government	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

(	0	O
BNG	1	B-ORG
GROUP	1	E-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Madrid	1	S-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
deputies	0	O
of	0	O
BNG	1	S-ORG
present	0	O
in	0	O
Constitutional	2	S-ORG
the	0	O
appeal	0	O
for	0	O
having	0	O
been	0	O
denied	0	O
obtaining	0	O
their	0	O
own	0	O
group	0	O
(	0	O
PP	3	B-ORG
CONGRESOS	3	E-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Santiago	1	S-LOC
/	0	O
A	2	B-LOC
Coruña	2	E-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
secretary	0	O
of	0	O
PP	1	S-ORG
Galician	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
Jesús	3	B-PER
Palmou	3	E-PER
,	0	O
offers	0	O
a	0	O
statement	0	O
to	0	O
EFE	4	S-ORG
to	0	O
explain	0	O
the	0	O
details	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
provincial	0	O
congresses	0	O
this	0	O
weekend	0	O
in	0	O
A	5	B-LOC
Coruña	5	E-LOC
and	0	O
Pontevedra	6	S-LOC
.	0	O

(	0	O
PHOTOGRAPHY	0	O
EXHIBITION	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

A	1	B-LOC
Coruna	1	E-LOC
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Museum	1	B-LOC
of	1	I-LOC
Fine	1	I-LOC
Arts	1	E-LOC
of	0	O
A	2	B-LOC
Coruña	2	E-LOC
inaugurates	0	O
the	0	O
photographic	0	O
exhibition	0	O
''	0	O
Emmanuel	3	B-PER
Souguez	3	I-PER
.	3	E-PER
Photographs	0	O
1928	0	O
1958	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

GREETINGS	0	O
.	0	O

EFE	1	B-ORG
GALICIA	1	E-ORG
by	0	O
Kathy	2	B-PER
Seleme	2	E-PER
Beirut	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	4	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
22	0	O
years	0	O
of	0	O
Israeli	1	S-MISC
occupation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanese	2	S-MISC
south	0	O
ended	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
few	0	O
hours	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
underlying	0	O
problems	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	3	S-LOC
persist	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
country	0	O
still	0	O
hostage	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
two	0	O
powerful	0	O
neighbors	0	O
,	0	O
Israel	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
Syria	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
who	0	O
can	0	O
use	0	O
it	0	O
at	0	O
any	0	O
time	0	O
for	0	O
their	0	O
interests	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Israeli	1	S-MISC
withdrawal	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
,	0	O
though	0	O
planned	0	O
and	0	O
announced	0	O
,	0	O
caught	0	O
everyone	0	O
off	0	O
guard	0	O
by	0	O
its	0	O
haste	0	O
,	0	O
six	0	O
weeks	0	O
earlier	0	O
than	0	O
announced	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Israel	2	S-LOC
Government	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
chaotic	0	O
manner	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
it	0	O
occurred	0	O
.	0	O

Israel	1	S-LOC
withdrew	0	O
in	0	O
just	0	O
over	0	O
48	0	O
hours	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
collapse	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
allies	0	O
in	0	O
Army	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
South	2	I-ORG
Lebanon	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
SLA	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
had	0	O
helped	0	O
him	0	O
maintain	0	O
his	0	O
occupation	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
whom	0	O
he	0	O
intended	0	O
to	0	O
leave	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
buffer	0	O
zone	0	O
''	0	O
to	0	O
protect	0	O
his	0	O
northern	0	O
border	0	O
,	0	O
along	0	O
with	0	O
to	0	O
United	4	B-ORG
Nations	4	I-ORG
Interim	4	I-ORG
Force	4	I-ORG
for	4	I-ORG
Lebanon	4	E-ORG
(	0	O
UNIFIL	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

Paradoxically	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
had	0	O
to	0	O
cede	0	O
ground	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
main	0	O
enemy	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Shiite	0	O
group	0	O
Hezbollah	1	S-ORG
(	0	O
God	2	B-ORG
's	2	I-ORG
Party	2	E-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
since	0	O
the	0	O
second	0	O
Israeli	3	S-MISC
invasion	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
in	0	O
1982	0	O
,	0	O
led	0	O
the	0	O
guerrilla	0	O
organizations	0	O
that	0	O
were	0	O
fighting	0	O
the	0	O
occupation	0	O
.	0	O

Hezbollah	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
supported	0	O
by	0	O
Beirut	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Damascus	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Tehran	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
took	0	O
control	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
liberated	0	O
south	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
absence	0	O
of	0	O
UN	5	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
not	0	O
yet	0	O
defined	0	O
the	0	O
mission	0	O
it	0	O
will	0	O
entrust	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
''	0	O
blue	0	O
helmets	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
whose	0	O
numbers	0	O
it	0	O
wants	0	O
to	0	O
increase	0	O
from	0	O
4,500	0	O
to	0	O
7,935	0	O
.	0	O

Although	0	O
Beirut	1	S-LOC
considers	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
Israeli	2	S-MISC
withdrawal	0	O
is	0	O
incomplete	0	O
,	0	O
because	0	O
it	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
include	0	O
the	0	O
controversial	0	O
farms	0	O
of	0	O
Chebaa	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
border	0	O
with	0	O
Syria	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
release	0	O
of	0	O
some	0	O
20	0	O
Lebanese	0	O
detained	0	O
in	0	O
Israel	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
it	0	O
assured	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
will	0	O
cooperate	0	O
with	0	O
UN	6	S-ORG
.	0	O

Israel	1	S-LOC
and	0	O
UN	2	S-ORG
assure	0	O
that	0	O
these	0	O
farms	0	O
are	0	O
Syrian	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
Damascus	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Beirut	4	S-LOC
affirm	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
Lebanese	5	S-MISC
and	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
effect	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Government	0	O
has	0	O
sent	0	O
several	0	O
documents	0	O
to	0	O
United	6	B-ORG
Nations	6	E-ORG
to	0	O
attest	0	O
to	0	O
its	0	O
sovereignty	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
leader	0	O
of	0	O
Hizbullah	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
Sheikh	0	O
Hasan	2	B-PER
Nasrala	2	E-PER
,	0	O
for	0	O
his	0	O
part	0	O
announced	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
will	0	O
continue	0	O
the	0	O
struggle	0	O
until	0	O
the	0	O
liberation	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
territory	0	O
,	0	O
located	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
foot	0	O
of	0	O
Mount	0	O
Hermon	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
rich	0	O
in	0	O
aquifers	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
response	0	O
to	0	O
Hezbollah	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
Israel	2	S-LOC
threatened	0	O
''	0	O
painful	0	O
responses	0	O
''	0	O
should	0	O
attacks	0	O
against	0	O
its	0	O
territory	0	O
continue	0	O
,	0	O
referring	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
katiuska	0	O
''	0	O
rockets	0	O
that	0	O
group	0	O
launches	0	O
sporadically	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
Israeli	3	S-MISC
north	0	O
.	0	O

Apparently	0	O
,	0	O
Syria	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
which	0	O
wields	0	O
preponderant	0	O
influence	0	O
in	0	O
Lebanon	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
where	0	O
it	0	O
has	0	O
some	0	O
35,000	0	O
soldiers	0	O
stationed	0	O
,	0	O
has	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
moment	0	O
given	0	O
carte	0	O
blanche	0	O
to	0	O
Hezbollah	3	S-ORG
,	0	O
a	0	O
pro	0	O
Iranian	0	O
group	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
Damascus	4	S-LOC
also	0	O
has	0	O
great	0	O
influence	0	O
.	0	O

Israel	1	B-LOC
's	1	E-LOC
's	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
was	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
strategy	0	O
of	0	O
Prime	0	O
Minister	0	O
Israeli	2	S-MISC
,	0	O
Ehud	3	B-PER
Barak	3	E-PER
,	0	O
to	0	O
force	0	O
Syria	4	S-LOC
in	0	O
its	0	O
negotiations	0	O
over	0	O
Golan	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
occupied	0	O
by	0	O
Israel	6	B-LOC
's	6	E-LOC
in	0	O
1967	0	O
and	0	O
annexed	0	O
in	0	O
1981	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
theory	0	O
,	0	O
Syria	1	S-LOC
is	0	O
harmed	0	O
by	0	O
Israeli	2	S-MISC
's	0	O
unilateral	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
from	0	O
Lebanese	3	S-MISC
,	0	O
since	0	O
it	0	O
deprives	0	O
Damascus	4	S-LOC
of	0	O
a	0	O
card	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
used	0	O
,	0	O
through	0	O
Hizbullah	5	S-ORG
,	0	O
to	0	O
put	0	O
pressure	0	O
on	0	O
Israel	6	S-LOC
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
practice	0	O
,	0	O
Damascus	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
being	0	O
adamant	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
question	0	O
of	0	O
returning	0	O
Golan	2	S-LOC
to	0	O
the	0	O
pre	0	O
June	0	O
1967	0	O
demarcation	0	O
line	0	O
,	0	O
appears	0	O
to	0	O
have	0	O
forced	0	O
Israel	3	S-LOC
to	0	O
carry	0	O
out	0	O
its	0	O
threat	0	O
and	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
strengthened	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
control	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
.	0	O
.	0	O

If	0	O
Israel	1	S-LOC
occupied	0	O
ten	0	O
percent	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanese	2	S-MISC
territory	0	O
,	0	O
Syrian	3	S-MISC
troops	0	O
are	0	O
deployed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
and	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
ruled	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
could	0	O
be	0	O
assigned	0	O
a	0	O
mission	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
thus	0	O
complicating	0	O
their	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
,	0	O
despite	0	O
the	0	O
desire	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
majority	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanese	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
great	0	O
powers	0	O
have	0	O
assigned	0	O
Syria	1	S-LOC
the	0	O
role	0	O
of	0	O
watchdog	0	O
for	0	O
Lebanon	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
they	0	O
know	0	O
that	0	O
if	0	O
they	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
reach	0	O
an	0	O
agreement	0	O
with	0	O
Israel	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanese	4	S-MISC
situation	0	O
will	0	O
continue	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
insecure	0	O
and	0	O
unpredictable	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
only	0	O
hope	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanese	1	S-MISC
situation	0	O
stabilizes	0	O
is	0	O
that	0	O
a	0	O
global	0	O
peace	0	O
is	0	O
achieved	0	O
in	0	O
the	2	B-LOC
Middle	2	I-LOC
East	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
the	0	O
main	0	O
victim	0	O
,	0	O
along	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
Palestinians	0	O
,	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Arab	3	B-MISC
Israeli	3	E-MISC
conflict	0	O
,	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
continue	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
so	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
.	0	O
by	0	O
Orlando	4	B-PER
Lizama	4	I-PER
Washington	4	E-PER
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

US	1	S-LOC
President	0	O
Bill	2	B-PER
Clinton	2	E-PER
scored	0	O
a	0	O
major	0	O
foreign	0	O
policy	0	O
win	0	O
with	0	O
House	3	B-ORG
of	3	I-ORG
Representatives	3	E-ORG
approving	0	O
a	0	O
trade	0	O
deal	0	O
with	0	O
China	4	S-LOC
that	0	O
will	0	O
add	0	O
to	0	O
his	0	O
government	0	O
's	0	O
economic	0	O
success	0	O
.	0	O

Political	0	O
analysts	0	O
indicated	0	O
today	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
decision	0	O
of	0	O
House	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
is	0	O
guaranteed	0	O
the	0	O
approval	0	O
of	0	O
Senate	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
will	0	O
open	0	O
a	0	O
new	0	O
chapter	0	O
in	0	O
relations	0	O
between	0	O
the	3	B-LOC
United	3	I-LOC
States	3	E-LOC
and	0	O
China	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
,	0	O
above	0	O
all	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
largest	0	O
market	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
for	0	O
North	0	O
American	0	O
products	0	O
.	0	O

By	0	O
approving	0	O
the	0	O
granting	0	O
of	0	O
permanent	0	O
trade	0	O
privileges	0	O
to	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
by	0	O
237	0	O
votes	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
to	0	O
197	0	O
against	0	O
,	0	O
House	2	S-ORG
put	0	O
an	0	O
end	0	O
yesterday	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
practice	0	O
of	0	O
discussing	0	O
those	0	O
privileges	0	O
every	0	O
year	0	O
and	0	O
ensured	0	O
the	0	O
application	0	O
to	0	O
Chinese	0	O
products	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
tariffs	0	O
that	0	O
are	0	O
charge	0	O
over	0	O
those	0	O
of	0	O
other	0	O
countries	0	O
.	0	O

Also	0	O
,	0	O
after	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
secured	0	O
a	0	O
similar	0	O
deal	0	O
last	0	O
week	0	O
with	0	O
European	2	B-ORG
Union	2	E-ORG
,	0	O
Beijing	3	S-LOC
authorities	0	O
secured	0	O
their	0	O
country	0	O
's	0	O
entry	0	O
into	0	O
World	4	B-ORG
Trade	4	I-ORG
Organization	4	E-ORG
(	0	O
WTO	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
return	0	O
,	0	O
once	0	O
Senate	1	S-ORG
formalizes	0	O
its	0	O
approval	0	O
in	0	O
June	0	O
,	0	O
China	2	S-LOC
will	0	O
open	0	O
its	0	O
market	0	O
of	0	O
1.3	0	O
billion	0	O
consumers	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
wide	0	O
range	0	O
of	0	O
US	3	S-MISC
products	0	O
,	0	O
from	0	O
agriculture	0	O
to	0	O
telecommunications	0	O
to	0	O
automobiles	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
no	0	O
foreign	0	O
conflicts	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
booming	0	O
economy	0	O
,	0	O
Clinton	1	S-PER
had	0	O
made	0	O
approval	0	O
the	0	O
legislative	0	O
priority	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
government	0	O
which	0	O
will	0	O
end	0	O
in	0	O
January	0	O
of	0	O
next	0	O
year	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
vote	0	O
he	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
hide	0	O
his	0	O
happiness	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
House	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Representatives	1	E-ORG
has	0	O
taken	0	O
a	0	O
historic	0	O
step	0	O
toward	0	O
continued	0	O
prosperity	0	O
in	0	O
the	2	B-LOC
United	2	I-LOC
States	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
reform	0	O
in	0	O
China	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
and	0	O
peace	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Clinton	4	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
in	0	O
1993	0	O
signed	0	O
Free	5	B-MISC
Trade	5	I-MISC
Agreement	5	E-MISC
(	0	O
FTA	6	S-MISC
)	0	O
with	0	O
Mexico	7	S-LOC
and	0	O
Canada	8	S-LOC
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
have	0	O
always	0	O
been	0	O
a	0	O
believer	0	O
that	0	O
if	0	O
we	0	O
open	0	O
markets	0	O
abroad	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
open	0	O
up	0	O
more	0	O
opportunities	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O

And	0	O
in	0	O
reference	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
criticism	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
lack	0	O
of	0	O
democracy	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
reported	0	O
violations	0	O
of	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
in	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
president	0	O
indicated	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
will	0	O
contribute	0	O
to	0	O
improving	0	O
the	0	O
situation	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
will	0	O
have	0	O
a	0	O
more	0	O
positive	0	O
influence	0	O
with	0	O
an	0	O
outstretched	0	O
hand	0	O
than	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
clenched	0	O
fist	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
added	0	O
.	0	O

Clinton	1	S-PER
and	0	O
his	0	O
advisers	0	O
had	0	O
previously	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
rejecting	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
would	0	O
have	0	O
meant	0	O
pushing	0	O
relations	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
countries	0	O
into	0	O
an	0	O
abyss	0	O
that	0	O
would	0	O
threaten	0	O
stability	0	O
in	0	O
Asia	2	S-LOC
and	0	O
aggravate	0	O
tensions	0	O
between	0	O
China	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
Taiwan	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
approval	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
a	0	O
concrete	0	O
result	0	O
because	0	O
it	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
make	0	O
sense	0	O
to	0	O
confront	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
populous	0	O
country	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
expressed	0	O
Sidney	1	B-PER
Weintraub	1	E-PER
,	0	O
from	0	O
Center	2	B-ORG
for	2	I-ORG
Strategic	2	I-ORG
International	2	I-ORG
Studies	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
CSIS	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Opening	0	O
other	0	O
markets	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
a	0	O
favor	0	O
we	0	O
do	0	O
to	0	O
other	0	O
countries	0	O
.	0	O

It	0	O
is	0	O
an	0	O
opportunity	0	O
that	0	O
we	0	O
create	0	O
for	0	O
ourselves	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Sherman	1	B-PER
Katc	1	E-PER
,	0	O
an	0	O
analyst	0	O
at	0	O
CSIS	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
there	0	O
was	0	O
also	0	O
criticism	0	O
,	0	O
especially	0	O
from	0	O
those	0	O
who	0	O
reject	0	O
China	1	B-LOC
's	1	E-LOC
's	0	O
political	0	O
ideology	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
situation	0	O
of	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
,	0	O
globalization	0	O
and	0	O
unions	0	O
who	0	O
fear	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
will	0	O
cause	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
jobs	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
influential	0	O
Senate	1	B-ORG
Foreign	1	I-ORG
Relations	1	I-ORG
Committee	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Jesse	2	B-PER
Helms	2	E-PER
,	0	O
has	0	O
vowed	0	O
to	0	O
fight	0	O
to	0	O
prevent	0	O
that	0	O
branch	0	O
of	0	O
Congress	3	S-ORG
from	0	O
approving	0	O
the	0	O
deal	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
I	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
want	0	O
to	0	O
spoil	0	O
your	0	O
party	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
I	0	O
feel	0	O
compelled	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
it	0	O
clear	0	O
that	0	O
I	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
intend	0	O
for	0	O
Senate	1	S-ORG
to	0	O
bow	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
plan	0	O
to	0	O
reward	0	O
the	0	O
Chinese	0	O
communists	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Friends	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
the	1	I-ORG
Earth	1	E-ORG
conservation	0	O
group	0	O
,	0	O
Brent	2	B-PER
Blackwelder	2	E-PER
,	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
deal	0	O
''	0	O
demonstrates	0	O
that	0	O
US	3	S-LOC
's	0	O
foreign	0	O
policy	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
captured	0	O
by	0	O
corporate	0	O
polluters	0	O
and	0	O
big	0	O
campaign	0	O
contributors	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

To	0	O
ensure	0	O
approval	0	O
,	0	O
House	1	S-ORG
legislators	0	O
added	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
bill	0	O
a	0	O
proposal	0	O
to	0	O
create	0	O
a	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
watchdog	0	O
group	0	O
.	0	O

But	0	O
,	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
Friends	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
the	1	I-ORG
Earth	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
project	0	O
omitted	0	O
references	0	O
to	0	O
environmental	0	O
protection	0	O
in	0	O
China	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
''	0	O
where	0	O
two	0	O
million	0	O
people	0	O
die	0	O
each	0	O
year	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
air	0	O
and	0	O
water	0	O
pollution	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Where	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
freedom	0	O
of	0	O
expression	0	O
?	0	O
Where	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
freedom	0	O
of	0	O
worship	0	O
?	0	O
Where	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
freedom	0	O
of	0	O
assembly	0	O
?	0	O

In	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
no	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
representative	0	O
for	0	O
Georgia	2	S-LOC
John	3	B-PER
Lewis	3	E-PER
when	0	O
expressing	0	O
his	0	O
rejection	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
agreement	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
If	0	O
we	0	O
defend	0	O
human	0	O
and	0	O
civil	0	O
rights	0	O
in	0	O
the	1	B-LOC
United	1	I-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
and	0	O
in	0	O
other	0	O
parts	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
,	0	O
we	0	O
must	0	O
defend	0	O
them	0	O
in	0	O
China	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
added	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
a	0	O
debate	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
made	0	O
more	0	O
with	0	O
economic	0	O
interests	0	O
in	0	O
mind	0	O
than	0	O
political	0	O
ones	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
approval	0	O
was	0	O
applauded	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
governor	0	O
of	0	O
Texas	1	S-LOC
George	2	B-PER
W.	2	I-PER
Bush	2	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
Republican	0	O
presidential	0	O
candidate	0	O
who	0	O
faces	0	O
the	0	O
Democrat	0	O
and	0	O
vice	0	O
president	0	O
Al	3	B-PER
Gore	3	E-PER
in	0	O
the	0	O
November	0	O
elections	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
It	0	O
means	0	O
a	0	O
stronger	0	O
economy	0	O
for	0	O
the	1	B-LOC
United	1	I-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
as	0	O
well	0	O
as	0	O
more	0	O
opportunities	0	O
for	0	O
freedom	0	O
in	0	O
China	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O
by	0	O
Claudia	3	B-PER
Gutiérrez	3	E-PER
Beijing	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Chinese	1	S-MISC
Government	0	O
today	0	O
urged	0	O
United	2	B-LOC
States	2	E-LOC
to	0	O
correct	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
error	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
having	0	O
included	0	O
the	0	O
creation	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
commission	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
resolution	0	O
that	0	O
grants	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
the	0	O
permanent	0	O
status	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
normal	0	O
commercial	0	O
relationship	0	O
(	0	O
PNTR	0	O
for	0	O
its	0	O
acronym	0	O
in	0	O
English	0	O
)	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
spokesperson	0	O
for	0	O
Foreign	1	B-ORG
Ministry	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Zhang	2	B-PER
Qiyue	2	E-PER
,	0	O
Beijing	3	S-LOC
has	0	O
already	0	O
presented	0	O
its	0	O
complaint	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
US	4	S-MISC
executive	0	O
in	0	O
relation	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
matter	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
it	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
opposes	0	O
the	0	O
articles	0	O
that	0	O
refer	0	O
to	0	O
said	0	O
commission	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
''	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
accept	0	O
them	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
urge	0	O
the	1	B-LOC
United	1	I-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
to	0	O
correct	0	O
its	0	O
mistake	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
such	0	O
a	0	O
way	0	O
as	0	O
to	0	O
ensure	0	O
a	0	O
healthy	0	O
and	0	O
calm	0	O
development	0	O
of	0	O
bilateral	0	O
economic	0	O
and	0	O
trade	0	O
cooperation	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
both	0	O
Ministry	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
Foreign	2	I-ORG
Affairs	2	E-ORG
and	0	O
in	3	S-ORG
Foreign	4	B-ORG
Trade	4	I-ORG
.	4	I-ORG
Economic	4	I-ORG
Cooperation	4	E-ORG
(	0	O
Moftec	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
warned	0	O
today	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
United	1	B-ORG
States	1	I-ORG
House	1	I-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Representatives	1	E-ORG
approved	0	O
this	0	O
resolution	0	O
last	0	O
morning	0	O
(	0	O
local	0	O
time	0	O
)	0	O
,	0	O
after	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
seven	0	O
hours	0	O
of	0	O
debate	0	O
,	0	O
by	0	O
237	0	O
votes	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
and	0	O
197	0	O
against	0	O
.	0	O

To	0	O
ensure	0	O
the	0	O
victory	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
historic	0	O
measure	0	O
,	0	O
strongly	0	O
advocated	0	O
against	0	O
Republicans	0	O
by	0	O
US	0	O
President	0	O
Bill	1	B-PER
Clinton	1	E-PER
in	0	O
recent	0	O
months	0	O
,	0	O
Congressional	2	S-ORG
leaders	0	O
agreed	0	O
to	0	O
create	0	O
a	0	O
legislative	0	O
and	0	O
executive	0	O
commission	0	O
that	0	O
will	0	O
annually	0	O
oversee	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
policy	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

Although	0	O
Beijing	1	S-LOC
today	0	O
described	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
resolution	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
wise	0	O
measure	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
it	0	O
also	0	O
accuses	0	O
Washington	2	S-LOC
of	0	O
using	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
as	0	O
an	0	O
excuse	0	O
to	0	O
interfere	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
internal	0	O
affairs	0	O
and	0	O
harm	0	O
its	0	O
interests	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
something	0	O
unacceptable	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Chinese	3	S-MISC
Government	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
Moftec	1	S-ORG
wasted	0	O
no	0	O
time	0	O
in	0	O
threatening	0	O
reprisals	0	O
if	0	O
said	0	O
commission	0	O
is	0	O
really	0	O
set	0	O
up	0	O
to	0	O
monitor	0	O
the	0	O
human	0	O
rights	0	O
situation	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
wishes	0	O
to	0	O
express	0	O
its	0	O
deep	0	O
dissatisfaction	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
resolution	0	O
and	0	O
reserves	0	O
the	0	O
right	0	O
to	0	O
react	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
future	0	O
''	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
matter	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
the	2	B-LOC
United	2	I-LOC
States	2	E-LOC
has	0	O
a	0	O
duty	0	O
to	0	O
resolve	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
warned	0	O
Hu	3	B-PER
Chusheng	3	E-PER
,	0	O
spokesman	0	O
for	0	O
Moftec	4	S-ORG
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
granting	0	O
of	0	O
PNTR	2	S-ORG
to	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
is	0	O
an	0	O
obligation	0	O
of	0	O
the	3	B-LOC
United	3	I-LOC
States	3	E-LOC
,	0	O
following	0	O
the	0	O
rules	0	O
of	0	O
World	4	B-ORG
Trade	4	I-ORG
Organization	4	E-ORG
(	0	O
WTO	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
pointed	0	O
out	0	O
the	0	O
representative	0	O
of	0	O
Foreign	6	B-ORG
Affairs	6	E-ORG
,	0	O
''	0	O
since	0	O
the	0	O
permanent	0	O
status	0	O
constitutes	0	O
the	0	O
basis	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
prior	0	O
requirement	0	O
''	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
entry	0	O
into	0	O
force	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
bilateral	0	O
agreement	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
access	0	O
of	0	O
China	7	S-LOC
to	0	O
WTO	8	S-ORG
signed	0	O
last	0	O
November	0	O
15	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
capital	0	O
.	0	O

Zhang	1	S-PER
indicated	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
resolution	0	O
of	0	O
Congress	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
ratified	0	O
in	0	O
mid	0	O
June	0	O
by	0	O
Senate	3	S-ORG
,	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
helps	0	O
China	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
the	5	B-LOC
United	5	I-LOC
States	5	E-LOC
develop	0	O
their	0	O
economic	0	O
and	0	O
commercial	0	O
exchanges	0	O
based	0	O
on	0	O
equality	0	O
and	0	O
mutual	0	O
benefit	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
helps	0	O
create	0	O
the	0	O
conditions	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
healthy	0	O
and	0	O
stable	0	O
development	0	O
of	0	O
bilateral	0	O
relations	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
spokeswoman	0	O
urged	0	O
the	0	O
US	1	S-MISC
party	0	O
to	0	O
respect	0	O
the	0	O
three	0	O
communiqués	0	O
signed	0	O
by	0	O
both	0	O
countries	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
basic	0	O
norms	0	O
that	0	O
govern	0	O
international	0	O
relations	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
rules	0	O
of	0	O
WTO	2	S-ORG
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
approval	0	O
of	0	O
PNTR	1	S-MISC
,	0	O
20	0	O
years	0	O
of	0	O
annual	0	O
reviews	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
commercial	0	O
status	0	O
of	0	O
China	2	S-LOC
by	0	O
United	3	B-LOC
States	3	E-LOC
come	0	O
to	0	O
an	0	O
end	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
doors	0	O
are	0	O
opened	0	O
for	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
to	0	O
become	0	O
the	0	O
136th	0	O
member	0	O
of	0	O
WTO	4	S-ORG
before	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
year	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
opportunity	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
more	0	O
within	0	O
reach	0	O
after	0	O
Beijing	5	S-LOC
signed	0	O
a	0	O
similar	0	O
agreement	0	O
with	0	O
European	6	B-ORG
Union	6	E-ORG
(	0	O
EU	7	S-ORG
)	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
capital	0	O
last	0	O
Friday	0	O
.	0	O

With	0	O
the	0	O
entry	0	O
of	0	O
China	1	S-LOC
into	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
trade	0	O
regulatory	0	O
body	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
tariffs	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
must	0	O
pay	0	O
to	0	O
access	0	O
the	2	B-LOC
US	2	E-LOC
will	0	O
be	0	O
equal	0	O
to	0	O
those	0	O
of	0	O
practically	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
nations	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
Beijing	3	S-LOC
will	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
open	0	O
its	0	O
markets	0	O
to	0	O
sectors	0	O
such	0	O
as	0	O
agriculture	0	O
,	0	O
telecommunications	0	O
or	0	O
insurance	0	O
of	0	O
that	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

While	0	O
the	0	O
detractors	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
resolution	0	O
believe	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
access	0	O
of	0	O
China	1	B-LOC
's	1	E-LOC
to	0	O
WTO	2	S-ORG
will	0	O
aggravate	0	O
the	0	O
already	0	O
gigantic	0	O
trade	0	O
deficit	0	O
that	0	O
USA	3	S-LOC
maintains	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
country	0	O
,	0	O
of	0	O
68,000	0	O
million	0	O
dollars	0	O
last	0	O
year	0	O
,	0	O
its	0	O
defenders	0	O
assure	0	O
that	0	O
not	0	O
only	0	O
the	0	O
North	0	O
American	0	O
economy	0	O
will	0	O
benefit	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
also	0	O
national	0	O
security	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
political	0	O
and	0	O
economic	0	O
reforms	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
promoted	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
Asian	0	O
giant	0	O
.	0	O

Lisbon	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Portuguese	1	S-MISC
press	0	O
today	0	O
highlights	0	O
Real	2	B-ORG
Madrid	2	E-ORG
's	0	O
eighth	0	O
victory	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
historic	0	O
European	3	B-MISC
Cup	3	E-MISC
final	0	O
that	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
first	0	O
time	0	O
pitted	0	O
two	0	O
teams	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
country	0	O
against	0	O
each	0	O
other	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
judgments	0	O
in	0	O
favor	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
game	0	O
developed	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
winning	0	O
team	0	O
are	0	O
unanimous	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
simply	0	O
insurmountable	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
history	0	O
won	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
madridistas	0	O
religiously	0	O
respected	0	O
their	0	O
past	0	O
and	0	O
built	0	O
a	0	O
cruel	0	O
ending	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
beautiful	0	O
adventure	0	O
of	0	O
Valencia	1	S-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
comments	0	O
''	0	O
A	2	B-ORG
Bola	2	E-ORG
''	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
first	0	O
pages	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
myth	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Real	1	B-ORG
Madrid	1	E-ORG
continues	0	O
to	0	O
grow	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
Raúl	2	B-MISC
:	2	E-MISC
the	0	O
eighth	0	O
wonder	0	O
''	0	O
headlines	0	O
''	0	O
Record	3	S-MISC
''	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
reports	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
sporting	0	O
event	0	O
was	0	O
''	0	O
superb	0	O
''	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
quality	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
game	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
stadium	0	O
divided	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
fans	0	O
that	0	O
passionately	0	O
followed	0	O
the	0	O
incidents	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
meeting	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
The	0	O
Valencian	0	O
rice	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
sweet	0	O
meringue	0	O
''	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
Jornal	1	B-ORG
de	1	I-ORG
Noticias	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
highlights	0	O
the	0	O
superiority	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Madrid	0	O
team	0	O
against	0	O
an	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
that	0	O
suffered	0	O
from	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
lack	0	O
of	0	O
rhythm	0	O
''	0	O
and	0	O
''	0	O
lost	0	O
almost	0	O
all	0	O
the	0	O
attacking	0	O
inspiration	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Freetown	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
murder	0	O
in	0	O
Sierra	1	B-LOC
Leone	1	E-LOC
of	0	O
four	0	O
soldiers	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
pro	0	O
government	0	O
forces	0	O
and	0	O
two	0	O
journalists	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
hands	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
United	2	B-ORG
Revolutionary	2	I-ORG
Forces	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
FRU	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
rebels	0	O
coincided	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
resurgence	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
wave	0	O
of	0	O
violence	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
African	0	O
country	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
experiencing	0	O
for	0	O
almost	0	O
a	0	O
month	0	O
.	0	O

Spanish	0	O
journalist	0	O
Miguel	1	B-PER
Gil	1	I-PER
Moreno	1	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
worked	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
cameraman	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
agency	0	O
Associated	2	B-ORG
Press	2	I-ORG
TV	2	E-ORG
and	0	O
his	0	O
colleague	0	O
American	3	S-MISC
Kurt	4	B-PER
Schork	4	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
correspondent	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
British	5	S-MISC
Reuters	6	S-ORG
news	0	O
agency	0	O
,	0	O
were	0	O
killed	0	O
yesterday	0	O
when	0	O
the	0	O
column	0	O
of	0	O
government	0	O
troops	0	O
they	0	O
were	0	O
traveling	0	O
with	0	O
was	0	O
assaulted	0	O
by	0	O
RUF	7	S-ORG
rebels	0	O
.	0	O
.	0	O

Two	0	O
other	0	O
journalists	0	O
,	0	O
Greek	0	O
Yannis	3	B-PER
Behrakis	3	E-PER
and	0	O
South	0	O
African	0	O
Mark	4	B-PER
Chisholm	4	E-PER
,	0	O
both	0	O
Reuters	5	S-ORG
correspondents	0	O
,	0	O
were	0	O
also	0	O
slightly	0	O
injured	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
incident	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
took	0	O
place	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
crossroads	0	O
of	0	O
Rogberi	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
some	0	O
80	0	O
kilometers	0	O
northeast	0	O
of	0	O
Freetown	2	S-LOC
.	0	O

Likewise	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
as	0	O
confirmed	0	O
by	0	O
UN	1	S-ORG
sources	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Sierra	2	B-LOC
Leone	2	E-LOC
capital	0	O
,	0	O
four	0	O
Sierra	3	B-MISC
Leonean	3	E-MISC
soldiers	0	O
were	0	O
also	0	O
killed	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
ambush	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
two	0	O
wounded	0	O
reporters	0	O
were	0	O
transferred	0	O
to	0	O
a	0	O
field	0	O
hospital	0	O
prepared	0	O
by	0	O
UN	1	S-ORG
forces	0	O
without	0	O
fear	0	O
for	0	O
their	0	O
lives	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
the	0	O
body	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
32	0	O
year	0	O
old	0	O
Spanish	0	O
journalist	0	O
was	0	O
yesterday	0	O
in	0	O
Freetown	2	S-LOC
waiting	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
repatriated	0	O
.	0	O
EFE	3	S-ORG
sources	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
city	0	O
told	0	O
EFE	3	S-ORG
.	0	O

As	0	O
soon	0	O
as	0	O
the	0	O
incident	0	O
became	0	O
known	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Secretary	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
UN	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
Ghanaian	0	O
Kofi	2	B-PER
Annan	2	E-PER
,	0	O
expressed	0	O
his	0	O
sadness	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
death	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
journalists	0	O
,	0	O
whom	0	O
he	0	O
stated	0	O
''	0	O
were	0	O
professionals	0	O
seeking	0	O
to	0	O
report	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
bloody	0	O
conflict	0	O
that	0	O
has	0	O
already	0	O
claimed	0	O
too	0	O
many	0	O
lives	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
They	0	O
were	0	O
doing	0	O
what	0	O
any	0	O
other	0	O
journalist	0	O
does	0	O
around	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
:	0	O
taking	0	O
risks	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
we	0	O
can	0	O
be	0	O
informed	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
Annan	1	S-PER
added	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
statement	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
his	0	O
part	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Associated	1	B-ORG
Press	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Louis	2	B-PER
D.	2	I-PER
Boccardi	2	E-PER
,	0	O
assured	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
loss	0	O
of	0	O
Miguel	3	S-PER
leaves	0	O
them	0	O
with	0	O
an	0	O
indescribable	0	O
sense	0	O
of	0	O
loss	0	O
.	0	O

Our	0	O
pain	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
eased	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
knowledge	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
doing	0	O
the	0	O
work	0	O
he	0	O
loved	0	O
when	0	O
tragedy	0	O
struck	0	O
.	0	O
''	0	O

Gil	1	B-PER
Moreno	1	E-PER
,	0	O
a	0	O
native	0	O
of	0	O
Barcelona	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
northeast	0	O
of	0	O
Spain	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
had	0	O
covered	0	O
the	0	O
conflicts	0	O
of	0	O
Kosovo	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
Chechnya	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
Iraq	6	S-LOC
and	0	O
Congo	7	S-LOC
,	0	O
among	0	O
others	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
as	0	O
stated	0	O
by	0	O
Nigel	8	B-PER
Baker	8	E-PER
,	0	O
news	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
North	0	O
American	0	O
agency	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
never	0	O
took	0	O
a	0	O
step	0	O
without	0	O
considering	0	O
the	0	O
reasons	0	O
for	0	O
doing	0	O
so	0	O
and	0	O
your	0	O
options	0	O
.	0	O

Reporter	0	O
Spanish	1	S-MISC
had	0	O
received	0	O
the	0	O
cameraman	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
year	0	O
award	0	O
for	0	O
''	0	O
Royal	2	B-ORG
Television	2	I-ORG
Society	2	E-ORG
''	0	O
last	0	O
month	0	O
.	0	O

Kurt	1	B-PER
Shork	1	E-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
victim	0	O
,	0	O
53	0	O
,	0	O
worked	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Reuters	2	S-ORG
agency	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
past	0	O
decade	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Kurt	1	S-PER
was	0	O
a	0	O
courageous	0	O
reporter	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
courageous	0	O
man	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
perhaps	0	O
better	0	O
than	0	O
other	0	O
journalists	0	O
knew	0	O
how	0	O
to	0	O
reflect	0	O
the	0	O
plight	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Kurdish	0	O
population	0	O
during	0	O
Gulf	2	B-MISC
War	2	E-MISC
and	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
victims	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Balkan	3	S-LOC
conflict	0	O
afterwards	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
chief	0	O
editor	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
British	4	S-MISC
agency	0	O
,	0	O
Geert	5	B-PER
Linnebank	5	E-PER
.	0	O

Likewise	0	O
,	0	O
the	1	B-LOC
United	1	I-LOC
States	1	E-LOC
issued	0	O
a	0	O
statement	0	O
yesterday	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
it	0	O
strongly	0	O
condemned	0	O
the	0	O
event	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
We	0	O
condemn	0	O
this	0	O
violent	0	O
attack	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
strongest	0	O
possible	0	O
terms	0	O
,	0	O
both	0	O
Embassy	1	B-ORG
in	1	E-ORG
US	2	S-LOC
in	0	O
Freetown	3	S-LOC
and	0	O
State	4	B-ORG
Department	4	E-ORG
in	0	O
Washington	5	S-LOC
stand	0	O
ready	0	O
to	0	O
help	0	O
families	0	O
at	0	O
this	0	O
difficult	0	O
time	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
said	0	O
Philip	6	B-PER
Reeker	6	E-PER
,	0	O
spokesperson	0	O
for	0	O
State	7	B-ORG
Department	7	E-ORG
.	0	O

The	0	O
journalists	0	O
were	0	O
assaulted	0	O
by	0	O
RUF	1	S-ORG
rebels	0	O
while	0	O
traveling	0	O
in	0	O
two	0	O
military	0	O
trucks	0	O
alongside	0	O
a	0	O
column	0	O
of	0	O
pro	0	O
government	0	O
soldiers	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
Rogberi	2	S-LOC
crossroads	0	O
near	0	O
the	0	O
town	0	O
of	0	O
Masaka	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
some	0	O
80	0	O
kilometers	0	O
northeast	0	O
of	0	O
Freetown	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
zone	0	O
,	0	O
of	0	O
high	0	O
strategic	0	O
value	0	O
,	0	O
other	0	O
confrontations	0	O
between	0	O
''	0	O
blue	0	O
helmets	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
UN	1	S-ORG
and	0	O
rebel	0	O
groups	0	O
had	0	O
been	0	O
previously	0	O
registered	0	O
.	0	O

Last	0	O
Monday	0	O
,	0	O
Sierra	0	O
Leonean	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
troops	0	O
had	0	O
taken	0	O
the	0	O
Rogberi	2	S-LOC
crossing	0	O
,	0	O
where	0	O
that	0	O
same	0	O
day	0	O
several	0	O
corpses	0	O
were	0	O
found	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
an	0	O
advanced	0	O
state	0	O
of	0	O
decomposition	0	O
,	0	O
dressed	0	O
in	0	O
UN	3	S-ORG
''	0	O
blue	0	O
helmet	0	O
''	0	O
uniforms	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
could	0	O
correspond	0	O
to	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
UN	3	S-ORG
.	0	O
international	0	O
organization	0	O
kidnapped	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
rebels	0	O
three	0	O
weeks	0	O
ago	0	O
.	0	O

FRU	1	S-ORG
is	0	O
still	0	O
holding	0	O
290	0	O
peacekeepers	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Liberian	0	O
president	0	O
,	0	O
Charles	2	B-PER
Taylor	2	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
acts	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
mediator	0	O
between	0	O
United	3	B-ORG
Nations	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
the	0	O
Sierra	0	O
Leonean	0	O
rebels	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
release	0	O
any	0	O
more	0	O
hostages	0	O
until	0	O
government	0	O
forces	0	O
stop	0	O
their	0	O
offensive	0	O
against	0	O
FRU	4	S-ORG
and	0	O
stop	0	O
their	0	O
attack	0	O
.	0	O
unstoppable	0	O
advance	0	O
towards	0	O
the	0	O
guerrilla	0	O
strongholds	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
interior	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

Rome	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
''	0	O
Europe	3	S-LOC
is	0	O
from	0	O
Real	4	B-ORG
Madrid	4	E-ORG
again	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
headline	0	O
used	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Italian	5	S-MISC
press	0	O
to	0	O
highlight	0	O
the	0	O
victory	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Spain	6	S-LOC
capital	0	O
team	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Champions	0	O
League	0	O
final	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
Spanish	7	S-MISC
club	0	O
,	0	O
Valencia	8	S-ORG
,	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
newspapers	0	O
say	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
show	0	O
the	0	O
brilliant	0	O
game	0	O
they	0	O
did	0	O
against	0	O
Barcelona	9	S-ORG
or	0	O
Lazio	10	S-ORG
.	0	O

Although	0	O
it	0	O
appears	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
box	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
front	0	O
pages	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Champions	1	B-MISC
Cup	1	E-MISC
final	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
make	0	O
the	0	O
front	0	O
page	0	O
headlines	0	O
of	0	O
Italian	2	S-MISC
sports	0	O
newspapers	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
case	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
Gazzetta	3	B-ORG
dello	3	I-ORG
Sport	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
confines	0	O
it	0	O
to	0	O
page	0	O
15	0	O
and	0	O
in	0	O
''	0	O
Corriere	4	B-ORG
dellos	4	I-ORG
Sport	4	E-ORG
''	0	O
at	0	O
17	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
is	0	O
because	0	O
no	0	O
Italian	1	S-MISC
club	0	O
was	0	O
among	0	O
the	0	O
finalists	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Real	1	S-ORG
achieves	0	O
its	0	O
eighth	0	O
victory	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Champions	0	O
Cup	0	O
.	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
defeated	0	O
3	0	O
0	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
headline	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
La	3	B-ORG
Gazzetta	3	I-ORG
dello	3	I-ORG
Sport	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
inside	0	O
page	0	O
adds	0	O
:	0	O
''	0	O
The	0	O
eighth	0	O
wonder	0	O
of	0	O
Real	4	S-ORG
,	0	O
Valencia	5	S-ORG
wakes	0	O
up	0	O
from	0	O
sleep	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
Milanese	0	O
newspaper	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
''	0	O
most	0	O
expert	0	O
''	0	O
team	0	O
,	0	O
Real	1	B-ORG
Madrid	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
''	0	O
won	0	O
over	0	O
an	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
that	0	O
stammered	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
adds	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
madridistas	0	O
prevailed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
duels	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
dominated	0	O
Redondo	1	S-PER
and	0	O
McManaman	2	S-PER
in	0	O
midfield	0	O
.	0	O

After	0	O
highlighting	0	O
Raul	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
's	0	O
game	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
La	2	B-ORG
Gazzetta	2	I-ORG
dello	2	I-ORG
Sport	2	E-ORG
''	0	O
affirms	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
young	0	O
Madridista	0	O
player	0	O
''	0	O
is	0	O
one	0	O
step	0	O
away	0	O
''	0	O
from	0	O
Golden	3	B-MISC
Ball	3	E-MISC
and	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
deserves	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Real	5	B-ORG
Madrid	5	E-ORG
Great	4	S-MISC
gallery	0	O
,	0	O
between	0	O
Di	6	B-PER
Stefano	6	E-PER
and	0	O
Kopa	7	S-PER
.	0	O

''	0	O
Huracán	1	B-ORG
Real	1	E-ORG
on	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
is	0	O
the	0	O
title	0	O
of	0	O
''	0	O
Corriere	3	B-ORG
dello	3	I-ORG
Sport	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Roman	0	O
newspaper	0	O
claiming	0	O
that	0	O
Madridistas	4	S-ORG
gave	0	O
''	0	O
a	0	O
severe	0	O
lesson	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
team	0	O
alienated	0	O
by	0	O
Cuper	5	S-PER
''	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
morning	0	O
paper	0	O
states	0	O
that	0	O
for	0	O
Real	1	S-ORG
winning	0	O
the	0	O
cup	0	O
means	0	O
making	0	O
up	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
bad	0	O
season	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
relied	0	O
too	0	O
much	0	O
on	0	O
their	0	O
counterattacks	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
stop	0	O
Moriente	3	S-PER
,	0	O
McManaman	4	S-PER
and	0	O
Raul	5	S-PER
from	0	O
''	0	O
signing	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
eighth	0	O
champions	0	O
cup	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
highlights	0	O
the	0	O
young	0	O
goalkeeper	0	O
Iker	1	B-PER
Casillas	1	E-PER
(	0	O
he	0	O
calls	0	O
him	0	O
the	0	O
baby	0	O
champion	0	O
)	0	O
and	0	O
Helguera	2	S-PER
and	0	O
especially	0	O
Raul	3	S-PER
,	0	O
whom	0	O
he	0	O
defines	0	O
as	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
total	0	O
champion	0	O
''	0	O
who	0	O
scores	0	O
goals	0	O
in	0	O
all	0	O
kinds	0	O
and	0	O
ways	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
He	0	O
has	0	O
a	0	O
strength	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
crazy	0	O
desire	0	O
to	0	O
win	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

For	0	O
''	0	O
Corriere	1	B-ORG
dello	1	I-ORG
Sport	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
,	0	O
Madrid	2	B-ORG
's	2	E-ORG
's	0	O
victory	0	O
means	0	O
Del	3	B-PER
Bosque	3	E-PER
(	0	O
the	0	O
coach	0	O
)	0	O
's	0	O
revenge	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
lost	0	O
the	0	O
1981	0	O
final	0	O
against	0	O
Liverpol	6	S-ORG
as	0	O
Real	4	S-ORG
's	0	O
player	0	O
in	0	O
Paris	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
and	0	O
Cuper	7	S-PER
's	0	O
surrender	0	O
.	0	O

San	1	B-LOC
Sebastian	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
judge	0	O
investigating	0	O
the	0	O
death	0	O
of	0	O
Mikel	1	B-PER
Zabalza	1	E-PER
in	0	O
1985	0	O
has	0	O
summoned	0	O
former	0	O
civil	0	O
guards	0	O
Enrique	2	B-PER
Dorado	2	E-PER
and	0	O
Felipe	3	B-PER
Bayo	3	E-PER
,	0	O
recently	0	O
sentenced	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
murders	0	O
of	0	O
Lasa	4	S-PER
and	0	O
Zabala	5	S-PER
,	0	O
to	0	O
testify	0	O
as	0	O
defendants	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
case	0	O
,	0	O
legal	0	O
sources	0	O
confirmed	0	O
today	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
an	0	O
order	0	O
notified	0	O
yesterday	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
of	0	O
Court	1	S-LOC
of	2	S-ORG
Instruction	3	B-LOC
Number	3	I-LOC
1	3	E-LOC
of	0	O
San	4	B-LOC
Sebastián	4	E-LOC
,	0	O
Augusto	5	B-PER
Maeso	5	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
is	0	O
currently	0	O
in	0	O
Section	6	S-ORG
First	0	O
of	0	O
Provincial	7	B-ORG
Court	7	E-ORG
on	0	O
commission	0	O
of	0	O
services	0	O
,	0	O
recalls	0	O
that	0	O
during	0	O
the	0	O
preliminary	0	O
investigation	0	O
the	0	O
names	0	O
of	0	O
Dorado	8	S-PER
and	0	O
Bayo	9	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
Called	0	O
to	0	O
testify	0	O
on	0	O
September	0	O
19	0	O
,	0	O
they	0	O
were	0	O
summoned	0	O
by	0	O
various	0	O
witnesses	0	O
and	0	O
appeared	0	O
in	0	O
press	0	O
reports	0	O
.	0	O

Maeso	1	S-PER
considers	0	O
that	0	O
some	0	O
of	0	O
these	0	O
testimonies	0	O
''	0	O
question	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
veracity	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
official	0	O
version	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
defends	0	O
that	0	O
Zabalza	2	S-PER
drowned	0	O
when	0	O
he	0	O
fell	0	O
into	0	O
the	0	O
river	0	O
Bidasoa	3	S-LOC
when	0	O
he	0	O
tried	0	O
to	0	O
escape	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Civil	4	B-ORG
Guard	4	E-ORG
agents	0	O
whom	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
leading	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
search	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
den	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
ETA	5	S-ORG
.	0	O

In	0	O
the	0	O
opinion	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
judge	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
anti	0	O
terrorism	0	O
legislation	0	O
was	0	O
applied	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
young	0	O
man	0	O
after	0	O
his	0	O
arrest	0	O
for	0	O
his	0	O
alleged	0	O
relationship	0	O
with	0	O
ETA	1	S-ORG
and	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
revealed	0	O
the	0	O
location	0	O
of	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
hole	0	O
''	0	O
are	0	O
data	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
recommend	0	O
security	0	O
measures	0	O
that	0	O
prevent	0	O
escapes	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
supposed	0	O
place	0	O
where	0	O
''	0	O
this	0	O
hideout	0	O
would	0	O
be	0	O
found	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
Zabalza	2	S-PER
was	0	O
driven	0	O
by	0	O
''	0	O
only	0	O
three	0	O
members	0	O
of	0	O
Civil	3	B-ORG
Guard	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
.	0	O

One	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
testimonies	0	O
on	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
order	0	O
is	0	O
based	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
statement	0	O
by	0	O
Dorado	1	S-PER
himself	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
admitted	0	O
to	0	O
two	0	O
journalists	0	O
from	0	O
El	2	B-ORG
Mundo	2	E-ORG
that	0	O
Zabalza	3	S-PER
died	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
Intxaurrondo	4	S-LOC
barracks	0	O
when	0	O
Bayo	5	S-PER
practiced	0	O
the	0	O
torture	0	O
known	0	O
as	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
bathtub	0	O
''	0	O
on	0	O
him	0	O
.	0	O

Moscow	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Russia	1	B-LOC
's	1	E-LOC
's	0	O
gold	0	O
and	0	O
foreign	0	O
exchange	0	O
reserves	0	O
rose	0	O
$	0	O
600	0	O
million	0	O
and	0	O
as	0	O
of	0	O
May	0	O
19	0	O
were	0	O
equivalent	0	O
to	0	O
$	0	O
18.3	0	O
billion	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
Central	2	B-ORG
Bank	2	E-ORG
statement	0	O
reported	0	O
today	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
report	0	O
,	0	O
Central	1	B-ORG
Bank	1	I-ORG
's	1	E-ORG
's	0	O
gold	0	O
and	0	O
foreign	0	O
exchange	0	O
reserves	0	O
stood	0	O
at	0	O
$	0	O
17.7	0	O
billion	0	O
as	0	O
of	0	O
May	0	O
12	0	O
.	0	O

Foreign	0	O
currency	0	O
assets	0	O
held	0	O
by	0	O
Central	1	B-ORG
Bank	1	E-ORG
and	0	O
Ministry	2	B-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
Finance	2	E-ORG
are	0	O
calculated	0	O
in	0	O
US	0	O
dollars	0	O
and	0	O
their	0	O
value	0	O
depends	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
official	0	O
ruble	0	O
dollar	0	O
exchange	0	O
rate	0	O
established	0	O
by	0	O
Central	3	B-ORG
Bank	3	E-ORG
at	0	O
the	0	O
time	0	O
of	0	O
posting	0	O
.	0	O

Gold	0	O
reserves	0	O
are	0	O
valued	0	O
at	0	O
US	0	O
$	0	O
300	0	O
per	0	O
troy	0	O
ounce	0	O
of	0	O
gold	0	O
.	0	O

Don	1	B-PER
Benito	1	E-PER
(	0	O
Badajoz	2	S-LOC
)	0	O
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
socialist	0	O
groups	0	O
of	0	O
Don	1	B-LOC
Benito	1	E-LOC
and	0	O
Villanueva	2	B-LOC
de	2	I-LOC
la	2	I-LOC
Serena	2	E-LOC
have	0	O
agreed	0	O
to	0	O
create	0	O
a	0	O
joint	0	O
political	0	O
commission	0	O
whose	0	O
function	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
to	0	O
prepare	0	O
joint	0	O
proposals	0	O
to	0	O
present	0	O
them	0	O
to	0	O
their	0	O
respective	0	O
City	0	O
Councils	0	O
,	0	O
Junta	3	B-ORG
de	3	I-ORG
Extremadura	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
the	0	O
central	0	O
government	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
has	0	O
been	0	O
announced	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
general	0	O
secretaries	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
respective	0	O
localities	0	O
,	0	O
Francisco	1	B-PER
García	1	I-PER
Ramos	1	E-PER
,	0	O
on	0	O
behalf	0	O
of	0	O
Villanueva	2	B-LOC
de	2	I-LOC
la	2	I-LOC
Serena	2	E-LOC
,	0	O
and	0	O
Juan	3	B-PER
Manzano	3	E-PER
,	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
Dombení	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
a	0	O
press	0	O
conference	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
PSOE	4	S-ORG
spokesperson	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
Don	5	B-LOC
Benito	5	E-LOC
City	0	O
Council	0	O
,	0	O
Julio	6	B-PER
Carmona	6	E-PER
,	0	O
has	0	O
also	0	O
been	0	O
present	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
number	0	O
two	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Villanovan	0	O
socialists	0	O
,	0	O
Raúl	7	B-PER
Borrasca	7	E-PER
.	0	O

The	0	O
aforementioned	0	O
commission	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
made	0	O
up	0	O
of	0	O
four	0	O
representatives	0	O
of	0	O
PSOE	1	S-ORG
from	0	O
Villanueva	2	B-LOC
de	2	I-LOC
la	2	I-LOC
Serena	2	E-LOC
and	0	O
another	0	O
four	0	O
from	0	O
Don	3	B-LOC
Benito	3	E-LOC
and	0	O
will	0	O
also	0	O
be	0	O
in	0	O
charge	0	O
of	0	O
submitting	0	O
its	0	O
proposals	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
provincial	0	O
,	0	O
regional	0	O
and	0	O
even	0	O
national	0	O
bodies	0	O
of	0	O
PSOE	4	S-ORG
itself	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
combined	0	O
force	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
socialists	0	O
in	0	O
both	0	O
town	0	O
councils	0	O
supposes	0	O
17	0	O
councillors	0	O
,	0	O
9	0	O
in	0	O
Villanueva	1	B-LOC
de	1	I-LOC
la	1	I-LOC
Serena	1	E-LOC
and	0	O
8	0	O
in	0	O
Don	2	B-LOC
Benito	2	E-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
number	0	O
of	0	O
affiliates	0	O
between	0	O
both	0	O
populations	0	O
is	0	O
greater	0	O
than	0	O
500	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
idea	0	O
of	0	O
creating	0	O
this	0	O
alliance	0	O
arose	0	O
approximately	0	O
three	0	O
weeks	0	O
ago	0	O
through	0	O
a	0	O
telephone	0	O
call	0	O
made	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
socialist	0	O
spokesman	0	O
for	0	O
Don	1	B-LOC
Benito	1	E-LOC
,	0	O
Julio	2	B-PER
Carmona	2	E-PER
,	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
socialist	0	O
spokesman	0	O
for	0	O
Villanueva	3	B-LOC
de	3	I-LOC
la	3	I-LOC
Serena	3	E-LOC
,	0	O
Francisco	4	B-PER
García	4	I-PER
Ramos	4	E-PER
,	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
latter	0	O
leader	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
subsequent	0	O
step	0	O
was	0	O
the	0	O
convening	0	O
of	0	O
both	0	O
local	0	O
executives	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
have	0	O
held	0	O
several	0	O
meetings	0	O
before	0	O
publicly	0	O
disseminating	0	O
the	0	O
understanding	0	O
.	0	O

Madrid	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
minister	0	O
of	0	O
Justice	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
Angel	2	B-PER
Acebes	2	E-PER
,	0	O
highlighted	0	O
today	0	O
that	0	O
judge	0	O
Manuel	3	B-PER
García	3	I-PER
Castellón	3	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
the	0	O
Spanish	4	S-MISC
liaison	0	O
magistrate	0	O
in	0	O
France	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
exercise	0	O
any	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
jurisdictional	0	O
function	0	O
but	0	O
rather	0	O
one	0	O
of	0	O
cooperation	0	O
and	0	O
collaboration	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
statements	0	O
to	0	O
Cadena	1	B-ORG
Cope	1	E-ORG
collected	0	O
by	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
Acebes	3	S-PER
explained	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
work	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
liaison	0	O
magistrate	0	O
consists	0	O
of	0	O
exercising	0	O
a	0	O
series	0	O
of	0	O
cooperation	0	O
functions	0	O
between	0	O
States	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
certain	0	O
matter	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
case	0	O
with	0	O
France	4	S-LOC
in	0	O
the	0	O
fight	0	O
against	0	O
terrorism	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
liaison	0	O
magistrates	0	O
try	0	O
to	0	O
promote	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
speed	0	O
up	0	O
the	0	O
procedures	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
contacts	0	O
between	0	O
the	0	O
competent	0	O
services	0	O
when	0	O
there	0	O
are	0	O
delays	0	O
and	0	O
they	0	O
know	0	O
the	0	O
laws	0	O
of	0	O
both	0	O
countries	0	O
,	0	O
indicated	0	O
Acebes	1	S-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
they	0	O
are	0	O
''	0	O
typical	0	O
tasks	0	O
of	0	O
collaboration	0	O
and	0	O
cooperation	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

He	0	O
clarified	0	O
that	0	O
García	1	B-PER
Castellón	1	E-PER
will	0	O
not	0	O
exercise	0	O
any	0	O
type	0	O
of	0	O
jurisdictional	0	O
function	0	O
and	0	O
recalled	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
system	0	O
that	0	O
regulates	0	O
these	0	O
liaison	0	O
magistrates	0	O
allows	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
not	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
judge	0	O
,	0	O
since	0	O
a	0	O
prosecutor	0	O
could	0	O
have	0	O
been	0	O
appointed	0	O
.	0	O

Even	0	O
,	0	O
he	0	O
added	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
other	0	O
countries	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
even	0	O
necessary	0	O
for	0	O
this	0	O
function	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
carried	0	O
out	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
magistrate	0	O
or	0	O
a	0	O
prosecutor	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
it	0	O
is	0	O
enough	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
be	0	O
a	0	O
specialist	0	O
in	0	O
law	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
It	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
resolve	0	O
any	0	O
issue	0	O
or	0	O
exercise	0	O
other	0	O
powers	0	O
of	0	O
judges	0	O
from	0	O
one	0	O
country	0	O
or	0	O
another	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
he	0	O
said	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
figure	0	O
is	0	O
regulated	0	O
by	0	O
a	0	O
law	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
approved	0	O
in	0	O
1998	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
establishes	0	O
its	0	O
legal	0	O
regime	0	O
and	0	O
its	0	O
election	0	O
system	0	O
,	0	O
said	0	O
the	0	O
Justice	1	S-ORG
minister	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
added	0	O
that	0	O
his	0	O
appointment	0	O
is	0	O
a	0	O
responsibility	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Government	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
previously	0	O
spoke	0	O
with	0	O
General	2	B-ORG
Council	2	I-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
the	2	I-ORG
Power	2	I-ORG
of	2	I-ORG
attorney	2	E-ORG
.	0	O

London	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Iraqi	1	S-MISC
President	0	O
Saddam	2	B-PER
Hussein	2	E-PER
is	0	O
rebuilding	0	O
his	0	O
arsenals	0	O
of	0	O
mass	0	O
destruction	0	O
and	0	O
is	0	O
once	0	O
again	0	O
a	0	O
threat	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
world	0	O
,	0	O
british	3	S-MISC
Deputy	0	O
Minister	0	O
for	0	O
Foreign	4	S-ORG
Affairs	0	O
Peter	5	B-PER
Hain	5	E-PER
said	0	O
today	0	O
,	0	O
Thursday	0	O
.	0	O

Speaking	0	O
to	0	O
BBC	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
Hain	2	S-PER
said	0	O
that	0	O
Husein	3	S-PER
should	0	O
allow	0	O
United	5	B-ORG
Nations	5	E-ORG
weapons	0	O
inspectors	0	O
access	0	O
to	0	O
Iraqi	4	S-MISC
territory	0	O
to	0	O
destroy	0	O
chemical	0	O
and	0	O
biological	0	O
weapons	0	O
.	0	O

Hain	1	B-PER
's	1	E-PER
's	0	O
warnings	0	O
came	0	O
after	0	O
former	0	O
UN	2	S-ORG
weapons	0	O
inspector	0	O
Richard	3	B-PER
Butler	3	E-PER
raised	0	O
concerns	0	O
about	0	O
the	0	O
military	0	O
capabilities	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Baghdad	4	S-LOC
regime	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
This	0	O
is	0	O
very	0	O
worrying	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
is	0	O
why	0	O
we	0	O
have	0	O
taken	0	O
a	0	O
very	0	O
strong	0	O
position	0	O
in	0	O
saying	0	O
that	0	O
UN	1	S-ORG
weapons	0	O
inspections	0	O
should	0	O
be	0	O
allowed	0	O
,	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
deputy	0	O
minister	0	O
added	0	O
.	0	O

Madrid	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Champions	1	B-MISC
League	1	E-MISC
final	0	O
that	0	O
ended	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
victory	0	O
for	0	O
Real	2	B-ORG
Madrid	2	I-ORG
's	2	E-ORG
against	0	O
Valencia	3	S-ORG
by	0	O
three	0	O
goals	0	O
to	0	O
nil	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
celebration	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
victory	0	O
in	0	O
Madrid	4	S-LOC
and	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
French	0	O
city	0	O
of	0	O
Paris	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
focuses	0	O
the	0	O
attention	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
sports	0	O
newspapers	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Cooler	0	O
than	0	O
an	0	O
eight	0	O
''	0	O
headlines	0	O
the	0	O
newspaper	0	O
''	0	O
Marca	1	S-ORG
''	0	O
to	0	O
focus	0	O
on	0	O
Real	2	B-ORG
Madrid	2	E-ORG
's	0	O
victory	0	O
in	0	O
Eighth	3	B-MISC
European	3	I-MISC
Cup	3	E-MISC
and	0	O
become	0	O
the	0	O
team	0	O
that	0	O
has	0	O
won	0	O
the	0	O
most	0	O
in	0	O
this	0	O
competition	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
final	0	O
of	0	O
Copa	1	B-MISC
del	1	I-MISC
Rey	1	E-MISC
that	0	O
Espanyol	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Atlético	3	B-ORG
de	3	I-ORG
Madrid	3	E-ORG
dispute	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
doubt	0	O
of	0	O
whether	0	O
the	0	O
new	0	O
coach	0	O
of	0	O
Atlético	4	B-ORG
de	4	I-ORG
Madrid	4	E-ORG
,	0	O
Fernando	5	B-PER
Zambrano	5	E-PER
,	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
able	0	O
to	0	O
count	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
presence	0	O
of	0	O
Solari	6	S-PER
or	0	O
Kiko	7	S-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
tennis	0	O
player	0	O
Russian	8	S-MISC
Anna	9	B-PER
Kournikova	9	E-PER
who	0	O
is	0	O
preparing	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
Roland	10	B-MISC
Garros	10	E-MISC
tournament	0	O
in	0	O
Mallorca	11	S-LOC
,	0	O
configure	0	O
the	0	O
news	0	O
bulletin	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
newspaper	0	O
.	0	O

Diario	1	B-ORG
''	1	I-ORG
As	1	E-ORG
''	0	O
focuses	0	O
on	0	O
Real	2	B-ORG
Madrid	2	E-ORG
's	0	O
8th	0	O
European	3	B-MISC
Cup	3	E-MISC
win	0	O
after	0	O
beating	0	O
Valencia	4	S-ORG
3	0	O
0	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
final	0	O
held	0	O
on	0	O
Paris	5	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
statements	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
president	0	O
of	0	O
Real	1	B-ORG
Madrid	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Lorenzo	2	B-PER
Sanz	2	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
team	0	O
coach	0	O
,	0	O
Vicente	3	B-PER
Del	3	I-PER
Bosque	3	E-PER
,	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
match	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
played	0	O
in	0	O
Paris	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
the	0	O
final	0	O
of	0	O
ACB	5	B-MISC
League	5	E-MISC
that	0	O
faces	0	O
Real	6	B-ORG
Madrid	6	E-ORG
and	0	O
Barcelona	7	S-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
Italian	0	O
club	0	O
of	0	O
Juventus	8	S-ORG
that	0	O
''	0	O
offers	0	O
7,500	0	O
million	0	O
for	0	O
Anelka	9	S-PER
''	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
Copa	10	B-MISC
del	10	I-MISC
Rey	10	E-MISC
final	0	O
match	0	O
between	0	O
Atlético	11	B-ORG
de	11	I-ORG
Madrid	11	E-ORG
and	0	O
Espanyol	12	S-ORG
complete	0	O
the	0	O
sports	0	O
news	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
newspaper	0	O
.	0	O

Real	1	B-ORG
Madrid	1	E-ORG
's	0	O
3	0	O
0	0	O
win	0	O
over	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
in	0	O
the	0	O
Champions	3	B-MISC
League	3	E-MISC
final	0	O
played	0	O
at	0	O
Paris	4	S-LOC
draws	0	O
the	0	O
attention	0	O
of	0	O
Barcelona	5	S-LOC
newspapers	0	O
.	0	O

''	0	O
Real	1	B-ORG
Madrid	1	E-ORG
overcame	0	O
.	0	O
an	0	O
Valencia	2	S-ORG
that	0	O
was	0	O
challenged	0	O
''	0	O
titled	0	O
''	0	O
Mundo	3	B-ORG
Deportivo	3	E-ORG
''	0	O
to	0	O
focus	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
little	0	O
resistance	0	O
that	0	O
Valencia	4	S-ORG
showed	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
European	5	B-MISC
Cup	5	E-MISC
final	0	O
that	0	O
was	0	O
played	0	O
in	0	O
Paris	6	S-LOC
and	0	O
in	0	O
which	0	O
Real	7	B-ORG
Madrid	7	E-ORG
emerged	0	O
victorious	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
latest	0	O
electoral	0	O
news	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Barcelona	0	O
club	0	O
that	0	O
focuses	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
consensus	0	O
for	0	O
Guardiola	1	S-PER
,	0	O
Figo	2	S-PER
and	0	O
Rivaldo	3	S-PER
to	0	O
continue	0	O
''	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
coach	0	O
of	0	O
Celta	4	S-ORG
,	0	O
Víctor	5	B-PER
Fernández	5	E-PER
,	0	O
who	0	O
will	0	O
renew	0	O
for	0	O
next	0	O
season	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
ACB	6	B-MISC
League	6	E-MISC
final	0	O
that	0	O
pits	0	O
Real	7	B-ORG
Madrid	7	E-ORG
against	0	O
Barca	8	S-ORG
complete	0	O
the	0	O
rest	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
newspaper	0	O
's	0	O
sports	0	O
news	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
newspaper	0	O
''	0	O
Sport	1	S-ORG
''	0	O
focuses	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
Champions	2	B-MISC
League	2	E-MISC
final	0	O
that	0	O
Real	3	B-ORG
Madrid	3	E-ORG
and	0	O
Valencia	4	S-ORG
played	0	O
yesterday	0	O
and	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
two	0	O
reactions	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
teams	0	O
:	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
one	0	O
hand	0	O
,	0	O
euphoria	0	O
and	0	O
tears	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
losers	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
other	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
final	0	O
of	0	O
Copa	1	B-MISC
del	1	I-MISC
Rey	1	E-MISC
between	0	O
Atlético	2	B-ORG
de	2	I-ORG
Madrid	2	E-ORG
and	0	O
Espanyol	3	S-ORG
,	0	O
the	0	O
new	0	O
signing	0	O
of	0	O
Real	4	B-ORG
Madrid	4	E-ORG
,	0	O
Albert	5	B-PER
Celades	5	E-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
fans	0	O
of	0	O
Barcelona	6	S-ORG
who	0	O
ask	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
contract	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
player	0	O
Luis	7	B-PER
Figo	7	E-PER
be	0	O
improved	0	O
so	0	O
that	0	O
he	0	O
does	0	O
not	0	O
leave	0	O
and	0	O
the	0	O
final	0	O
of	0	O
Liga	8	B-MISC
ACB	8	E-MISC
between	0	O
Real	9	B-ORG
Madrid	9	E-ORG
and	0	O
Barca	10	S-ORG
focuses	0	O
the	0	O
attention	0	O
of	0	O
this	0	O
newspaper	0	O
.	0	O

Tokyo	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
community	0	O
euro	0	O
fell	0	O
today	0	O
in	0	O
Tokyo	1	S-LOC
against	0	O
the	0	O
Japanese	0	O
yen	0	O
and	0	O
was	0	O
trading	0	O
at	0	O
97.22	0	O
yen	0	O
by	0	O
mid	0	O
afternoon	0	O
,	0	O
compared	0	O
to	0	O
96.25	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
beginning	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

Against	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
dollar	0	O
,	0	O
Euro	1	S-MISC
stood	0	O
at	0	O
0.901	0	O
units	0	O
,	0	O
down	0	O
from	0	O
0.903	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
open	0	O
.	0	O

Tokyo	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFECOM	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
community	0	O
euro	0	O
fell	0	O
today	0	O
in	0	O
Tokyo	1	S-LOC
against	0	O
the	0	O
Japanese	0	O
yen	0	O
and	0	O
was	0	O
trading	0	O
at	0	O
97.22	0	O
yen	0	O
by	0	O
mid	0	O
afternoon	0	O
,	0	O
compared	0	O
to	0	O
96.25	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
beginning	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
.	0	O

Against	0	O
the	0	O
US	0	O
dollar	0	O
,	0	O
Euro	1	S-MISC
stood	0	O
at	0	O
0.901	0	O
units	0	O
,	0	O
down	0	O
from	0	O
0.903	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
open	0	O
.	0	O

Manila	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

A	0	O
man	0	O
armed	0	O
with	0	O
a	0	O
grenade	0	O
parachuted	0	O
into	0	O
a	0	O
neighborhood	0	O
of	0	O
Manila	1	S-LOC
today	0	O
to	0	O
escape	0	O
the	0	O
plane	0	O
he	0	O
had	0	O
tried	0	O
to	0	O
hijack	0	O
from	0	O
Philippine	2	B-ORG
Airlines	2	E-ORG
(	0	O
PAL	3	S-ORG
)	0	O
airlines	0	O
,	0	O
local	0	O
radio	0	O
station	0	O
DZMM	4	S-ORG
reported	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
hijacker	0	O
,	0	O
according	0	O
to	0	O
this	0	O
version	0	O
,	0	O
did	0	O
not	0	O
harm	0	O
the	0	O
crew	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
plane	0	O
and	0	O
jumped	0	O
over	0	O
the	0	O
Antipolo	1	S-LOC
district	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
capital	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
shortly	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
plane	0	O
landed	0	O
without	0	O
problems	0	O
at	0	O
the	0	O
same	0	O
Manila	2	S-LOC
airport	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
plane	0	O
,	0	O
a	0	O
Airbus	1	B-MISC
330	1	E-MISC
with	0	O
280	0	O
passengers	0	O
,	0	O
took	0	O
off	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Davao	2	S-LOC
airport	0	O
,	0	O
at	0	O
Mindanao	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
at	0	O
14:00	0	O
local	0	O
time	0	O
(	0	O
06:00	0	O
GMT	4	S-MISC
)	0	O
and	0	O
was	0	O
scheduled	0	O
to	0	O
land	0	O
at	0	O
Manila	5	S-LOC
time	0	O
.	0	O
half	0	O
later	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
director	0	O
of	0	O
Office	1	B-ORG
of	1	I-ORG
Civil	1	I-ORG
Aviation	1	E-ORG
,	0	O
Antonio	2	B-PER
Gana	2	E-PER
,	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
hijacker	0	O
asked	0	O
the	0	O
pilot	0	O
to	0	O
return	0	O
to	0	O
Davao	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
some	0	O
1,000	0	O
kilometers	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
Manila	4	S-LOC
,	0	O
but	0	O
the	0	O
lack	0	O
of	0	O
fuel	0	O
forced	0	O
him	0	O
to	0	O
continue	0	O
to	0	O
Manila	5	S-LOC
,	0	O
where	0	O
his	0	O
arrival	0	O
is	0	O
expected	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
statements	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
state	0	O
radio	0	O
station	0	O
DZRB	1	S-ORG
,	0	O
Ricardo	2	B-PER
Puno	2	E-PER
,	0	O
spokesman	0	O
for	0	O
the	0	O
president	0	O
Filipino	3	S-MISC
,	0	O
Joseph	4	B-PER
Estrada	4	E-PER
,	0	O
stated	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
hijacker	0	O
was	0	O
part	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
passenger	0	O
and	0	O
was	0	O
carrying	0	O
a	0	O
hand	0	O
grenade	0	O
and	0	O
a	0	O
parachute	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Puno	1	S-PER
,	0	O
the	0	O
air	0	O
pirate	0	O
asked	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
allowed	0	O
to	0	O
parachute	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
plane	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
due	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
flight	0	O
altitude	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
not	0	O
possible	0	O
to	0	O
open	0	O
the	0	O
doors	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
aircraft	0	O
,	0	O
so	0	O
''	0	O
Airbus	2	S-MISC
''	0	O
went	0	O
to	0	O
Manila	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

However	0	O
,	0	O
after	0	O
descending	0	O
the	0	O
plane	0	O
to	0	O
about	0	O
1,800	0	O
meters	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
air	0	O
pirate	0	O
insisted	0	O
on	0	O
his	0	O
purpose	0	O
and	0	O
managed	0	O
to	0	O
parachute	0	O
.	0	O

Jerusalem	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

The	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-ORG
has	0	O
adapted	0	O
its	0	O
concept	0	O
of	0	O
security	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
new	0	O
reality	0	O
created	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
evacuation	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanon	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
which	0	O
consists	0	O
of	0	O
defending	0	O
its	0	O
border	0	O
within	0	O
its	0	O
own	0	O
soil	0	O
instead	0	O
of	0	O
fighting	0	O
against	0	O
the	0	O
fundamentalist	0	O
group	0	O
Hizbullah	4	S-ORG
in	0	O
Lebanese	0	O
territory	0	O
,	0	O
explained	0	O
its	0	O
commander	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
chief	0	O
commander	0	O
of	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-ORG
,	0	O
General	0	O
Shaúl	3	B-PER
Mofaz	3	E-PER
,	0	O
said	0	O
that	0	O
this	0	O
includes	0	O
the	0	O
order	0	O
to	0	O
open	0	O
fire	0	O
,	0	O
although	0	O
he	0	O
considered	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
soldiers	0	O
have	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
very	0	O
careful	0	O
not	0	O
to	0	O
make	0	O
mistakes	0	O
that	0	O
lead	0	O
to	0	O
an	0	O
escalation	0	O
of	0	O
violence	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
means	0	O
that	0	O
the	0	O
Israeli	1	S-MISC
soldiers	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
shoot	0	O
when	0	O
they	0	O
see	0	O
Hezbollah	2	S-ORG
guerrillas	0	O
as	0	O
they	0	O
did	0	O
until	0	O
now	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
Lebanese	3	S-MISC
,	0	O
just	0	O
as	0	O
they	0	O
will	0	O
not	0	O
interfere	0	O
with	0	O
the	0	O
Syrian	0	O
troops	0	O
,	0	O
whose	0	O
country	0	O
actually	0	O
controls	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
.	0	O

Mofaz	1	S-PER
indicated	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
we	0	O
must	0	O
be	0	O
very	0	O
alert	0	O
''	0	O
and	0	O
added	0	O
that	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
coming	0	O
days	0	O
representatives	0	O
of	0	O
UN	2	S-ORG
and	0	O
Army	3	S-ORG
Israeli	4	S-ORG
will	0	O
examine	0	O
the	0	O
exact	0	O
lines	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
international	0	O
border	0	O
with	0	O
Lebanon	5	S-LOC
and	0	O
,	0	O
if	0	O
necessary	0	O
,	0	O
their	0	O
deployment	0	O
will	0	O
be	0	O
adjusted	0	O
.	0	O

Meanwhile	0	O
,	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-ORG
continued	0	O
to	0	O
be	0	O
deployed	0	O
today	0	O
the	0	O
day	0	O
after	0	O
the	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
north	0	O
of	0	O
his	0	O
country	0	O
,	0	O
bordering	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	3	S-LOC
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
Mofaz	1	S-PER
,	0	O
''	0	O
Army	2	S-ORG
Israeli	3	S-MISC
left	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
(	0	O
at	0	O
dawn	0	O
yesterday	0	O
,	0	O
Wednesday	0	O
)	0	O
in	0	O
an	0	O
appropriate	0	O
manner	0	O
and	0	O
without	0	O
casualties	0	O
in	0	O
its	0	O
ranks	0	O
,	0	O
despite	0	O
the	0	O
fact	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
a	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
under	0	O
fire	0	O
''	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
group	0	O
Lebanese	5	S-MISC
pro	0	O
Iranian	6	S-MISC
Hizbullah	7	S-ORG
(	0	O
God	8	B-ORG
's	8	I-ORG
Party	8	E-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
became	0	O
with	0	O
control	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
abandoned	0	O
area	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
neighboring	0	O
Arab	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
general	0	O
pointed	0	O
out	0	O
that	0	O
at	0	O
least	0	O
twelve	0	O
guerrillas	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
Shia	0	O
group	0	O
Hezbollah	1	S-ORG
died	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
fighting	0	O
,	0	O
which	0	O
also	0	O
took	0	O
weapons	0	O
left	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
ground	0	O
by	0	O
Israeli	2	S-MISC
soldiers	0	O
and	0	O
militiamen	0	O
from	0	O
Army	3	B-ORG
of	3	I-ORG
South	3	I-ORG
Lebanon	3	E-ORG
(	0	O
SLA	4	S-ORG
)	0	O
,	0	O
an	0	O
ally	0	O
of	0	O
Israel	5	S-LOC
.	0	O

The	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-ORG
commander	0	O
in	0	O
chief	0	O
stressed	0	O
that	0	O
it	0	O
was	0	O
important	0	O
for	0	O
his	0	O
troops	0	O
to	0	O
get	0	O
out	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
quick	0	O
operation	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
dark	0	O
and	0	O
before	0	O
it	0	O
got	0	O
light	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
that	0	O
soldiers	0	O
were	0	O
not	0	O
justified	0	O
in	0	O
putting	0	O
their	0	O
lives	0	O
at	0	O
risk	0	O
for	0	O
weapons	0	O
left	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
ground	0	O
.	0	O

Finally	0	O
,	0	O
Mofaz	1	S-PER
warned	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
I	0	O
do	0	O
not	0	O
advise	0	O
anyone	0	O
,	0	O
including	0	O
Palestinians	0	O
,	0	O
to	0	O
draw	0	O
the	0	O
wrong	0	O
conclusions	0	O
about	0	O
Army	2	S-ORG
Israeli	3	S-MISC
's	0	O
responsiveness	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

In	0	O
this	0	O
regard	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
well	0	O
known	0	O
journalist	0	O
Palestinian	1	S-MISC
Daud	2	B-PER
Kutab	2	E-PER
asks	0	O
himself	0	O
,	0	O
in	0	O
a	0	O
column	0	O
published	0	O
today	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Israeli	3	S-MISC
newspaper	0	O
''	0	O
Jerusalem	4	B-ORG
Post	4	E-ORG
''	0	O
:	0	O
''	0	O
How	0	O
can	0	O
we	0	O
convince	0	O
people	0	O
that	0	O
non	0	O
violent	0	O
resistance	0	O
works	0	O
,	0	O
when	0	O
we	0	O
see	0	O
that	0	O
armed	0	O
resistance	0	O
(	0	O
from	0	O
Hezbollah	5	S-ORG
)	0	O
works	0	O
while	0	O
negotiations	0	O
fail	0	O
?	0	O

''	0	O
.	0	O

As	0	O
for	0	O
Lebanon	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
Israel	2	S-LOC
recognizes	0	O
its	0	O
sovereignty	0	O
over	0	O
its	0	O
entire	0	O
territory	0	O
,	0	O
but	0	O
demands	0	O
that	0	O
Beirut	3	S-LOC
guarantee	0	O
a	0	O
secure	0	O
border	0	O
and	0	O
,	0	O
if	0	O
this	0	O
is	0	O
not	0	O
achieved	0	O
,	0	O
Army	4	S-ORG
Israeli	5	S-MISC
is	0	O
prepared	0	O
for	0	O
a	0	O
series	0	O
of	0	O
responses	0	O
and	0	O
retaliation	0	O
.	0	O

This	0	O
was	0	O
announced	0	O
in	0	O
recent	0	O
days	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Israeli	1	S-MISC
prime	0	O
minister	0	O
,	0	O
Ehud	2	B-PER
Barak	2	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
also	0	O
by	0	O
Mofaz	3	S-PER
himself	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Foreign	4	B-ORG
Affairs	4	E-ORG
minister	0	O
,	0	O
David	5	B-PER
Levy	5	E-PER
,	0	O
and	0	O
other	0	O
leaders	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
blamed	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanese	6	S-MISC
and	0	O
Syrian	0	O
governments	0	O
for	0	O
maintaining	0	O
calm	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
border	0	O
.	0	O

That	0	O
is	0	O
to	0	O
say	0	O
,	0	O
if	0	O
fire	0	O
is	0	O
fired	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	1	S-LOC
against	0	O
the	0	O
north	0	O
of	0	O
Israel	2	S-LOC
,	0	O
Army	3	S-ORG
Israeli	4	S-ORG
will	0	O
immediately	0	O
launch	0	O
a	0	O
retaliation	0	O
against	0	O
Lebanese	5	S-MISC
,	0	O
Syrian	0	O
and	0	O
even	0	O
Iranian	6	S-MISC
interests	0	O
throughout	0	O
that	0	O
neighboring	0	O
Arab	0	O
country	0	O
.	0	O

To	0	O
defend	0	O
the	0	O
borders	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-MISC
decided	0	O
to	0	O
set	0	O
up	0	O
fortified	0	O
positions	0	O
in	0	O
their	0	O
own	0	O
towns	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
north	0	O
of	0	O
their	0	O
territory	0	O
,	0	O
where	0	O
their	0	O
more	0	O
than	0	O
250,000	0	O
inhabitants	0	O
have	0	O
often	0	O
been	0	O
the	0	O
target	0	O
of	0	O
attacks	0	O
from	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Lebanon	3	S-LOC
,	0	O
in	0	O
particular	0	O
by	0	O
''	0	O
Katiusha	4	S-MISC
''	0	O
rockets	0	O
fired	0	O
by	0	O
the	0	O
Hizbullah	5	S-ORG
.	0	O

Military	0	O
commentators	0	O
today	0	O
note	0	O
that	0	O
Army	1	S-ORG
Israeli	2	S-MISC
will	0	O
have	0	O
more	0	O
troops	0	O
to	0	O
the	0	O
south	0	O
,	0	O
prepared	0	O
to	0	O
respond	0	O
with	0	O
new	0	O
techniques	0	O
,	0	O
as	0	O
well	0	O
as	0	O
with	0	O
great	0	O
speed	0	O
and	0	O
mobility	0	O
,	0	O
while	0	O
maintaining	0	O
a	0	O
''	0	O
low	0	O
profile	0	O
''	0	O
on	0	O
the	0	O
border	0	O
itself	0	O
.	0	O

Faced	0	O
with	0	O
this	0	O
new	0	O
situation	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
military	0	O
commentator	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
prestigious	0	O
Israeli	1	S-MISC
''	0	O
Haaretz	2	S-ORG
''	0	O
newspaper	0	O
,	0	O
Zeev	3	B-PER
Schiff	3	E-PER
,	0	O
concludes	0	O
that	0	O
''	0	O
the	0	O
withdrawal	0	O
of	0	O
Lebanon	4	S-LOC
does	0	O
not	0	O
mean	0	O
the	0	O
end	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
conflict	0	O
''	0	O
.	0	O

Ceuta	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
May	0	O
25	0	O
(	0	O
EFE	2	S-ORG
)	0	O
.	0	O

-	0	O

Two	0	O
young	0	O
people	0	O
,	0	O
both	0	O
natives	0	O
of	0	O
Morocco	1	S-LOC
,	0	O
face	0	O
a	0	O
six	0	O
year	0	O
prison	0	O
sentence	0	O
accused	0	O
of	0	O
having	0	O
stuck	0	O
a	0	O
knife	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
head	0	O
of	0	O
another	0	O
young	0	O
man	0	O
,	0	O
also	0	O
Moroccan	0	O
,	0	O
who	0	O
was	0	O
robbed	0	O
of	0	O
1,500	0	O
pesetas	0	O
when	0	O
he	0	O
was	0	O
on	0	O
a	0	O
beach	0	O
in	0	O
Ceuta	0	O
.	0	O

According	0	O
to	0	O
judicial	0	O
sources	0	O
,	0	O
the	0	O
Court	1	S-ORG
Criminal	2	B-LOC
Court	2	I-LOC
number	2	I-LOC
2	2	E-LOC
of	0	O
Ceuta	3	S-LOC
has	0	O
judged	0	O
RE	4	B-PER
Ch	4	E-PER
today	0	O
.	0	O
and	0	O
MM	5	S-PER
,	0	O
for	0	O
which	0	O
the	0	O
prosecutor	0	O
is	0	O
asking	0	O
for	0	O
six	0	O
years	0	O
in	0	O
prison	0	O
,	0	O
two	0	O
for	0	O
injuries	0	O
and	0	O
four	0	O
for	0	O
robbery	0	O
.	0	O

The	0	O
events	0	O
in	0	O
court	0	O
occurred	0	O
on	0	O
January	0	O
2	0	O
when	0	O
both	0	O
young	0	O
people	0	O
presumably	0	O
attacked	0	O
a	0	O
third	0	O
party	0	O
in	0	O
the	0	O
vicinity	0	O
of	0	O
the	0	O
Ribera	1	S-LOC
beach	0	O
,	0	O
and	0	O
stole	0	O
1,500	0	O
pesetas	0	O
and	0	O
two	0	O
sleeping	0	O
bags	0	O
after	0	O
inflicting	0	O
a	0	O
knife	0	O
on	0	O
his	0	O
head	0	O
that	0	O
caused	0	O
his	0	O
hospitalization	0	O
.	0	O
